<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resource>XTM Test Key in the file flashres.xmlNo clanPlease log in againNo hit points left. Repair your ship in the hangar or buy a new ship!You're not logged in. Go to the homepage and log in to continue playing!NoteWarningErrorYou're already logged in on the map.  Please close the other browser window.You can make a jump if your level allows it._You can't use this portal: You need to have at least level %!Unable to attack: You didn't select an opponent.%! collectedCollecting %!Cargo bay full! Sell your raw materials at the space station.You collected:Salvaging %!%! destroyedWarning: If you attack a spaceship from your own company, honor points and credits will be deducted.Collecting box alreadyThe resources are already being gathered.Aborting attack. Not enough laser ammo for an attack.No repair necessaryRepairs startedLogout not possibleYou canceled the logout process.Repairs completed. Your spaceship now has 100% hit points.You need level %! for the jump. Not possible to jump from your level.Raw material collection failedCargo bay is full.You escaped the attack.Out of rangeDemilitarized zoneThe battle continues.The battle was canceled.Your opponent canceled the battle.Your connection was interrupted.Attack on %! was canceled.Attacking: %!%! is under attack.No laser ammo left - buy new laser ammoLog-disksYour connection was interrupted.Error - please check your ship for damage.Cloaking detectedShip uncloakedWarning! Mine launched - 5 seconds until armed.CARGO BAYURIDIUMCREDITSEXPERIENCELEVELHONORJACKPOT EUROHIT POINTSSHIELDROCKETSAMMOLASER ATTACKROCKET ATTACKROCKET MENULASER MENUPORTAL JUMPROBOTS + EXTRASREPAIRHELPLOGOUTCOMPANY CHATGLOBAL CHATREPLAYMAP/POSDARKORBIT INTROMini-map legendOwn shipCompany memberEnemy ship/NPCAggressive enemyHome baseJump portalDEMILITARIZED ZONEPlease UPDATE your Flash player!UPDATECANCELWARNINGRADIATION LEVEL ABOVE THE TOLERANCE LIMITRETURN TO A SAFE ZONE BEFORE YOU ARE DESTROYED.Radiation level above the tolerance limit. Return to a safe zone before you're destroyed.LOGOUTLOGGING OUT INSECONDSCANCELDEMILITARIZED ZONERESOURCE OUTPOSTPLEASE ENTER HOW MANY RAW MATERIALS YOU WANT TO SELL:VALUESELLSPACE STATIONVALUESELLTO THE LABOKSHIPSWEAPONSAMMOGENERATORSEXTRASCREDITSMISSIONSCLANHALL OF FAMESELL RESOURCES:SELL RESOURCES:Sell ResourcesPrometiumEnduriumTerbiumPrometidDURANIODuraniumPromeriumPrometiumEnduriumTerbiumPrometidDuraniumPromeriumXenomitPrepare raw material shipmentSend droneJUMP PORTALSHIP DESTROYEDYour ship has just been destroyed. To continue playing, repair your spaceship or buy yourself a new one.OKOKCONNECTION INFORMATIONThe connection was interrupted.You're no longer connected to the DarkOrbit game server. Do you wish to reconnect?New connectionLogoutCANCELEstablishing connection ...Please wait ...STARTLOAD STAR SYSTEMLOADINGSettingsAutomatic weapons upgrade by activating lab CPUShow damage barShow all lasersShow explosionsShow player namesShow company iconShow transparent backgroundShow resourcesShow bonus boxesShow NPCs/enemiesShow jump portalsShow increasing hit countShow message statusShow chatPlay musicMusic volumePlay sound effectsSound Effects volumeBoard Computer volumePlay combat musicShow ammo/HP/shields with numbersShow dronesHide star chart automatically after jumpShow cargo boxesShow cargo boxes which are not freeShow minimap backgroundChange ammo/rocket type automaticallyShow "Buy now" menu for ammo on the space mapShow my dronesShow lens flareShow meteorsShow space dustLog into client automaticallyDouble-click to launch attackShow backgroundShow Battleray notificationsShow low HP warningAuto-equip new itemsAlways allow draggable windowsPreload shipsSimplify shipsSimple resources and boxesShow engine tracksShow engine tracksAutomatically adjust quality settingsHover ship when idleDisplay premium quickslot barPurchase green booty keys automatically.Some quality settings will be temporarily reduced when the CPU load is too high. When this load is reduced, the quality settings will be increased to the previously specified levels.When activated, ships will slowly move up and down while idling.This setting activates / deactivates the premium quickslot bar. Warning: The keyboard settings will not be active when the premium quickslot bar is deactivated.MISSHITSaveChanges savedChanges will take effect after the space map has been reloaded.Greetings Space Pilots!Let the journey to a galaxy far, far away begin.Your spaceship is located in the center of the space map. Click on the map to move your ship around space and fly by holding down your mouse button. Use the mini map on the bottom right to travel long distances. The crosshairs on the mini map show your spaceship's location in the universe.Click on LASERS or ROCKETS to fire your weapons at enemies.Here are some useful tips to help you on your space odyssey:1. Your ship is currently located in the demilitarized zone surrounding your space station.2. Collect raw materials in space and exchange them at your space station for Credits.3. Be careful not to attack ships from your own company.4. Collect experience points by shooting down aliens and enemy ships.You're connected to the game server.Establishing connectionYou successfully complete the mission.You have successfully completed this mission and received your reward.You have successfully completed %COUNT% missions and received your reward.You canceled the mission.Your rating: %POINTS% pointsRaw material mission:NPC KILL Mission:Company Mission:STAR SYSTEMPORTALSJumping is only possible 15 seconds after re-login.Special ship - can't attack and can't be attackedRemaining mines: %!Mission time remaining: %!Mission time expired.Game server will restart in %! minutes.Game server will restart in %! seconds.Restarting game serverGame server will shut down in %! minutes.Game server will shut down in %! seconds.Your cargo box was stolen by: %!Attack protection was lifted - time for you to fight!%! minutes attack protection remaining%! seconds of attack protection remaining%! minutes until relocation to the semi-final map.%! seconds until relocation to the semi-final map.%! minutes until relocation to the final map.%! seconds until relocation to the final map.Your ship doesn't have any laser cannons. That's why you can't attack.Your ship doesn't have any laser cannons. That's why you can't attack.Rocket type cannot be used without equiping a rocket launcher!Columbus CoinsSpace TurkeyAdvent Star collectedSmall Advent star collectedLarge Advent star collectedBonus boxCargo boxEaster eggYou found the following special item: %!Banking DoublerBanking TriplerBanking Quadrupler%! activeYou still have one %MULTI% to use!You found a %MULTI%!%MULTI% found%MULTI% activeMega Happy Hour has begun!1 minute remaining until Mega Happy Hour ends%MINS% minutes remaining until Mega Happy Hour ends%SECS% seconds remaining until Mega Happy Hour ends%TIME% remaining until Mega Happy Hour endsHappy Hour has begun!1 minute remaining until Happy Hour ends%MINS% minutes remaining until Happy Hour ends%SECS% seconds remaining until Happy Hour ends%TIME% remaining until Happy Hour endsChristmas star collectedSmall Christmas star collectedLarge Christmas star collectedCongratulations!You reached level %!.For the next level-up, you need %! EP.You now have the rank:Equipping is now available. Visit the hangar (on website) if you'd like to equip or change your ship.Equipping is not available at the moment.ConfigurationAutomatic restocking purchase of ammunition failed - not enough CreditAutomatic ammo purchase with Ammunition CPUYour were not able to automatically purchase more cannons because you do not have enough Credit.Automatic rocket purchase with Rocket CPUJump not possible - you're in the middle of a battle.Jump not possible - to use the Jump CPU, you need to be out of combat for 20 seconds after engaging another pilot.Jump not possible - to use the Jump CPU, you need to be out of combat for 5 seconds after engaging an alien vessel.Jump not possible - you're already on the target map.Jump from the current map not possible with your CPU!ERROR42 - error with your Jump CPU!Automatic rocket upgrade with Lab CPUAutomatic laser upgrade with Lab CPURaw materials were automatically refined.Jump not possible: Your last jump or (last) login was less than 10 seconds ago.Jump not possible! You can't escape from a battle map when you're fighting in a battle.Jump not possible! You're not located close enough to a jump gate.PointsMultiTotalMaster of the OrbitSpace CleanerDark PilotEmperorNewbieGoli HunterBossAlien HunterSharpshooterSpace WhizOrbit KingPhoenix ShockChaos PilotMost WantedPortal GuardBattle MasterSystem LordThe LegendPvP Hunter of the DayPirate HunterSpring Fighter MMO 2Spring Fighter EIC 2Spring Fighter VRU 2Spring Fighter MMOSpring Fighter VRUSpring Fighter EICSpring Fighter MMO 2Spring Fighter VRU 2Spring Fighter EIC 2Spring King MMOSpring King EICSpring King VRUPirate-Hunting ChampionPirate HunterPirate DestroyerPirate AnnihilatorAll-StarBoss of BossesLord of LikesTime killerError in space-time continuum?MatadorDeath-defyingOrbit drifterGodfatherEnlightenedHonoredTranscendentExpertLegendP.E.T. Animal TrainerP.E.T. commanderNinja MasterRock 'n' Roll, baby!Lazer GunZ!Swarm of rocketsOrbital BombardmentOne-man ArmyWorld DestroyerFireworks, fireworks!SupernovaKilltastic!DestroyerBoxful of richesKing of the BoxesCredit BillionaireCroesusMind on my moneyKing MidasButcherThe ReaperUltimate Drone CommanderOrbit TrotterProdigyAll-around Master30 second battleDrone CommanderSpring King MMOSpring King EICSpring King VRUPirate Hunt Champion IIPirate Hunters IILurkerHollow ManInterfererBuzz KillerCoordinatorStrike LeaderEnemy SpotterOracleTop MedicFleet EngineerGuardianElectrifierMobile MechanicWorkshop WonderTeam PlayerDamage MagnetAcceleratorSpace RunnerLifesaverProtectorScapegoatIndestructibleFootball OfficialBlizzardAttack wave %COUNT% started%GATE% put in positionAttack waveInvasionAttack wave %COUNT%5 years DarkOrbit Thank you for your support and faith.DarkOrbit's 6th birthday Thank you for your continued support!a Gateß Gate? Gate999/1,000 Gated GateAlpha GateBeta GateGamma Gate999/1,000 GateDelta GateYou reached level %!. Please complete registration so that you can continue playing with your spaceship.GUEST%! lives leftLaunching mines is only possible %! seconds after login or after a server change.You can launch the next mine in %! seconds.Connection to the game server failed. Reloading window.Quality: %QLT%LowMediumHigh%COUNT% %TYPE% rockets purchased%COUNT% rounds of %TYPE% laser ammo purchasedAmmo purchase failed! Not enough Uridium.Ammo purchase failed! Not enough Credits.Ammo purchase failed! Not enough room on board.Ammo purchase failed! No ammunition for sale.Smart bomb can't be lit - you don't have enough mines.Smart bomb can't be lit - you don't have enough Xenomit.You can light the next smart bomb in %SECONDS% seconds.Insta-shield can't be started - you don't have enough mines.Insta-shield can't be started - you don't have enough Xenomit.You can start the next Insta-shield in %SECONDS% seconds.No rockets of this type left - automatic rocket attack canceledAutomatic upgrade of speed generators by the Generator Boost CPUAutomatic upgrade of shield generators by the Generator Boost CPUThe Cloaking CPU doesn't work here.Cloaking failedWarning: Configuration can only be changed every 5 seconds.Warning: The Targeting Guidance CPU isn't working. You don't have enough Xenomit.Team DeathmatchTDMRegister for Team DeathmatchLog inThis is a special jump portal which you, as a Team Deathmatch participant, can use to log in.Countdown until the next game round: %COUNTDOWN%Countdown: %COUNTDOWN%Your current position in your company's waiting list is %POSITION%.Waiting list position: %POSITION%There are currently %MATCHES% games in progress.Games: %MATCHES%Players left on your team: %COUNT%Friends: %COUNT%Players left on the opponent's team: %COUNT%Enemies: %COUNT%Team Deathmatch Combo: %COMBO%Combo: %COMBO%%COMPANY1% versus %COMPANY2%versusThe ships which registered for the Team Deathmatch will now be placed on the game map.All participants for the next TDM round have been chosen.You're not in the current TDM round. Your waiting list position is #%POSITION%.Non-Attack PhaseWarning: You're leaving the TDM starting zone and entering a dangerous radioactive zone.Attack countdown: %COUNTDOWN%Attack protection has been lifted. You may now fight!Current round will end in %SECONDS% seconds.Your team won the round with %COUNT% survivors.The winning team will be restored with %COUNT% new players.Sorry, there aren't enough players available. Your team will be removed from the map. Your group constellation will remain until your next round.Your team lost the round with %COUNT% survivors.You'll be removed from the map.DrawDraw: Both teams lose and will be removed from the map.Final scoreRepair your ship and prepare for the next round.Visit the Hall of Fame to view the Team Deathmatch results and statistics.Your level is too high to play in this Team Deathmatch. Try out %MAP% map instead!Your time is being recordedHurry up!Complete in less than %TIME%You must have at least 0 Honor!Complete this mission within %TIME%!This mission will expire in:Hang in there for at least %TIME%Stick around as long as possible!Stay for at least %TIME% consecutivelyCollect %ore%Collect as much %ore% as possibleDestroy %npc%Destroy as many %npc% as possibleDestroy enemy players.Destroy enemy %types%Destroy as many %types% as possibleDestroy %faction% shipsDestroy as many %faction% ships as possibleDestroy %faction% %types% shipsDestroy as many %faction% %types% as possibleHunt down %avatars%Kill %npcs%Destroy as many %npcs% as possibleDon't destroy more than %count% %npc%Destroy as few %npc% as possible.Don't destroy any %npc%Don't destroy more than %count% %npcs%Destroy as few %npcs% as possibleDon't destroy any %npcs%Don't destroy more than %count% ships from other playersDon't destroy more than one ship from other playersDon't destroy any ships from other playersDon't destroy more than %count% enemy %types%Don't destroy more than one enemy %types% shipDon't destroy any %types%Don't destroy more than %count% %faction% shipsDon't destroy more than one %faction% shipDon't destroy any %faction% shipsDon't destroy more than %count% %faction% %types% shipsDon't destroy more than one %faction% %types% shipDon't destroy any %faction% %types% shipsYou're not allowed to destroy %avatars%.All damage to your ship will be recorded.Laser damage to your ship will be recorded.Rocket damage to your ship will be recorded.Mine damage to your ship will be recorded.Radiation damage to your ship will be recorded.Laser and rocket damage to your ship will be recorded.Let the enemy damage your shipLet the enemy damage your ship with lasersLet the enemy damage your ship with rocketsLet the enemy damage your ship with minesLet the enemy damage your ship with radiationLet the enemy damage your ship with lasers and rocketsAvoid being damagedAvoid being damaged by lasersAvoid being damaged by rocketsAvoid being damaged by minesAvoid being damaged by radiationAvoid being damaged by lasers and rocketsWatch your tail: don't get killed!You can only die %count% times.to coordinates %x%/%y%Keep an eye on how far you travelTravel the target distanceAvoid movingGet as close as possible to %opponent%on %map% mapBeon maps: %maps%on an enemy mapon a PvP mapuncloakedcloakedIn a radiation zonewith an active Insta-shieldwith less than a tenth of your maximum hit pointsattackingattackedattacked without defending yourselfwith an active repairbotoutlawon your home mapon an enemy X-1 mapon a 1-X mapon a 2-X mapon a 3-X mapon one of your company's mapson an X-1 mapon an X-2 mapon an X-3 mapon an X-4 mapon an X-5 mapon an X-6 mapon an X-7 mapon an X-8 mapPay attention to the amount of ammo usedPay attention to the amount of laser ammo usedPay attention to the amount of %type% laser ammo usedPay attention to the amount of rockets usedPay attention to the number of %type% rockets usedPay attention to the amount of mines usedDon't use any weaponsDon't use any laser ammoDon't use any %type% laser ammoUse less than %count% rounds of laser ammoUse less than %count% rounds of %type% laser ammoDon't use any rocketsDon't use any %type% rocketsUse less than %count% rocketsUse less than %count% %type% rocketsDon't use any minesUse less than %count% minesUse %count% rounds of laser ammoUse as much laser ammo as possibleUse %count% rounds of %type% laser ammoUse as much %type% laser ammo as possibleUse %count% rocketsUse as many rockets as possibleUse %count% %type% rocketsUse as many %type% rockets as possibleUse %count% minesUse as many mines as possibleCollect ore from destroyed shipsCollect as much ore as possible from destroyed shipsCollect %ore% from destroyed shipsCollect as much %ore% as possible from destroyed shipsCollect ore from destroyed %npc% shipsCollect as much ore as possible from destroyed %npc% shipsCollect %ore% from destroyed %npc% shipsCollect as much %ore% as possible from destroyed %npc% shipsCollect ore from destroyed %faction% shipsCollect as much ore as possible from destroyed %faction% shipsCollect %ore% from destroyed %faction% shipsCollect as much %ore% as possible from destroyed %faction% shipsCollect ore from destroyed %ship%Collect as much ore as possible from destroyed %ship% shipsCollect %ore% from destroyed %ship%Collect as much %ore% as possible from destroyed %ship% shipsCollect ore from destroyed %faction% %ship% shipsCollect as much ore as possible from destroyed %faction% %ship% shipsCollect %ore% from destroyed %faction% %ship% shipsCollect as much %ore% as possible from destroyed %faction% %ship% shipsSteal the cargo boxes from opponentsSteal as many of your opponents' cargo boxesSteal cargo boxes from %ship% shipsSteal as many %ship% cargo boxes as possibleSteal cargo boxes from %faction% pilotsSteal as many cargo boxes as possible from pilots of the %faction% companySteal cargo boxes from %faction% %ship% shipsSteal as many cargo boxes as possible from %faction% %ship% shipsSteal cargo boxes from enemy %ship% ships.Steal cargo boxes from your opponents.Steal as many cargo boxes from enemy %ship% ships as possible.Steal as many cargo boxes from your opponents as possible.Destroy %opponent_type%Inflict %damage_type% damage to your opponentsDamage NPCsDamage NPCs with lasersDamage NPCs with rocketsDamage NPCs with lasers and rocketsDamage %npcs%Damage %npcs% with lasersDamage %npcs% with rocketsDamage %npcs% with lasers and rocketsDamage any playersDamage the enemy companies' players with lasersDamage the enemy companies' players with rocketsDamage the enemy companies' players with minesDamage the enemy companies' players with lasers and rocketsDamage %types%Damage %types% with lasersDamage %types% with rocketsDamage %types% with minesDamage %types% with lasers and rocketsDamage %faction% playersDamage %faction% players with lasersDamage %faction% players with rocketsDamage %faction% players with minesDamage %faction% players with lasers and rocketsDamage %faction% %types%Füge %types% feindlicher Firmen Schaden zu.Damage %faction% %types% with lasersDamage %faction% %types% with rocketsDamage %faction% %types% with minesDamage %faction% %types% with lasers and rocketsDamage %avatars%Damage %avatars% with lasersDamage %avatars% with rocketsDamage %avatars% with minesDamage %avatars% with lasers and rocketsDestroy enemy ships using %laser% laser ammo.Destroy %faction% ships using %laser% laser ammo.Destroy enemy %ship% ships using %laser% laser ammo.Destroy %faction% %ship% ships using %laser% laser ammo.Destroy enemy ships using %rocket% rockets.Destroy %faction% ships using %rocket% rockets.Destroy %ship% ships using %rocket% rockets.Destroy %faction% %ship% ships using %rocket% rockets.Destroy %npc% enemies using %laser% laser ammo.Destroy NPCs using %laser% laser ammo.Destroy %npc% enemies using %rocket% rockets.Destroy NPCs using %rocket% rockets.Destroy %npc% enemies without using lasers.Destroy NPCs without using lasers.Destroy %npc% enemies without using rockets.Destroy NPCs without using rockets.Collect %count% bonus boxes.Reach level %count%.Sell %ore%.Gain influenceUse a jump gate.Upgrade your speed and/or shield generator with Promerium.Use the "Buy now" function to get more rockets or laser ammo.Invite another player to join a group or receive an invite from another player to join a group.Fly back to Mission Control.The smaller your ship is, the more bonus points you'll receive.Travel to %map% mapClick on the "Help" button.Join an group with at least %count% membersIn a groupComplete %count% of the following tasksCompleteComplete in order:Don't damage other player"%quest_name%" accepted"%quest_name%" completed"%quest_name%" canceled"%quest_name%" canceledYou failed to complete: "%quest_name%"DMG X1DMG X2DMG X3DMG X4SABR310PLT-2026PLT-2021Tutorial MissionsCongratulations!  You've completed the tutorial and are now a full-fledged member of the %faction%. Embark on your outer space journey and discover the far reaches of the DarkOrbit universe.  Have a blast!Activate the following item: %TYPE%Use the Jump Gate between %FROM% and %TO%Visit the following maps: %map%Collect %TYPE%Fight off the Devolarium attack.Complete the Galaxy Gate %TYPE%.Cold Wave (easy)Cold Wave (hard)P.E.T Attack (easy)P.E.T Attack (hard)Join a ClanRefine raw materials to produce %TYPE%.Equip %ITEM% into %SLOT% in %BAR%Equip %ITEM% to %BAR%Upgrade your %TARGET% with %TYPE%Boost your lasers with %TYPE%Boost your rockets with %TYPE%Boost your speed generators with %TYPE%Boost your shields with %TYPE%Fly to the following location: %TYPE%Collect cargo boxesLet yourself be destroyedCollect as many cargo boxes as possibleUpgrade %TYPE% to next levelPromerium RefineryTODOTODOTODOTODOPrometium collectorTODOTODOTODOTODOTODOTODOYou need to upgrade your %TYPE% to level %COUNT%Capture %amount%x Beacons in "Capture the Beacon"Capture %amount%x Sector Control BeaconsCapture %amount%x Domination BeaconsVisit P.E.T. disrupting zones on the following maps:Collect an assembled item from the AssemblyCollect %amount% assembled items from the AssemblyCollect an assembled %recipeId% from the AssemblyCollect %amount% assembled %recipeId%s from the Assembly%BOOSTERNAME% (%HOURS% hours) receivedYou can't attack any friendly ships on your company's first two maps!You can't attack any players on a base map!%VALUE% Credits%VALUE% C.%VALUE% Uridium%VALUE% U.You were hit by a hologram-emitter rocket. Your ship's appearance has now been temporarily altered.The hologram emitter has lost its effect: Your ship looks normal again.Welcome to DarkOrbit's Open %VERSION%!  Help us find the errors and bugs in this test version before the final version goes live.  Report any errors you find in the game in the forum: %BOARD_LINK% You'll also find a detailed description of how to create a good bug report there. It'll help us get the job done quicker!  Please remember that there is no e-mail support for this test environment. That's why you'll have to clarify all problems and questions in the Beta forum.  We reserve the right to close the test server or reset accounts at any time.  Have a blast testing, Your DarkOrbit TeamFor a limited time only - special boosters available in the shop now!Happy Hour! Now's the time to get your Uridium at a bargain price!Mega happy hour! Now's the time to get your Uridium at a bargain price!Time remaining for registrationDraft periodChatCreditsUridiumAmount: %COUNT%Light fireworksHelpSettingsTradeJumpYou can only jump from a portal.Fast repairImmediate repairs on your home base only.MissionsLogoutLogMini mapUserShipHit pointsNanohullShieldExperienceLevel: %COUNT%Upgrade Level: %COUNT%HonorJackpotCargo baySpeedDamageAmmoRocketsLasersRocketsSpecial ammoCPUsBuy nowConfiguration: %COUNT%NameLaser selectedRocket selectedSpecial ammoModule Type: %TYPE%Module Owner: %NAME%Laser: %TYPE%Rocket: %TYPE%Special ammo: %TYPE%BuyYou can't lay mines on a home base map!You can't lay mines in a Galaxy Gate!You can't use Smartbombs on a home base map!You can't drop Smartbombs in a Galaxy Gate!Cloak not possible in the %MAP% map!You cannot cloak while you own the Beacon!Jump not possible - you're already on the target map.Jump from the current map not possible with your CPU!You do not own enough Drones for this formation.You do not have enough %LOOT_ID%. %COUNT% more %LOOT_ID% needed.Amount: %COUNT%Piece: %AMOUNT%Jump to map %MAPDouble click to buyDouble click to firePrice: %PRICE% CreditsPrice: %PRICE% UridiumNot definedCooldown Remaining: %TIME%Targeting Guidance CPU: %TYPE%Auto Rocket CPU: %TYPE%Cloaking CPU: %TYPE%Jump CPU: %TYPE%Trade drone: %TYPE%Repair bot: %TYPE%Rocket-launcher CPU: %TYPE%Target-assist CPUDrone repairsCloaking CPUJump CPURepair botDrone repair type: %TYPE%Remaining drone repairs: %COUNT%Not enough resourcesYou need %RESOURCE_COUNT% %RESOURCE%You do not have enough %CURRENCY%%COUNT% %CURRENCY_SINGULAR% drones can’t be repaired - you need %AMOUNT% more %CURRENCY%Visit the Tech FactoryRocket CPU (automatic purchase: not defined)Ammo CPU (automatic purchase: not defined)Configure in HangarCreditYou don't own this itemAdvanced Jump CPUAdvanced Jump CPU: %TYPE%MinesTech itemsRocket launchersShip abilitiesSpecial itemsLasersDrone formationsBuy nowShow items not ownedOpen config modeConfiguration ModeReset &amp; ExitSave &amp; ExitorConnection informationConnection lostBeta informationLogoutMissionsSpecial offerLogMini mapSettingsShopHelpTrade raw materialsYou can only trade raw materials on your home base.HeroShipStar systemFireworksCommand line interfaceRepairEquipmentTargeting Guidance CPU: %TYPE%Auto Rocket CPU: %TYPE%Cloaking CPU: %TYPE%Jump CPU: %TYPE%Trade drone: %TYPE%Repair bot: %TYPE%Outside our star system. Unable to locate position ...Amount: %COUNT%Amount: %COUNT%Amount: %COUNT%Amount: %COUNT%Amount: %COUNT%Price: %COUNT%Pieces: %COUNT%Remaining jumps: %COUNT%Remaining salvos: %COUNT%Remaining cloakings: %COUNT%Initiates a direct jump to your home baseRocket launcher: %TYPE%Loaded rockets: %COUNT% (%TYPE%)Attention: No launcher installedClan Battle StationOwnerCompanySinceAsteroidFree sinceAllShow ship values in numbersUserBoostersSpaceballInvasionCapture the BeaconYou changed the screen resolution. Please wait %SECONDS% seconds and then log out. Log back into the game for the changes to take effect on the space map.Welcome to INTEX SystemsTDM(s) underwayChances of participation / Waiting list positionResolutionTeam DeathmatchGroup systemGroupInviteContacts%COMPANY% has just scored a goal!Logging out in %SEC% seconds,.%DIST% pp%NICKNAME% (%COMPANY_1%) captured the %COMPANY_2% beacon.%NICKNAME% retrieved %COMPANY% beacon from your base!Your fellow space pilot %NICKNAME% captured the %COMPANY% beacon!Your company captured the %COMPANY_2% beacon!Your base is missing the %COMPANY% beacon!%NICKNAME% (%COMPANY_1%) lost the %COMPANY_2% beacon.%NICKNAME% (%COMPANY_1%) brought the %COMPANY_2% beacon into the target zone.%COMPANY% gets one point.Capture the BeaconCTBThe %COMPANY_1% beacon was relocated to %COMPANY_2%.Your beacon was relocated to %COMPANY%.%SECONDS% seconds remaining until the end of the CTB match%SECONDS% seconds remaining until the start of the CTB match%MINUTES% minutes remaining until the end of the CTB match%MINUTES% minutes until the start of the CTB matchYou can't capture this beacon.You can't jump to this map with the beacon.%TYPE% fireworks put into position by you.You have put fireworks into position.Igniting fireworks%NICKNAME% ignited his/her fireworks.%SECS% seconds remaining to detonationFireworks are now available to buy in the hangar.Fireworks are now ready for ignition.%name% rolled a %number%.This group already has the maximum number of members!This player is already in a group.This player isn't online.No player exists with this name.This player is no longer online.Invite was already deleted.Only group leaders can send invites.You've reached the maximum number of invites.This player already has the maximum number of invites.This player has blocked all invites.Spam! Please respect the invitation limit.You already invited this player.%name% declined your invite.%name% canceled their invite.The group leader declined %candidate%'s invite.%inviter% invited %candidate%.Your invite to %invited% expired in the hands of the group leader.Your invite to %invited% expired in their hands.%inviter%'s invite to %candidate% has expired.%inviter%'s invite has expired.You and this player are not at the same Hades Gate stage.Build the Hades Gate to help this player defeat the Emperors.You and this player are at the same Hades Gate stage.New invite receivedInvite deletedMaximizeMinimizeHide invitesShow invitesPending group leader's acceptanceAcceptCancelDeclineConfirmNominate as group leaderChange invite settingsGroup leaders onlyOpen to allUpon requestKick out memberLeave group%name% left the group.%name% left the group.%name% was kicked out by the group leader.%name% is offline%name% is online%name% was shot down.%name% was killed in action.%name% was destroyed in the radiation zone.Share of lootDisband groupGroup was disbanded.%name% joined the group.Change loot settingsRandom distributionNeed before greedWhat you take is what you getPingToo many pings%name%'s targetHit pointsNanohullShieldMap%name% jumped to the %map% map.fightingnot fightingcloakeduncloakedfly to %name%location unknown: wrong mapFollowPingKick outPromoteBlock invitesAllow invitesBlock invitesAllow invitesInviteInvite from %name%Invite for %name%You've received an invite from %name%.You've sent an invite to %name%.Group members can't be attacked.Drone repair CPU: %TYPE%SepromLasersRocketsGeneratorsShields%COUNT% rounds%COUNT% units%COUNT% min.Drag 'n drop to easily upgrade your items: Just drag the resource over the desired item!Raw materials/Resources:%VALUE% Sec.%VALUE% Min.%VALUE% Hrs.%VALUE% DaysUpgrading with this resource will result in the loss of any other recently completed upgrades.15% increase in firepowerPerformance +10%Firepower +30% / Performance +20%Firepower +60% / Shield generator performance +40%WarningUpgradeCancelYesNoQuantityRefiningUpgradeLabSkylabAuto-refine raw materialsOnly works with a premium pack.Shield upgradedLaser ammo upgradedRockets upgradedGenerator upgradedPrometium is the red raw material which can be collected in outer space.Endurium is the blue raw material which can be collected in outer space.Terbium is the gold raw material which can be collected in outer space.You need Xenomit to produce Promerium.Click on the Xenomit image to purchase it in the trading post.%COUNT_1% %ORE_1% and %COUNT_2% %ORE_2% = 1 unit%COUNT% %ORE% required per unitUpgradeUpgradeRefiningRefineHow much do you want to produce?%ORE% creation failedYou don't have enough %ORE%.Ammo CPU (automatically purchases: %TYPE% laser)Rocket CPU (automatically buys: %TYPE%)Start and stop attacks using the shortcut barJump to the %map% mapNot equippedTransactions remaining: %COUNT%Transactions remaining: UnlimitedAutomatic CPU Fuel Assistant FB-X (automatically purchases P.E.T. fuel)The Automatic CPU Fuel Assistant has purchased 10,000 units of P.E.T. fuel.No active missionsClick here for more jobs!Fly to Mission Control to see if there are any missions for you.The shortcut bar has 10 opens slots. You can drag &amp; drop items into these slots to use them as shortcut buttons. The buttons are all numbered. Just press on that number on your keyboard to use the slot item.The inventory bar has up to three levels. The 5 hexagons in the top level are permanent. They represent lasers, rockets, special ammo, CPUs and the “Buy now” function. If you click on one of these five hexagons, a second level and possibly a third level will open. The bars in the second-level icons change color depending on how much of each item you have in stock. Blue represents a healthy supply, red means less and gray means none. The third-level icons can be used to start an attack with the relevant weapon type, and can also be used to stop laser attacks only.The log window is your logbook history. It shows all DO activities such as recent announcements, kills, countdowns, etc. You can resize it using the triangle symbol on the bottom right.The mini map is your panoramic view of the entire space map. The cross-axis shows your current coordinates and the danger bar on the left-hand side changes color and size to indicate your level of danger.The star system helps you find your way in the endless expanse of space. It shows how the different maps are connected and how you can travel between them.The ship window displays all important ship information such as HP, nanohull strength, cargo bay capacity, rockets, ammo and current configs. Click on the information to switch between graphical and digital displays.The user window shows all important account information such as EP, level, honor, Credits, Uridium and Jackpot balance.The group window displays current information about your group's members and pending group invites. Invitations can be accepted, declined, or sent. Once an invitation has been sent and accepted, a group is formed.The PET window provides you with an overview of your PET. The bar displays important information - its hit points, amount of fuel, shield stats and experience. Activate the PET by using the Play button. You can refill it next to it and on the right you may select and activate the gear.Greetings space pilot!  Your spaceship is located in the center of the space map. Click on the map to move your ship around space and fly by holding down your mouse button.Left-click your mouse to select targets and click on the ammo symbol in the shortcut bar to fire weapons.  Collect experience points by shooting down aliens and enemy ships, but don't attack any of your company's ships!Collect raw materials in space and exchange them for Credits at your space station.Do you really want to reset your settings? Warning: If you accept, your browser window will close and you'll have to re-launch the game.ResetCancelWeapons system compromisedWeapons system back onlineTargeting device compromised by enemy EMP burst!Targeting device compromised by enemy EMP burst!Enemy targeting device disabledTargeting device back onlineYour ship was compromised by the Draw Fire effect.Draw Fire effect terminatedYour ship was compromised by the JAMX effect.JAMX effect terminatedYou received a 50% EP booster!%DAYS% day(s) remaining for your 50% EP booster.%HOURS% hour(s) remaining for your 50% EP booster.Your 50% EP booster has expired.You've received a 50% Honor Booster!Your 50% Honor Booster is still good for %DAYS% day(s).Your 50% Honor Booster is still good for %HOURS% hour(s).Your 50% Honor Booster is expired.Not availableAmount: %COUNT%GameplayDisplaySoundIncoming messageNextShow allSpaceshipWe're under attack in an outlying sector! Come to our rescue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blue&gt;Follow the flashing arrow:&lt;/blue&gt; &lt;blue&gt;Left-click&lt;/blue&gt; the location to which your ship should fly.&lt;br&gt;Over and out!Quick, destroy the three rival ships! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blue&gt;Left-click them to target in on the ships.&lt;/blue&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Launch your attack with the &lt;blue&gt;[1]&lt;/blue&gt; key or the &lt;blue&gt;laser button in the shortcut bar&lt;/blue&gt;.Kill opponents quicker with &lt;blue&gt;rockets&lt;/blue&gt;. Fire off rockets with the &lt;blue&gt;[2]&lt;/blue&gt; key or the &lt;blue&gt;rocket button in the shortcut bar&lt;/blue&gt;.Nice work, space pilot! Remember to repair your ship after being hit by enemy fire.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To repair it, just press &lt;blue&gt;[3]&lt;/blue&gt; or click the &lt;blue&gt;repair bot button in the shortcut bar.&lt;/blue&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Note: Robots will stop repairing your ship as soon the ship moves.Do you see those &lt;blue&gt;glowing orange boxes?&lt;/blue&gt; They contain valuable resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blue&gt;Click on them to collect them.&lt;/blue&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find out what's inside them at the top of the screen or in your logbook.Well done, pilot! Destroy enemies in space to get &lt;blue&gt;money and resources.&lt;/blue&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This will increase your &lt;blue&gt;experience and honor points,&lt;/blue&gt; allowing you to enter new galaxies and maps.Escort your ally's damaged ship to the &lt;blue&gt;space station&lt;/blue&gt; so that it can be repaired.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blue&gt;Contact the ship by flying close to it.&lt;/blue&gt;Thanks for your help! Unfortunately, I lost my cargo. You'll find &lt;blue&gt;3 Prometium, 2 Endurium&lt;/blue&gt; and &lt;blue&gt;1 Terbium&lt;/blue&gt; not far from here.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could you get them for me? Just &lt;blue&gt;click on the items and wait until they've been beamed aboard.&lt;/blue&gt;All right, backup is finally here. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blue&gt;Follow us to the jump portal&lt;/blue&gt; so we can fly back to the station and have my ship repaired.This is the &lt;blue&gt;jump portal&lt;/blue&gt; that takes you to other maps. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Press &lt;blue&gt;[J]&lt;/blue&gt; or &lt;blue&gt;click on the circle symbol&lt;/blue&gt; to fly through the gate.Safe at last! You can keep the resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blue&gt;Sell them at the station&lt;/blue&gt; by clicking on the &lt;blue&gt;Trade button on the top right.&lt;/blue&gt;Take a look around the &lt;blue&gt;hangar&lt;/blue&gt;. You can buy &lt;blue&gt;new ships&lt;/blue&gt; and &lt;blue&gt;weapons&lt;/blue&gt; there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You're on your own from now on, but you're a capable space pilot, and I'm sure you won't have any problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks again, and good luck! Over and out.Thanks for the help, Pilot!&lt;br&gt;You're new, aren't you?&lt;br&gt;You should probably introduce yourself to &lt;blue&gt;Mission Control&lt;/blue&gt;, then. They'll give you a few &lt;blue&gt;beginner missions&lt;/blue&gt; and you could win &lt;blue&gt;amazing equipment and weapons&lt;/blue&gt;.&lt;br&gt;They'll be waiting for you at the home base. Over and out.Space Pilot!&lt;br&gt;Glad to see a friendly face - listen I got trapped here and could need &lt;blue&gt;your help!&lt;/blue&gt;Yeah, before you ask, I really don't know how I ended up in here.&lt;br&gt;Just jumped through that gate that came out of nowhere and here I am ...... my cargo room is half empty, ship's severely damaged and most of&lt;br&gt;... wait, what is that?!&lt;br&gt; &lt;blue&gt;Watch out!!&lt;/blue&gt;Well this is more annoying than dangerous but &lt;blue&gt;I think I can help you &lt;/blue&gt; - just need a little time setting things up ...Well there you are again - thought these Streuners would have driven you off.Remember that I lost most of my cargo? Actually I still have limited &lt;blue&gt;control over some boosters&lt;/blue&gt; I just bought recently.Let's see if we can put them to some use. Don't expect and be sure to &lt;blue&gt;stay close to the booster&lt;/blue&gt; - and check the &lt;blue&gt;booster interface&lt;/blue&gt; in your ship's computer - prepare for another wave of enemies!OK &lt;blue&gt;activating booster 1.&lt;/blue&gt; Now - this should give you some &lt;blue&gt;extra damage&lt;/blue&gt; for a brief amount of time. I will send the booster's &lt;blue&gt;coordinates to your navigation system.&lt;/blue&gt;Worked like a charm, didn't it? I will reroute energy to the &lt;blue&gt;second booster&lt;/blue&gt; now, this will increase your &lt;blue&gt;shield regeneration rate.&lt;/blue&gt; Stay sharp!Hey bud, welcome back! I figured out how to implement a series circuit that activates boosters more rapidly. &lt;blue&gt;Health-regeneration and hitpoints&lt;/blue&gt; will be boosted.Good you made it back. I've been tinkering around a bit in your absence - you might need to move to get all the advantages, though. Good Luck.You are quite a pilot! I developed some activation patterns, which should help you a lot.Damn, these things are starting to scare me. Being trapped in here feels like living in a goldfish bowl! Oh, and here they come again!This will be a hard wave ... be sure to use the &lt;blue&gt;boosters,&lt;/blue&gt; mate.Hey, welcome back! Just wondering if you believe in all these "end of the world" rumors that have been spreading recently? Oh, here we go again!Hi, buddy! Say, don't I know you from somewhere? You seem kind of familiar ... INCOMING!Ok ... once again, I've improved the booster activation patterns. Check it out and give me some feedback ... I just might be on to something here!What the &lt;blue&gt;frack&lt;/blue&gt; is this thing? I'll try to power up the &lt;blue&gt;boosters&lt;/blue&gt; as long as I can - make the best out of it. Good Luck!My friend, it has been an &lt;blue&gt;honor&lt;/blue&gt; fighting with you. I will reroute &lt;blue&gt;all remaining energy&lt;/blue&gt; to keep the &lt;blue&gt;boosters&lt;/blue&gt; going. Should &lt;blue&gt;life support fail&lt;/blue&gt; before you've brought this wave down, please try to &lt;blue&gt;get me out of here.&lt;/blue&gt; Farewell.Some temprorary text for new tutorial step&lt;blue&gt;Left-click&lt;/blue&gt; the target coordinates.Wrong direction!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;blue&gt;Follow the arrow!&lt;/blue&gt;C'mon, move it. We've got to get to the station quickly so I can repair my ship.Welcome to reality, space pilot! Up until now, we've taken it easy on you. But now it's time. In orbit, there are tramps and scoundrels everywhere. They have you in their sights. They know no mercy!Therefore, for the next two weeks we are admitting you to the company-wide pilot protection program and will provide you access to all premium advantages free of charge... enjoy the privileges!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Free repairs, time advantages and automatic helpers: use the advantages, because two weeks are quickly overRepairLeaveUse this setting carefully. When the game is loaded, you will be automatically logged into the client, and other pilots will be able to attack you immediately.HangarYou have been destroyed!Destroyer: &lt;b&gt;%VALUE%&lt;/b&gt;Destroyer: &lt;b&gt;%VALUE%&lt;/b&gt;Destroyer: &lt;b&gt;radiation zone&lt;/b&gt;Destroyer: &lt;b&gt;mine&lt;/b&gt;Destroyer: &lt;b&gt;unknown&lt;/b&gt;Repair your ship to continue playing!No chargeRepair your ship at the nearest home base.Replace your ship with a free Phoenix.Repair your ship at the next jumpgate in the DMZ. Careful, there are no NAZs on battle maps.Repair your ship on the spot with 10% of your base hitpoints. After the repairs are complete, your ship will be protected by an Insta-shield for 10 seconds. Warning: The attack protection expires as soon as you attack someone else.Free repair at your company's spawn point.Free repairs on the active Hades Gate server.Free repairs on the active TDM server.Cooldown: %cooldown% seconds.Caution! After logging out, the repair options "next jumpgate" and "on the spot" are no longer available.Caution! After logging out or changing ships, the "next jumpgate" and "on the spot" repair options are no longer available.Caution! If you log out or let the countdown reach zero, you will be removed from the match.If you log out or run out of time, you will be removed from this Hades Gate server.Careful! If time is up or you log out, you'll be removed from the TDM server.Caution! After logging out, the repair option 'on the spot' is no longer available.You can repair your ship at your factions arrival area.Free repairUse repair creditRepair (%COUNT% U.)Repair (%COUNT% %CURRENCY%)Free PhoenixBuy uridium now.Choose an option.A stroke of luck: this repair is free! Your ship was destroyed during a time in which repairs are free.Your ship was destroyed on a Galaxy Gate map, which offers free repairs.Your ship was destroyed on a Galaxy Gate map that offers free repairs. You still have %COUNT% lives left.A stroke of luck: this repair is free! Your ship was destroyed while the CTB beacon was on board.Your ship was destroyed on a Jackpot Battle map, which offers free repairs.As a Premium member, you can always repair your ship for free.This ship design can always be repaired for free.This repair is free because you lost one of your lives from Scoremageddon.Your ship was destroyed at a free-repair event.Your ship was destroyed on a map which offers free repairs.This repair is free.This repair is free.This repair is free because your ship was destroyed on a battle map during the Spaceball Event.Careful! Repairing for free at your company's spawn point is only available for the next few seconds.You still have %COUNT% lives left for the Hades Gate.You still have %COUNT% life for the TDM match.You can repair your ship at your factions arrival area.You can pay an additional %COUNT% U. to make on-the-spot repairs.You can pay an additional %COUNT% U. to make repairs at the next jumpgate.You can pay an additional %COUNT% U. to make on-the-spot repairs.You can pay an extra %COUNT% %CURRENCY% to be able to repair at the next jumpgate.You can pay an extra %COUNT% %CURRENCY% to repair on the spot.This repair will cost you %COUNT% Uridium.This repair will cost you %COUNT% %CURRENCY%.You do not have enough Uridium to repair your ship.  Go to Payment to buy more Uridium or continue playing with the "Free Phoenix."You don't have enough Credits to repair your ship, but you can keep playing with the "Free Phoenix."Use you last repair credit.Use one of your %COUNT% repair credits.This option is only available for the next %COUNTDOWN% seconds.%COUNTDOWN% second(s)Free repair in the Hades Gate available for the next %COUNTDOWN% seconds.You have %COUNTDOWN% seconds to take advantage of free repairs in the TDM match.Jump portals serve as gates to other galaxies. To use one, fly up to it and press [J].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; CAUTION: The deeper into DarkOrbit you fly, the stronger your enemies will be.Your cargo bay is full: Fly back to the station to sell your cargo. Once you get to the station, click on "Trade raw materials" in the top-right corner of your game window to open the trade menu.There are two hot keys to make using your P.E.T. easier and more effective.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activate and deactivate your P.E.T. with the &lt;blue&gt;[E] key&lt;/blue&gt; and&lt;br&gt; switch to guard mode with the &lt;blue&gt; [R] key&lt;/blue&gt;.Did you know?CloseStart-up MissionsStart-up MissionsReward:Did you like this item? Click here to buy a second one for a special price!Did you like this item? Then click here to buy a second one for a special price!Buy nowBuy nowBuy now for %PRICE|SYMBOL%Buy now for %PRICE|SYMBOL%Explorer MissionExplore your base and win a new ship!Liberator StarfighterClick in the orbit to navigate to a certain point and explore your home base.Streuner MissionDestroy a Streuner.LF-2 laser cannonUse your laser (1 key) and your rockets (2 key) to destroy a Streuner.Box Collection MissionCollect 5 bonus boxes.Repair-bot Auto CPUCollect 5 of the glowing orange boxes by clicking on them. You can find them on all maps.Level Up MissionReach level 2 by shooting down enough aliens to collect 10,000 experience points.SG3N-B01 shield generatorDestroy more aliens using your laser (1 key) and your rockets (2 key) or complete a few quests to collect enough experience points to reach level 2.Ore Collection MissionCollect ten Prometium.1,000 UridiumCollect ten pieces of red ore that can be found on all maps.Merchant MissionSell your collected ore.2,500 rounds of MCB-50 laser ammoFly to the space station shown on the mini map and click on the button with the arrows in the top-right corner of your screen to sell your cargo in the trade window.Jump Gate MissionJump to the second map in your system.G3N-7900 speed generatorFly to the jump portal that looks like a white ring on the mini map by pressing the [J] key or clicking on the yellow button with the circular symbol in the top-right corner of your game window.Lordakia MissionDestroy a Lordakia.100 PromeriumDestroy a Lordakia on your system's second map. But be careful! You only have newbie protection on the first map.Generator Update MissionUpgrade your speed or shield generator with Promerium.LF-3 laser cannonFirst, conclude the Lordakia mission, then click on the button in the top-right corner that looks like a rocket with a plus sign. Click on the upgrade tab at the top of the pop-up and drag the Prometium (light orange ore) to one of your generators.Quick Buy MissionUse the "Buy now" function to get more rockets or laser ammo.500 PLT-2021 rocketsClick on the yellow C-shaped pipe icon at the bottom of your screen in the shortcut bar to open the "Buy now" menu. Select the laser ammo or rockets of your choice. When the pipe icon underneath your selection looks like a C, you can pay for the item you chose in Credits. When the pipe icon looks like a U, you must pay in Uridium. Tip: You may have to use up some ammo or rockets before you can buy more.Starter MissionAccept and complete a mission from the DarkOrbit website.5 repair creditsClick on the button with the star symbol to open the Mission window. Open the "Jobs" page, accept a mission, and complete it.Group MissionInvite another player to join your group, or get another player to invite you into theirs.Flax droneClick on the button with the three small figures to invite another player to join your group. Click on a player to select them and then on the letter symbol in the group pop-up to invite them. The other player must accept your invitation. Tip: If none of the players you invite accept, use the chat to search for a player who'll help you.Explorer MissionExplore your base and win a new ship!Liberator StarfighterNavigate around the orbit by clicking your mouse. Your ship will follow so you can explore your home base!Streuner MissionDestroy a Streuner alien!LF-2 laser cannonUse your laser (1 key) and your rockets (2 key) to destroy a Streuner.Box Collection MissionCollect 5 bonus boxes.Repair-bot auto CPUCollect 5 of the glowing orange boxes by clicking on them. You can find them on all maps.Level Up MissionReach level 2 by shooting down enough aliens to collect 10,000 experience points.SG3N-B01 shield generatorDestroy more aliens using your laser (1 key) and your rockets (2 key) or complete a few quests to collect enough experience points to reach level 2.Ore Collection MissionCollect ten Prometium.1,000 UridiumCollect 10 pieces of the red ore that can be found on the map.Merchant MissionSell your collected ore.2,500 rounds of MCB-50 laser ammoFly to the space station clearly shown on the mini map and click on the button with the two arrows in the top-right corner of your screen to sell your cargo in the trade window.Jump Gate MissionJump to the second star chart in your system.G3N-7900 speed generatorFly to the jump portal that looks like a white ring on the mini map and then press on the [J] key or click on the yellow button with the circular symbol in the top-right corner of your game window.Lordakia MissionDestroy a Lordakia alien!100 PromeriumDestroy a Lordakia on your star system's second map. But be careful! You only have newbie protection on the first map.Generator Update MissionUpgrade your speed or shield generator with Promerium!LF-3 laser cannonFirst conclude the Lordakia quest, then click on the button in the top-right corner that looks like a rocket with a plus sign. Click on the upgrade tab at the top of the pop-up and drag the Promerium (orange-yellow ore) to one of your generators.Quick Buy MissionUse the "Buy now" function to get more rockets or laser ammo.500 PLT-2021 rocketsClick on the yellow C-shaped icon at the bottom of your screen in the shortcut bar to open the "Buy now" menu. Select the laser ammo or rockets of your choice. When the icon underneath your selection looks like a C, the item can be purchased for the price shown in Credits. When it looks like a U, the price is shown in Uridium. Tip: You may have to use up some ammo or rockets before you can buy more.Starter MissionAccept and complete a mission from the DarkOrbit website.5 repair creditsClick on the button with the star symbol to open the Mission window (if that window isn't already open). Open the "Jobs" page, accept a mission, and complete it.Group MissionInvite another player to join your group, or get another player to invite you into theirs.Flax droneClick on the button with the three small figures to invite another player to join your group. Click on a player to select them and then on the letter symbol in the group pop-up to invite them. The other player must accept your invitation. Tip: If none of the players you invite accept, use the chat to search for a player who'll help you.Rocket-launcher CPU: %TYPE%GET YOUR OWN: ONLY %PRICE|SYMBOL%!GET YOUR OWN: ONLY %PRICE|SYMBOL%!GET YOUR OWN: ONLY %PRICE|SYMBOL%!TRY IT OUT: ONLY %PRICE|SYMBOL%!%PRICE|WORD_CAPS%!%PRICE|WORD_CAPS%! NOW!%PRICE|WORD_CAPS%! NOW!Exclusive item: Only available while supplies last!Use it 100 times!Test it out for 3 days - No obligation!LET US KNOW WHAT YOU THINK! TAKE THE BETA SURVEY NOW!Take surveyUSDEURGBPPLNKRWJPYMXNRUB$€£Zł₩¥$руб.¢cpgr¢коп.US dollarseurospoundsZłotyWonYenESP/dollarRUB-RubelcentscentspenceGroszyPesoKopekeUS DOLLARSEUROSPOUNDSZŁOTYWONYENESP/dollarRUB-RUBELCENTSCENTSPENCEGROSZYPESOKOPEKE%SYMBOL%%FULL%.%SUB%%SYMBOL%%FULL%%SYMBOL%%FULL%%SUB%%SYMBOL%%FULL%.%SUB% %CODE%%FULL% %CODE%%FULL% %CODE%%FULL%.%SUB% %WORD%%FULL% %WORD%%FULL% %WORD%%SUB% %WORD%%nick% lost attack protectionAttack protection lost%nick% regained attack protectionAttack protection regainedRelay station activatedHeadquarters to Delta squad:&lt;br&gt;Your mission is to infiltrate the pirate galaxy, collect intel and destroy the enemy by taking out the pirate leader, known as Century Falcon. Do you copy?I'll keep you up to date on enemy positions.&lt;br&gt;Remember to watch your six - you're in enemy space now.&lt;br&gt;Good luck ... you're gonna need it.&lt;br&gt;Over and out!Nice work! According to our intel, the facility provided power to pirate headquarters before it was shut down.Use your laser cannons on the relay station - maybe the laser energy will bring the facility back online.Great job! The relay station's operational again.&lt;br&gt;The scout drones are reporting an extra energy signature.&lt;br&gt;The relay station must have been linked to their HQ. Reactivating it triggered the HQ repair zone.&lt;br&gt;Fly into the zone and repair your ships.Their HQ's running on auxiliary power. They must have interrupted the power supply to turn off life support and keep us out.Activate the other relay stations to increase the power supply.&lt;br&gt;Prepare yourselves: once that HQ is operational, Century Falcon will know we've penetrated his defenses and attack us.&lt;br&gt;Get ready for the battle of a lifetime!Our intel was accurate - the pirates were defending the relay stations to prevent us from activating their HQ.&lt;br&gt;Find and activate all their relay stations!Top notch! The extra power reactivated the HQ and Century Falcon's come out of hiding to defend it.&lt;br&gt;This is it, destroy Century Falcon and the operation will be complete.Operation Charlie Foxtrot successful!&lt;br&gt;That was some fine flying! You've earned yourselves some downtime.&lt;br&gt;Over and out!You must be part of a group to jump to this map.No instance availableNo instance found - Creating instance for group leader ...Instance found - Beaming players to the instance ...Map fullGroup leader must create an instance before you can jump to the map.Not enough players on the map - All players will be returned and the instance canceled.Maximum number of instances reached - Please try again soon.Pirate HQ activatedRelay station activatedRelay station deactivatedIncoming piratesCentury Falcon sightedCentury Falcon called reinforcementsMission completedMission failed - Get some better gear and try again!Your ship was destroyed - Get some better gear and try again!Your ship was destroyed - If three or more group members are still on the map, you can jump back to it.%ASSET_NAME% under attackAttack on %ASSET_NAME% interruptedYou can't attack %ASSET_NAME%!%POI_NAME% activated%POI_NAME% deactivatedTech itemsNo tech item in production/producedProduction facility availableFacility under constructionProduction facility availableProducing techEnergy leechRemaining time: %TIME%Amount: %COUNT%Chain impulseAmount: %COUNT%Precision targeterAmount: %COUNT%Remaining time: %TIME%Backup shieldsAmount: %COUNT%Battle repair botAmount: %COUNT%Remaining time: %TIME%A commando squad has just been spotted on map %MAP%. Blow it's cover and destroy it!Commando squads have just been spotted on maps %MAPS%. Blow their cover and destroy them!You effectively blew the commando squad's cover and destroyed it!You failed to destroy the commando squad and thus let them escape.Infiltration GameTime remaining: %TIME%Infiltrators killed: %COUNT%Provides current info on the infiltration defenses.A(n) %NPC_NAME% has spawned on the %MAP%. Quick, destroy it!A(n) %NPC_NAME% just spawned in your vicinity. Quick, destroy it!An ice meteoroid has appeared in your vicinity. Quick, destroy it!A super ice meteoroid has appeared in your vicinity. Quick, destroy it!A binary bot 1100101 just appeared in your vicinity. Destroy it quickly!Warning: Because of your level, you'll only get %AMOUNT%% of box contents on this map!You can't collect any box content on this map because your level is too high!Warning: Because of your level, you'll only get %AMOUNT%% of the loot on this map!Your level is too high, so you'll get no loot on this map.The mission reward booster increases your rewards by %AMOUNT%%.The bonus box booster increases bonus box content by %AMOUNT%%.Remaining Jackpot Battle contestants: %COUNT%Thank you for participating in the Jackpot Arena. Better luck next time!Special capabilitySolace nano-cluster instant repairDiminisher Weaken ShieldSentinel fortressSpectrum prismatic shieldingSingularityLightning afterburnerSolace nano-cluster instant repairDiminisher Weaken ShieldSentinel fortressSpectrum prismatic shieldingSingularityLightning afterburnerHP repair gradually restores your ship's HP as well as the HP of selected ships.Shield repair gradually restores your ship's shields as well as the shields of selected ships.Reparatur Pod Creates an energy field and repairs your ship as well as fellow group ships.Draw Fire temporarily redirects the trajectory of nearby enemy fire towards your ship.Travel Mode briefly increases your ship's speed, so you can quickly travel long distances.Fortify bolsters your ship with protective armor and increases its resistance to damage; however, it will immobilize your ship.Protection Deploys a protective shield around your ship and redirects a portion of the damage inflicted on all nearby group members to your ship.Ultimate Cloaking This ability cloaks your ship, immediately removes you from the mini map and stops others from making you the target.JAMX emits an interference field which paralyzes enemy ships' functions. All effects which they are currently using will be compromised.Target Marking It marks all targets for your group (even on the mini map) and increases the damage caused by all group members.Recon This skill doubles your recon range on the mini map.Nano-cluster instant repair completedGroup nano-cluster instant repair completedMember nano-cluster instant repair completedYour enemy is using "weaken shield": your defenses are compromised.Weaken shield has been activated: enemy defenses compromised.Shields recoveredEnemy shields recoveredPrismatic shielding activated: Laser systems compromised.Prismatic shielding deactivated: Laser systems back to full power.Fortress activatedFortress deactivatedSingularity activatedSingularity deactivatedYour DarkOrbit client is outdated. Please update your current version %LOCAL% to the latest version %CURRENT% by emptying your cache and restarting the client!Jump CPUJump CPU configurationLower mapsUpper mapsShow upper mapsShow lower mapsPlease select a target destination to jump to by clicking on the corresponding map.Current mapSelected jump destinationJump credits: %COUNT%Jump credits: %COUNT%Repair vouchers: %COUNT%JumpStarts jump.  Ave. time till jump: %SECONDS% sec.PriceFreeCurrent map: %MAP%Selected jump destination: %MAP%Select %MAP% map as jump destinationJump not possible. Not enough Uridium.Jump not possible. Level too low.Jump not possibleCPU cooling down. Jump not possible.CPU jump started. %COUNT% sec. remaining till jump.%COUNT% sec. remaining till jump.1 sec. remaining till jump.Jump canceled. CPU can't be used during combat.Jump canceled. CPU can't be used during flight.Jump canceled. Unknown error.CPU jump completed. Map switched.The CPU jump cost you %COSTS%.CPU jump successfulP.E.T.Activate your P.E.T.Deactivate your P.E.T.Activate the selected gearSingularity buff: Causes continual damage to targets for 1 minute.Trade buff: lets your P.E.T trade with the space station.Shield weakening buff: Inflicts 50% more damage to your target for 1 minute.You don't have enough Uridium to repair your P.E.T..Repair your P.E.T. for %COUNT% Uridium.Repairs your P.E.T. for free.FuelKamikaze Detonator may not be selected until its cooldown has ended.Combo-Ship-Repair-Gear is cooling down and may not be selected.Sacrificial Flame is cooling down and may not be selected.Cooldown: %TIME%Buy P.E.T. fuelP.E.T. activatedP.E.T. deactivatedGuard mode activatedP.E.T. repairs the ship now.P.E.T. does not have sufficient fuel to activate the gear.Your P.E.T. reached level %LEVEL%.Your P.E.T. was destroyed.Your P.E.T. is involved in combat.Your P.E.T. ran out of fuel.Your P.E.T. is running low on fuel.Your P.E.T. is out of ammo.Your P.E.T. isn't equipped with lasers.Not enough fuelWarning! Your P.E.T. is under attack!Not enough cargo roomYour P.E.T. can't attack this target.Kamikaze Detonator cooldown time has elapsed. Detonator may now be selected.Sacrificial Flame cooldown time has elapsed. Sacrificial Flame may now be selected.Kamikaze Detonator may not be used in this map.Get fuelPassive modeGuard modeDestroyerAuto-looterAuto-resource collectorEnemy locatorResource locatorCargo traderP.E.T. repairerKamikaze DetonatorCombo Guard Mode GearCombo Ship Repair GearSacrificial FlameRanked huntPirate HuntRanked Mordon huntRanked Saimon huntRanked Lordakia huntWarbond: Pirate RaidBounty pointsClan bounty pointsYou received %AMOUNT% bounty points.You received one bounty point.You received one bounty point.You received %AMOUNT% bounty points.The bounty points will be updated every five minutes.You received the %TYPE% drone design.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% drone designs.This target is immune and can't be slowed down.Afterburner activated. New speed: Supersonic speed.Afterburner deactivated. New speed: Standard speed.Jump not possible - target map is full. Please try again!(CPU not equipped)Version %VERSION%Not enough of this laser ammo for an attack - change laser typeLaser ammo changed to %!.Changing laser ammoYou need to buy new rockets.No rockets of this type left - rockets were changed to %! type.No rockets of this type left - change rocket typeNo rockets left - buy new rockets.Collected word puzzle letter: %LETTER%Word puzzle is complete. You have received a capsule.A foreign impulse has taken your P.E.T. out of battle.The impulse is out of range. Your P.E.T. is ready for battle again!You received %! Jackpot Euros.You received one jackpot %CURRENCY%.You received %COUNT% jackpot %CURRENCY%s.You received %! Credits.You received one Credit.You received %COUNT% Credits.One Credit has been deducted.%COUNT% Credits have been deducted.You received %! Uridium.You received %! Viral Purge Points.You received one Uridium.You received %COUNT% Uridium.One Uridium has been deducted.%COUNT% Uridium have been deducted.You received extra energy for the galaxy-gate generator.You received extra energy for the galaxy-gate generator.You received extra energy for the galaxy-gate generator %COUNT% times.You received %! EP.You received one experience point.You received %COUNT% experience points.One experience point has been deducted.%COUNT% experience points have been deducted.You received %! HP.You have already completed this Gate. You can try again in %HOURS% hours and %MINUTES% minutes.You received one hit point.You received %COUNT% hit points.Your Nanohull Strength was increased by 1.Your Nanohull Strength was increased by %COUNT%.%! %2! Hellstorm rockets receivedYou received one %TYPE% rocket.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% rocket-launcher rockets.You received %! %2! laser ammo.You received one round of %TYPE% laser ammo.You received %COUNT% rounds of %TYPE% laser ammo.You received %! %2! fireworks.You received one %TYPE% firework.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% fireworks.You received %! %2! rockets.You received %! WIZ-X rockets.You received one %TYPE% rocket.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% rockets.You received one EMP-01 burst.You received %COUNT% EMP-01 bursts.You received a log-disk.You received %COUNT% log-disks.You received a jump credit for the advanced jump CPU.You received %COUNT% jump credits for the advanced jump CPU.You received one %TYPE% mine.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% mines.You received one P.E.T. fuel.You received %COUNT% P.E.T. fuel.%! HP were deducted.One hit point has been deducted.%COUNT% hit points have been deducted.You received %! honor points.You received one honor point.You received %COUNT% honor points.One honor point has been deducted.%COUNT% honor points have been deducted.You received a repair voucher.You received %COUNT% repair vouchers.You received a(n) %TYPE%.You received %COUNT% %TYPE%.An item was found in the ore collected.You received a %TYPE% P.E.T. gear.You received a %TYPE% speed generator.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% speed generators.You received a %TYPE% shield generator.You received a %TYPE% laser.You have received %COUNT% %TYPE% shield generators.You have received %COUNT% %TYPE% lasers.You received a %TYPE% cloaking CPU.You received a %TYPE% jump CPU.You received a(n) %TYPE% CPU.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% CPUs.You received a(n) %TYPE% automatic CPU.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% automatic CPUs.You received a %TYPE% drone repair CPU.You received a %TYPE% ship design.You received one %TYPE% skill design.You received one %TYPE% Goliath design.You received one %TYPE% Vengeance design.You received a %TYPE% ship.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% ship(s).You received %TYPE%.You received %COUNT% %TYPE%s.You received a %TYPE% drone.You received %COUNT% %TYPE% drones.You received a banking doubler.You've received an Upgrade Voucher.You've received %COUNT% Upgrade Vouchers.NPC huntYou received 1 NPC Hunt point.You received %AMOUNT% NPC Hunt points.NPC Hunt pointsClan NPC Hunt pointsThanks for your loyalty. We've put together some great packs for you. Get one now on the game's Uridium page!Visit the game's Uridium page and get a great deal today. This offer expires in %COUNT% days!Visit the game's Uridium page and get a great deal today. This offer expires in 1 day!Visit the game's Uridium page and get a great deal today. This offer expires in %COUNT% hours!Visit the game's Uridium page and get a great deal today. This offer expires in 1 hour!Visit the game's Uridium page and get a great deal today. This offer expires in %COUNT% minutes!Your starter premium ends in: %COUNT% day(s).Your starter premium ends in: %COUNT% day(s).. Renew your Premium membership on the Uridium page at a special price!Your starter premium is valid for: 1 day. Renew your Premium membership on the Uridium page at a special price!Display game performance messagesYour game performance is suboptimal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To improve your game performance, you can adjust the quality of the graphics to your computer in the &lt;blue&gt;display settings&lt;/blue&gt;.InterfaceResolution820x6001024x5761024x7201280x7201280x900Preloaded ships use more memory, but attacks will happen quicker in the game.HighGoodAverageLowNoneAdjustedGraphic quality:Advanced modeStandard modeThe advanced mode allows you to individually adapt the settings to your needs.The standard mode simplifies the setting options and uses predefined parameters.ShipsSelect between simplified and detailed ship designs.EnginesSelect between simplified and detailed engine animations.ExplosionsDetermine the extent to which damage and destruction animations are shown.Resources and boxesSelect between simplified and detailed resources and boxes.BackgroundDefine the quality of the background detailsHigh quality settings not supported - GPU acceleration not available.ZonesSelect between simplified and detailed zones.KeyboardOther keyPress new keyActionKey1st and 3rd bar SlotPremium quickslotLogoutP.E.T. Guard ModeP.E.T. Combo Guard ModeP.E.T. Ship RepairActivate/deactivate P.E.T.Laser attackRocket attackMin/max all windowsFPS display on/offChange configurationActivate jump gateZoom inZoom outFocus chatShow/Hide Item Category BarUndefinedBackspaceCtrlEscCaps LockDelEndEnterHomeInsertPage UpPage DownSpacebarShiftTabArrow upArrow downLeft arrowRight arrowNum LockScroll LockPauseWindowsOption`1234567890-=QWERTYUIOP[]ASDFGHJKL;'\\ZXCVBNM,./SHOPURIDIUMThis location offers free ore trading.P.E.T. trade ready: You have to use P.E.T. fuel to trade.Trade Drone activated: 1 transaction remainingTrade Drone activated: %COUNT% transactions remaining%VALUE% extra energy%VALUE_OUTPUT%:%VALUE_INPUT% extra energyIn exchange for %VALUE_INPUT% Palladium, you'll get %VALUE_OUTPUT% units of extra energy.%VALUE% extra energyExchange %VALUE_INPUT% Palladium for %VALUE_OUTPUT% units of energy.Fly to the pirate's headquarters to exchange Palladium for extra energy.Per unit you'll get %VALUE% Credits.EXCHANGEPalladiumPalladiumJump portal is out of order.Booty keys: %AMOUNT%Collection canceled.A booty key is required to collect.Collecting pirate bootyYou received a booty key.You have received %AMOUNT% booty keys.Green booty key(s): %AMOUNT%Blue booty key(s): %AMOUNT%Red booty key(s): %AMOUNT%Silver Booty Keys: %AMOUNT%Apocalypse Booty Keys: %AMOUNT%Green pirate booty collected.You can now collect golden pirate booty.Blue pirate booty collected.Red pirate booty collected.Silver pirate booty collected.Apocalypse booty collected.Streuner pirate booty collected.To collect the treasure, you need a green booty key.To collect the treasure, you need a blue booty key.To collect the treasure, you need a red booty key.To collect these, you need a silver Booty Key.To collect these, you need a Apocalypse Booty Key.To collect these, you need a Prometheus Fragment.You received a green booty key.You received a blue booty key.You received a red booty key.You have acquired a silver Booty Key.You have acquired an Apocalypse Booty Key.You received %AMOUNT% green booty key(s).You received %AMOUNT% blue booty key(s).You received %AMOUNT% red booty key(s).You have acquired %AMOUNT% silver Booty Keys.You have acquired %AMOUNT% Apocalypse Booty Keys.A green booty key will be purchased automatically to open this booty.You do not have a green booty key. Purchase them in the shop or activate the auto purchase feature in settings.You do not have sufficient Uridium to automatically purchase a green booty key.You have acquired a Prometheus Fragments.You have acquired %AMOUNT% Prometheus Fragments.To collect these, you need a Prometheus Fragment.Prometheus Fragments: %AMOUNT%Prometheus Fragment collected.Awesome! You've acquired an Obsidian Microchip. Essential for opening an Obsidian Booty Box.Wow pilot! You've managed to acquire %AMOUNT% Obsidian Microchips. How many Obsidian Booty Boxes can you open now?To learn the secrets of the Obsidian Booty Box you need to have gathered Obsidian Microchips.Obsidian Microchips: %AMOUNT%Obsidian Booty Box collected.Remaining timeCurrent waveCurrent pointsHigh-score challengeYou found a high-score gate activator. You can now jump through the high-score gate.You completed the high-score gate with %SCORE% points and will now be sent to your home map.You do not have an activator - let your P.E.T. collect P.E.T. boxes to find one.This box can only be collected by a P.E.T.ScoremageddonYou still have this many lives.In the combo-meter you can see the size of your combo and, apart from that, your point multiplier.In the combo-timer you can see how much time you still have before your combo is reduced.Your Scoremageddon points collected until now:Triple kill!Unstoppable!Godlike!Like a boss!Scoremageddon has been started.Scoremageddon: only 1 minute left.Scoremageddon: still %TIME% minutes.Scoremageddon has been ended.Scoremageddon target destroyed: you will receive %SCORE% points.The opponent's level is too low. He did not participate in the Scoremageddon and therefore there are no points.Your opponent was eliminated during Scoremageddon and therefore there are no points.The opponent belongs to your own company and therefore there are no points.The opponent belongs to your clan and so there are no points.You were destroyed and have been eliminated from Scoremageddon with %SCORE% points.You have ended the Scoremageddon with %SCORE% points.Warning pilots! The radiation zone is expanding. It's time for the final battle!You received an APIS drone.You found a component of the Apis drone blueprints. The immediate production price for this drone is now lower.You found %COUNT% components of the Apis drone blueprints. The immediate production price for this drone is now lower.APISYou received a Zeus drone.You have found a component of the Zeus blueprints. The immediate production price for this drone is now lower.You have found %COUNT% components of the Zeus blueprints. The immediate production price for this drone is now lower.ZEUSSecurity checkPlease enter the two words!Unfortunately you failed the security check!You passed the security check!SubmitThe captcha code was correctly entered. In return, here's a bonus box doubler for the next box you collect.The captcha code was incorrectly entered. Please try entering it again in order to continue collecting boxes.Please enter the captcha code in order to continue collecting boxes.AdvertisementAchievement "%ACH_NAME%" activated!Drone FormationsStandard Formation No bonuses or mali.Turtle Formation Increases shield power by 10%, but reduces laser and rocket damage by 7.5%.Arrow Formation Increases rocket damage by 20%, but reduces laser damage by 3%.Lance Formation Increases mine damage by 50%.Star Formation Increases rocket damage by 25%, but also increases rocket launcher reload time by 33%.Pincer Formation Increases laser damage by 3% against other players and provides an additional 5% honor point bonus. However, it reduces shield penetration by 10%.Double Arrow Formation Increases shield penetration by 10%, but reduces shield power by 20%.Diamond Formation Your shield regenerates 1% of your max shield power per second, up to a maximum of 5,000 per second. But hit points are reduced by 30%.Chevron Formation Increases rocket damage by 50%, but ship hit points will be reduced by 20%.Moth Formation Increases shield penetration by 20%. Increases hit points by 20%, as well. But weakens your shield strength at a rate of 1% per second.Crab Formation Increases your shield absorption by 20%, but reduces your speed by 20%, as well.Heart Formation Increases you shield power by 10% and your hit points by 20%. Reduces, however, laser damage by 5%.Barrage Formation It causes 5% more laser damage to NPCs and also gives you 5% more EP. Shield Leech will, however, be reduced by 15%.Barrage Formation It causes 5% more laser damage to NPCs and also gives you 5% more EP. Shield Leech will, however, be reduced by 15%.Bat Formation Increases the damage you cause to NPCs by 8% and earns you 8% more XP, as well. Decreases your speed by 15%.Ring-Formation -50% Laserschaden +180% SchildwertBohrer-Formation -50% Schildwert und Schild-Absorbation +50% LaserschadenVeteran Formation -20% Laserschaden, Schildwert und Hitpoints +50% EhreKuppel Formation -25% Geschwindigkeit +10% Schildwert und dein Schild bekommt 100% SchadensabsorptionDoppel Rad Formation -15% Laserschaden +10% GeschwindigkeitX Formation -30% Hitpoints +100% Raketenschaden (für standard Raketen und Raketenwerfer Raketen)Wellen Formation Protze mit der Wellen Formation, diese Dronen wissen wie sie sich bewegen!)You need at least %COUNT% drones to use this formation!You have successfully switched ships.Warp not allowed on this map.Attention! Warp aborted.Connection activated. Beginning warp.Connection activated. Beginning activate.No warping while engaged in combat!Ship warpWarp controlsThis warp costs one jump credit.This warp will cost %COUNT% jump credits.You only have 1 jump credit remaining.You have %REMAINING% Credits remaining.This warp is free, because you are at the station.Commence warpWarp costsAbort warpWarp: %SECONDS%Warp finished in 1 secondActivate: %SECONDS%Activate finished in 1 secondCannot warp. You do not have a flight-ready ship.Communication window - Mission ControlMissionsNormal MissionsStarter MissionsDaily MissionsEvent MissionsChallengesSpecialsHistoryOverviewDescriptionRewardRankingObjective(s)No available missionsAccept missionAbort missionAccept challengeAbort challengeConfirmAre you sure you wish to abort this mission?Destroy Destroy the required enemies.Collect Collect the required materials.Discovery Go on a journey of discovery.PvP Battle other players.Time Complete the mission in the time allowed.Event Complete the event missions.Event Complete the event missions.Epic Complete this mission for particularly valuable rewards.No available missionsWell done, pilot. You have completed all the tasks available. Stop by tomorrow and take on some more.There are no missions currently available for you. Make sure you check in on a regular basis, so you don't miss any!TBDMission unavailable. You may only have %AMOUNT% missions active at the same time.You have to reach level %AMOUNT% to be able to accept this mission.This mission will be available in %BEGIN% and lasts %TIME%.%MIN% of %MAX% missions have been completed to unlock this mission.This mission is only available during a special event.Show this player's pilot profile page%AMOUNT% mission slots remaining%AMOUNT% mission slots remainingDisplay current available missionsDisplay unavailable missionsDisplay completed missionsShow available quests which are recommended for your current levelSort missions by ascending/descending levelDisplay already attempted challengesDisplay not yet attempted challengesNameScoreDifference from leaderIn progressLevel %COUNT%CompletedStation ManagementStation InstallationModule InventoryModule InstallationInstallation StatusDeflector StatusTimeReg. RateNo rights to build a Station.Station RatingsBuildDeactivateClan ProgressProgress of leading ClanAn unknown error occurred.You have to be in a Clan to be able to build a Battle Station.&lt;br&gt;Click on the "Clan List" button below to see an overview of all current, active Clans!Clan ListThis Station has already been built.The Module has been destroyed and cannot be installed. To be able to use it again, you must repair it in your inventory.This Module is in use at another Station.This slot has already been filled by another player.You don't have the Clan rights to replace Modules.You don't own this Module.You are out of the Station's range.More than one Module cannot be installed at the same time.Only external Modules can be installed in this slot.Only central Modules can be installed in this slot.This Module has already been removed.You cannot install any more of these Modules.You don't have the rights to deactivate the Deflector.The Deflector has already been deactivated.No Modules to repair.You don't have enough Uridium to repair this item.This item repair is already underway.Module FilterClick: On/OffHullDeflectorsBoostersWorkshopLaser BanksRocket PhalanxShow allConstruction timeChoose the construction time for this Station.%VALUE% hBuildDeactivate DeflectorChoose your deactivation time%VALUE% hConfirmEmergency repairActivate emergency repairConfirmConstruction progressAsteroid captured by:CloseErrorOKConfirm Module removalAre you sure you want to remove this Module?ConfirmCancelCompany hierarchyCompany hierarchyConquer Battle Stations for your company and place your Clan in a position of power.Your Clan's positionPositionClanLeaderPointsEmployeesCEOTechnical OfficersStaff OfficersSecurity OfficersMining OfficersSecret Service OfficersResource OfficersRequisitions OfficersPress OfficersPurchased emergency repair for the %STATION% Battle Station.Emergency repair initiated for %STATION% Battle Station.You've received %AMOUNT% Uridium from the %MODULE% (Level %LEVEL%) Module at the %STATION% Battle Station.You've received %AMOUNT% Uridium from the %STATION% Battle Station.%CLAN% is now in control of the %STATION% Battle Station on the %MAP% map!%CLAN% is nowin control of the %STATION% Battle Station on the %MAP% map! This Battle Station's Defelctor is being activated.Battle Station %STATION% from %CLAN% on map %MAP% is now complete! The Battle Station's deflector is now being charged.%LOSER%'s %STATION% Battle Station was destroyed on the %MAP% map!%DESTROYER% destroyed %LOSER%'s %STATION% Battle Station on the %MAP% map!Activated Battle Station's Prime TimeEnded Battle Station's Prime TimeThe %STATION% Asteroid mysteriously disappeared from the %MAP% map.The %STATION% Asteroid showed up on the %MAP% map.You cannot attack this Battle Station because your Clan owns it.You cannot attack any Battle Stations that belong to a Clan in your company.The installation of this Module has been cancelled.Battle station %STATION% (%MAP%) is under attack! %MODULE% (%LEVEL%) module has been destroyed.This slot only works with Central Modules (Deflector or Hull).Your Clan installed %AMOUNT% Modules.%CLAN_NAME% installed %AMOUNT% Modules.You don't have the rights to build a Battle Station.Attack rateDefense rateRepair rateEP Booster RateDamage Booster RateHonor Booster RateRemaining Deflector MinutesDeflector Minutes Rate of ReturnGalaxy Gate %GATE% completed.Alpha Gate completed.Beta Galaxy Gate completed.Gamma Gate completed.Delta Gate completed.Galaxy Gate Groundforce completed.New Client Gate completed.Y3 Gate completed.Y4 Gate completed.Y5 Gate completed.Way to go, Pilot! You completed the Birthday Gate.Epsilon Gate completed.Zeta Gate completed.Galaxy Gate Kappa completed.Lambda Gate completed.Kronos Gate completed.Galaxy Gate Cold Wave (easy) completed.Galaxy Gate Cold Wave (hard) completed.Part received for the Kronos Gate.%COUNT% parts received for the Kronos Gate.Kronos Gate erected.Galaxy Gate P.E.T Attack (easy) completed.Galaxy Gate P.E.T Attack (hard) completed.Vortex of Terror Gate completed.Permafrost Fissure Gate completed.You still have unread messages in your inbox.You still have %COUNT% unread messages in your inbox.Please update your FlashPlayer to use the fullscreen mode.Internet Explorer unfortunately does not support interactive fullscreen mode.Fullscreen mode on/offHot keys only work if interactive fullscreen mode is allowed for the Flash Player.Fullscreen mode on/offYou can only plant one mine per position.You have requested to complete an action too soon after the last action. Please try again.Word puzzleThe puzzle is incomplete.Congratulations, you solved the puzzle!A capsule for the lottery has been booked to your account. As soon as you've collected the next letter, the puzzle starts over again.Collect cargo boxes from the Hitac minions. With a little luck, you'll find some of the letters you need. When you solve the word puzzle, you'll receive a capsule that you can trade in for a lottery ticket on the Uridium page. Solve the puzzle as often as you'd like.You received a capsule for the lottery!Progress in summoning Boss CurcubitorDisplay progress in summoning Boss Curcubitor.Wipe out %AMOUNT%/%TOTAL% Curcubitors to summon the Boss Curcubitor.Sector Control Lobby (Level %LEVELZONE%)Match%COMPANY% PlayersTicketsIn QueueThis match has been running for %TIME% minutesMatch needs at least %COUNT% players in two teams!Waiting for players!You are already in a queue for a different match. Do you really want to leave your current queue for another one?JoinLeaveClose the Lobby windowJoin the selected matchLeave the selected matchWaiting for more playersMatch has startedYou are in the queue for this matchAmount of tickets remainingNumber of players in matchYou are currently at position %POSITION% in the queue for match %MATCHID%Current location is not compatible with the Sector Control queuing system. No longer in queue.You have left the queue for Sector Control.Focus, pilot! Your match begins in %SECONDS% seconds.No turning back now – FIGHTWarning! Only %PERCENTAGE%% of tickets remaining!%COMPANY% lost all tickets and is out!%COMPANY% won the match!You destroyed %KILLS% players and will receive EP &amp; Honor bonuses of %PERCENTAGE%%. You died %DEATHS% times giving you a kill-to-death ratio of %KILL_DEATH_RATIO%.Time is of the essence! You are bleeding tickets %FACTOR% times faster than you were before!Sector Control%FACTION% tickets remainingPlayers in match%PERCENTAGE%% Damage BoosterCONQUERING ...NEUTRALIZING ...Sector Control - Level RequirementSector Control is a company-based event that requires players to be a level 8 or higher. You cannot participate yet.Participation ConfirmationThe Sector Control match you are queued for has begun. Do you still want to participate? You have %SECONDS% seconds to decide before automatically being removed from the queue.Sector ControlYour company has already lost this match. Try another one!Sector Control - Leave Game?Are you sure you want to leave this match? If you do, you will not qualify for any EP or Honor bonuses your team wins.Sector Control - Queue FullSorry but the queue is full. Join another match.%COUNT% / %TOTAL%%COUNT% - %TOTAL%Jackpot StatusRound %COUNT%Players remaining: %COUNT%/%TOTAL%Warping for this match starts in : %TIME%Warping is about to begin!Match ends in: %TIME%Warning: Radiation Zone is closing in!The next round begins in: %TIME%Congratulations, You got a free pass for this round, next update in: %TIME%JokerUnknown playerThis Free Pass is yours for the next round. You're receiving it because your opponent was missing or there were an odd number of players.You do not yet have an opponent for this round.StatsJackpot Arena - Match StatsHint: %HINT%A different ship or design might give you the competitive edge you've been looking for!There's nowhere to hide, pilots: make sure you've got some powerful shields!Make sure you have both arena configurations ready!WinLossDurationDamage inflictedDamage sustainedPeak damageWinsLossesWin rateMatch durationDamage inflictedDamage sustainedPeak damage per secondTotal winsTotal lossesWin to lose ratio in percentLength of match in minutes: %TIME%%NAME% inflicted %COUNT% damage%NAME% sustained %COUNT% damage%NAME%'s peak damage was %COUNT%%NAME% won %COUNT% times%NAME% lost %COUNT% times%NAME%'s win rate is %COUNT%%Hades Gate successfully completed.Hades Gate successfully activated.Attack canceled. It's not possible to attack other pilots when in the Hades Gate.Access denied - your group needs at least %COUNT% members to enter the Hades Gate.Access denied - you must be at the same stage as the group leader.Hades Gate server is at maximum capacity. Consider joining or creating a new group.Activation canceled – all group members must remain in the activation zone to start the gate.Access denied - Your group already completed the Hades Gate.Glad you made it. Amongst the usual alien chatter, I've picked up three unusually complex signals.I think they originated from the Aliosi Sector. It looks like the aliens' leaders are planning something...Only one way to find out for sure - destroy the alien waves, draw out their leaders, then do your companies proud and vaporize them!Fly to the activation zone marked on your minimap. This will trigger a subsonic frequency designed to draw the aliens out from the Nebula. Heads up: You'll need a complete group with at least 4 pilots to get started. If there are additional allies in the area, all will need to go into battle.Puny humans!Your unevolved skeletons and monkey brains make me want to puke.The sooner we wipe your stench from the galaxy the better!How dare you intrude on the inaugural Annihilation of Humanity Conference!I, Emperor of the mighty Lordakium, will not stand for this insolence! Prepare to die!We have observed your continuous wars and inability to live peacefully.Tolerating your existence would be illogical ...First-rate work, pilot! Your exploits are becoming a thing of legend. Watch your back...the alien leaders are already planning their next attack!That'll teach them not to underestimate us. Well done, pilot!You insignificant insects! I would have permitted you to die as your universe did, but you have now earned my particular attention - and this warning, which you are all receiving at once. I will see your entire puny race drained of its energy before I consume the rest of your universe!Do not presume to believe that you've defeated me, tiny beings. You have merely briefly delayed my conquest of your universe. Once I have recovered enough to open a new Breach, you will learn the meaning of fear: I will show you no mercy!Window has been resized. Reload the client with new resolution?You cannot gather laser ammo because your cargo is full.You cannot gather rockets or mines because your cargo is full.You cannot gather P.E.T. fuel because your cargo is full.Exit lobbyJoin selected matchLeave selected matchMatch scorePlayers in this matchWaiting for more playersMatch in progressYou're in the match queueMatch scoreMaximum number of playersTeam Deathmatch Lobby %LEVELZONE%Matches require at least 3 players per sideMatch ends in %TIME%LEAVEJOINTeam Deathmatch - Level requirementsTeam Deathmatches require players to be Level 8 or higher. Your level is too low to participate yet.Confirm Team DeathmatchThe Team Deathmatch for which you are queued has begun. Do you still want to participate? You have %SECONDS% seconds to decide before you are automatically removed from the queue.AGREELEAVE QUEUEPrizeItemQuantityYou have killed %KILLS% players, and died %DEATHS% times. This disqualifies you from receiving a reward.You have killed %KILLS% players, died %DEATHS% times and will receive the following reward:Team Deathmatch ResultsYour current location precludes you from joining a Team Deathmatch. You have been removed from the queue.Winning streakScore differenceKillsDeathsNo lives leftDrawLog OutWould you like to leave the Team Deathmatch?Would you like to leave the Team Deathmatch? You will not receive any rewards.Level too lowYour level is too low to participate in this match.Game endedThe game has already ended.No available game.There is no game available for this company.Team Deathmatch: %WINNER% has defeated %LOSER% with a score of %POINTS_WINNER% to %POINTS_LOSER%.  Match duration: %TIME%.Friendly fire disabledTeam Deathmatch Status:Lives:Time remaining:You have left the Team Deathmatch queue and will not receive any rewards.You are currently in queue position %POSITION% for match %MATCHID%The match has started. FIGHT!Waiting for more players.The next Jackpot Arena happens on %DAY%. %MONTH%.Tip: Fight in the monthly Jackpot Arena for a chance to win a maximum of 10,000 Euros!Open your company's Organization HierarchyOpen the Hangar where you can equip your ship (opens a browser tab or window)Repair your ship immediately. You have %VOUCHERS_PRESENT% repair vouchers which gives you %REPAIRS_POSSIBLE% immediate repairs.You don't have sufficient repair vouchers for an immediate repair. You have %VOUCHERS_PRESENT% repair vouchers, but a total of %VOUCHERS_NEEDED% is needed for an immediate repair.Trade your Ore for CreditsBrowse your company's missionsThis Jump Gate takes you to %MAP%.Click to open Sector Control match making UI.Click to open Team Deathmatch match making UI.How to disable Pepper Flash Player1. Open Chrome and type in chrome://plugins/ in URL. 2. Expand the ‘Details’ 3. Deactivate PepperFlash 4. Restart the browserShow me how!Your default Flash player can spoil your game experience. Fortunately this can be easily fixed!You get less reward from %NAME%, he is too weak for you!You aren't receiving any reward from %NAME%Corporate HeadquartersCorporate OutpostMission ControlAsteroidBattle StationHangarOutpost HangarRepair StationOutpost Repair StationOre RefineryOutpost Ore RefineryTeam Deathmatch BeaconSector Control BeaconBillboardOpen Galaxy GateCompany Policy ChangeThanks to a change in company policy, you're being upgraded to Level 5 and being issued a Piranha class ship! Lucky dog. You're also getting a few practical items, as our newest Hornet. Not that this is a reason to get comfy sittin' on your rear - check Mission Control for your next assignment!Orders from on high! Due to a company policy change, you're being upgraded to Level 5 and being issued a Piranha class ship. And as a welcome basket to our newest Scorpion, you also get a few other small, practical things. This all is no excuse for laziness, though: get to Mission Control and look for your next task!The memo I'm holding says that due to a change in company policy, your whole class of new Cobra members not only get promoted to Level 5, but also are being issued a goodie bag of practical items and a brand-new Piranha class starship! VRU takes care of its own! This is truth. Now - report to Mission Control!Open Shop NowOpen Equipment NowOpen SkylabOKArchiveFor Your InformationNew Employee OrientationPetterson here; come in, %HERONAME%. Welcome to MMO HQ, bug-hugger! Your bird should come installed with tracer 'ware that'll show a yellow (!) over Mission Control when I've got something for you.Welcome to EIC Headquarters, %HERONAME%; Admiral Crowley on the comm. Proceed at your earliest convenience - that means now, recruit - to Mission Control, over which your display should show a (!) whenever I have a mission for you.Greetings, %HERONAME%. I am so pleased to welcome you to the VRU fold! When I have an assignment for you, I've uploaded code to have a (!) show up on your display, over Mission Control in our HQ - come see me there now.MovementIt's simple: click anywhere on the map, or on a (!) , to fly to that location.Click on a location on the map, or on a (!) , to fly to that location. Clear?Click on a location on the map, or on a (!) , to fly there.MissionsWhen I have a mission for you, click on the yellow (!) displayed above Mission Control to accept it.Click on the yellow (!) displayed above Mission Control to accept a mission.Click on the yellow (!) displayed above Mission Control to accept a mission from me!Nanobot Ship RepairTake a breather! Once you're out of combat, whether you're on the move or staying still, pressing the 3 key will repair your ship.Let your guns cool for a moment. Any time you're out of combat, even if you're in motion, pressing the 3 key will repair your ship.Thanks to our upgraded bots, pressing the 3 key will repair your ship even when you're on the move - as long as you're not engaged in combat.Selling ResourcesIf you want to sell resources for Credits, you can do so at any time at the Refinery building at MMO HQ.Sell resources for Credits at any time at the Refinery building at EIC Headquarters. Build up your portfolio.If you want to sell resources for Credits, you can do so at the Refinery building here at VRU Headquarters, whenever you like.XP and AdvancementEarn XP (experience points), Honor, Credits, and Uridium by completing missions and destroying alien ships. That's how you get noticed!Earn XP (experience points), Honor, Credits, and Uridium by completing EIC missions and destroying alien ships. That's how you get noticed!Earn XP (experience points), Honor, Credits, and Uridium by completing missions and destroying xeno ships. That's how you get noticed!UpgradesGo to your Refining window's Upgrade tab to improve your weapons by drag-and-dropping ores onto them.Improve your weapons by drag-and-dropping ores onto them in your Refining window's Upgrade tab.To improve your weapons, drag and drop ores onto them in your Refining window's Upgrade tab.Buying MunitionsIf gathering munitions is taking too long for you, you can also buy them by clicking on the green Quick Shop button. Not that I'm arguin' against a little hard work, you understand - but it's just not sensible to pass up any possible avenue of advancement.If gathering munitions is taking too long for you, you can also buy them by clicking on the green Quick Shop button. Try to maintain yourself equipped with the best of what you can afford: it's a smart investment.If gathering munitions is taking too long for you, you can also buy them by clicking on the green Quick Shop button. And remember, you can tinker and improve and upgrade just about anything!QuickslotsWhen you expand the quickslot bar, you can drag and drop munitions into the quickslots you want to use as well as open all the munition menus. Get comfortable with your controls, pilot; speed saves lives.When you expand the quickslot bar, you can drag and drop munitions into the quickslots you wish to use, as well as open the various munition menus. Familiarize yourself with your controls: Fast reaction times saves lives.When you expand the quickslot bar, you can drag and drop munitions into the quickslots you want to use, as well as open the various munition menus. Know your tools, and you'll know your constraints: get used to your controls and displays!Jump GatesIf you're near a Gate, you can perform a jump by clicking on the Jump icon over the Gate, or by pressing the J key.If you are near a Gate, you can perform a jump by pressing the J key, or by clicking on the Jump icon over the Gate.If you are near a Gate, you can perform a jump by pressing the J key, or by clicking on the Jump icon over the Gate. Convenient, isn't it?The HangarPay a visit to the Hangar, in MMO Headquarters, when you want to get new equipment installed. I'll mark your mission complete once you're there.Once you've visited the Hanger, at EIC HQ, to install new equipment into your ship, I'll mark this mission a success in your ledger. I'm proud of you, recruit.To install new equipment into your ship, pay a visit to the Hangar, at VRU Headquarters. Once you're there, I'll be delighted to mark your mission a resounding success!The ShopYou can always buy better equipment from the Shop. Click on OPEN SHOP NOW and browse the Ships, Lasers, Generators, and more on offer there. Ahem. .....This has been an MMO-approved message.EIC requires me to inform you that you can click on OPEN SHOP NOW and browse the Ships, Lasers, Generators, and more on offer there. Ahem. ..."Only the best for the pride of Earth's security forces."You can always buy better equipment from the Shop, all of it thoroughly tested by and approved for VRU use! Click on OPEN SHOP NOW to browse the Ships, Lasers, Generators, and more on offer there.Shop and HangarYou're on your way to becoming a real asset to MMO - and the higher-ups agree. They've set you up with a sweet little ship - go to the Hangar to check it out! You probably already know that you can always buy better equipment in the Shop, too. Well done.You are becoming a true asset to EIC, and I'm not the only one who thinks so. High Command has granted you a bonus: a rather nice little vessel. You can visit it in the Hangar. And should you want to purchase better equipment for it or another of your ships, you can do so in the Shop.You're doing VRU proud. I'm not the only one to think so: the Security Circle has sent you a brand-new ship! Congratulations! Look for it in the Hangar - and if you want to buy it or another of your ships some better equipment, you can always find a good deal in the Shop.Allocate ShipEach Hangar hall has room for one spaceship. Place one in it with the "Allocate" button. Warning! If that Hangar already contains a ship, that ship will automatically be sold!Equip ShipEquipping your ship is as easy as drag and drop! Open the Hangar while you're at your Headquarters, and drag the item in question into the appropriate slot on your ship. That's it!Changing ShipsYou can change ships by clicking on the Ship Warp button. Make yourself comfortable later; we have things to do now.You can change ships by clicking on the Ship Warp button. Take my advice, though: wait until downtime to hang any artwork, and use something stronger than standard-issue Stikplast.You can change ships by clicking on the Ship Warp button! Don't worry, you won't have to mess about with suits or airlocks - we're not cavemen!Your Greatest EnemySo, tentacle-bait, you may have wondered why rival corp's higher-ranked pilots haven't, well, murdered you in the face. See, you're flagged as being under full and official MMO protection until your training's over - but that doesn't prevent people from killin' you if you start something. So behave. ...For now.You may have wondered why you're not already dead at the hands of higher-ranked rival Company pilots. You see, you're flagged as meriting full EIC retaliation if you're attacked, until this little audition is over - but that protection will not cover any altercations you initiate. So behave yourself. ...For now.While we have a moment, I'd like to explain why none of the other Companies' more advanced pilots have killed you - I'm sure you've wondered. VRU has an all-points flag on you, promising retribution if you are attacked without provocation, until your training is finished. So don't start anything with anyone human! ...For now.Premium PilotYour performance through the Galaxy Gate has earned me a commendation - and for that I'm getting you Premium status. It'll shorten your rocket cooldown time and improve your repairbots' efficiency. Congratulations!Your performance through the Galaxy Gate has earned me a commendation - and for that I'm getting you Premium status. It'll shorten your rocket cooldown time and improve your repairbots' efficiency. Congratulations!Your performance through the Galaxy Gate has earned me a commendation - and for that I'm getting you Premium status. It'll shorten your rocket cooldown time and improve your repairbots' efficiency. Congratulations!Officially Elite%HERONAME%... welcome to the Hornets! Use your Energy Spins to build Galaxy Gates, which will take you to distant and potentially profitable corners of the galaxy. As the recruitment speech I've mostly avoided giving you says: "no longer must humanity cower in the dark orbits of our own solar system - you are now part of our greater destiny among the stars!"%HERONAME%, it is my honor to welcome you to the Scorpions. You can now use your Energy Spins to build Galaxy Gates, which will take you to dangerous, far-flung, and potentially very profitable corners of the galaxy. Er, as EIC's mandatory recruitment speech puts it: "no longer must humanity cower in the dark orbits of our own solar system - you are now part of our greater destiny among the stars!"%HERONAME%, you are now officially a Cobra! Your Energy Spins can now build Galaxy Gates, which will take you to distant, xeno-filled, and potentially profitable sectors. As VRU's recruitment department has beautifully put it: "no longer must humanity cower in the dark orbits of our own solar system - you are now part of our greater destiny among the stars!"Equip Your Rockets!The right equipment can save your life, rookie. I'm not sure why you haven't equipped the more powerful PTL-2021 rockets yet, instead of the ordnance you're depending on now, but if I were you - I would!You need to be methodical and prepared in this line of work, and that means keeping an eye on the ordnance you're using and how it stacks up against your options. You should equip those PTL-2021 Rockets before you see action - they could save your life!Innovation, progress, upgrading - VRU values, all! You may want to keep them in mind more: you've got PTL-2021s in your hold, and they're a lot more powerful than what you have equipped. I'd strongly suggest switching them in before your next battle!The SkylabI recommend you build yourself that miracle of Martian technology: the Skylab!  You'll be able to refine the raw materials you find for yourself, to upgrade your weapons - or look under Trade Raw Materials to sell them for Credits.I recommend you build yourself that miracle of Earthling technology: the Skylab! You'll be able to refine the raw materials you find for yourself, to upgrade your weapons - or look under Trade Raw Materials to sell them for Credits.I recommend you build yourself that miracle of Venusian technology: the Skylab!  You'll be able to refine the raw materials you find for yourself, to upgrade your weapons - or look under Trade Raw Materials to sell them for Credits.Jump CPUMessage, rookie! Now that those goo-buckets have turned tail, we need you back here! Use the Jump CPU 1 built into your ship to jump straight back to your home map.Good work, there! You gave those spineless blobs what for. They've withdrawn, for now. Use your built-in Jump CPU 1 to jump directly back to our home map. You're needed here once more!Oh, wonderful job! Those Lordakia certainly weren't expecting that. Let's get you back here; there's always work to do! Use the Jump CPU 1 - it's built into your ship, and always allows you to jump straight back to your home map.Unencountered DangersGood work, there! MMO is formally thanking you with Premium status, but don't let it go to your head: that last wave only consisted of Sibelon cannon-fodder. When an actual Sibelon shows up on your display, be prepared for a real fight! But don't let that stop you from exploring deep space. That's where the richest prizes are earned.First-class work! Don't let EIC's reward of Premium status go to your head. You've confronted the hapless cannon fodder that the Sibelon feed into their war machine, but you've not come across an actual Sibelon yet. The first time one comes up on your display, steel yourself for a deadly opponent! As you explore deeper into space, you'll have a chance to show your mettle.Congratulations! VRU has rewarded you for your efforts with Premium status - but don't let that make you cocky! You still haven't met humanity's greatest enemy: the Sibelon; you've just come across their cannon-fodder vassals. Hone your skills and ready yourself, and eventually you'll be able to face one in combat, in the deep, wonderful, mysterious reaches of space.Attack!All right, rookie, here's a quick rundown of your new ship's basic offensive commands. Click on an enemy to select it as your target. Press &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;1 on your keyboard&lt;/font&gt; to &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;fire your lasers&lt;/font&gt;. Pressing the 1 button again will stop them firing. To &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;launch a rocket&lt;/font&gt; at your target, press &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;2 on your keyboard&lt;/font&gt;. That's it!Let's get used to your new ship's controls, in terms of offence. First, click on any enemy to select them as your target. Then, press &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;1 on your keyboard&lt;/font&gt; to &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;fire your lasers&lt;/font&gt;; pressing 1 again will stop them firing. Press &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;2 on your keyboard&lt;/font&gt; to &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;launch a rocket&lt;/font&gt;.I do so love new gadgets, don't you? Let's get you used to the controls on yours! It's simple: click on any enemy to select them as your target, then pressing &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;1 on your keyboard&lt;/font&gt; will &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;fire your lasers&lt;/font&gt;, and pressing 1 again will stop them firing. Or, you can press &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;2 on your keyboard&lt;/font&gt; to &lt;font color="%marked_yellow%"&gt;launch a rocket&lt;/font&gt; at your target.Your cargo is fullYour cargo is completely full. To make room you can sell resources at the refinery in your home base or by upgrading the ore yourself using the refining option from the menu on the bottom.Your cargo is completely full. To make room you can sell resources at the refinery in your home base or by upgrading the ore yourself using the refining option from the menu on the bottom.Your cargo is completely full. To make room you can sell resources at the refinery in your home base or by upgrading the ore yourself using the refining option from the menu on the bottom.Auction HouseAt your Company's Auction House, you'll find premium munitions and ships for a good price. Check in often: there are always good bargains to be found!Battle StationsYou and your fellow Clan members can gain many advantages from a Battle Station - create your own by installing modules onto an asteroid!Contact ListOn your Contact List you can add and manage your friends and contacts, making it easier to get in touch with them and play together.Extras and CPUsVisit the Extras tab in the Shop to view and install various items that can modify and improve your ship's performance in flight or combat.Galaxy gatesWe need you at the front lines! Open a Galaxy Gate to become part of an incursion into the heart of alien territory. Huge rewards await you - build and enter a Galaxy Gate now. We here at %companyShortName% have some extra Energy for you to speed up its construction!Looking for GroupsFind other players to join you in the Groups window - there's strength in numbers!Ore TransferIn the Skylab window, you can transfer ore between your ship and your Skylab, allowing you to improve your income of Credits or upgrade your weapons with Seprom!PalladiumPalladium can be traded for Extra Energy at the Marauder's market in Map 5-2. Collect all you can, as that Energy speeds up Galaxy Gate construction!Rocket launcherThe Rocket Launcher is a powerful tactical weapon, and is required to fire off Eco and Hellstorm rockets. After installing one of them onto your ship, return to the game client and drag-and-drop the rocket launcher into your quickslot bar. Then, select a valid ammunition to load it.ConfigurationsYour ship has two Configurations; you can switch between them by pressing the C key, even in the middle of a battle. This can help you last longer in a fight. Set up your second Configuration in the Hangar now!Ship DesignsNew and different Ship Designs don't just make your ship look flashier - they also grant tactical advantages, in battle and out of it. Try out and install a new design, and drive your enemies before you!Skill TreePilot skills can improve your performance in battle - upgrade them with log-disks in the Skill Tree section of your Pilot Sheet now! A change to even a small detail can make all the difference in an emergency.Tech FactoryVisit the Tech Factory in the Upgrades window to produce various items that will give you a range of advantages in combat. Surprise your enemy with your tactical superiority!Equipment UpgradesIt's time to start upgrading your equipment, using Uridium to make it more efficient and powerful! Visit the Upgrades window to do so.Extra Energy PackGalaxy GateStart Upgrading!Open HangarView CPU'sOpen ContactlistOpen Pilot SheetGet Log DisksVisit FactoryOpen SkylabOpen nowRocket LauncherShow DesignsRecall your friendsSome of your friends haven't been around lately and you need their help to dominate the Galaxy? Recall them now!Recall friendsUltimate Battle ArenaThe Ultimate Battle Arena is a safe place to improve your PvP skills in rapid 1 vs. 1 duels. Win or lose, dare to try: you won't lose any resources or suffer damage to your drones. After the duel, you'll be returned to the map you were on before, with full HP and shields.Take part in the player survey!We are constantly working on making our game more interesting and appealing, and your opinion is very important to us. Please take part in our survey and help us shape the future of DarkOrbit!&lt;br&gt;The survey will open in a separate window and will take you no more than 15 minutes.&lt;br&gt;You will receive 250 Extra Energy as a small thank you gift!Dear Space Pilot,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are constantly trying to improve fairness and prices, and we request your assistance!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please take this 10 minute survey and give us your feedback!Take the surveyNo thank youCategoriesPremium BarStandard BarThis pilot is under full corporate protection until the end of his training period and cannot be attacked.You withstood the Devolarium attack.New missions are now availableContactsContactsShow/hide your contactsShow/hide clan membersInvitesView pending invitesBlacklistThis pilot is on your blacklist.Show/hide ignored pilotsIgnore all invitesAutomatically ignores all invites.Click on a ship or enter the pilot's name into this field to select it.Adds the selected pilot(s) to your Contact list.Removes the selected pilot(s) from your Contact list.Ignores the selected pilot(s), preventing them from contacting you.Stop ignoring this pilot. They will be able to contact you again.Adds the selected pilot(s) to your Contact list.Decline this invite.Remove this pending invite.Invite this pilot to join your group.ClanClick to edit this contact.Click to edit this contact. Double-click to whisper to them.Level %LEVEL% - Clan: %CLANTAG% This pilot is online and on the same map as you are.Level %LEVEL% - Clan: %CLANTAG% This pilot is online.Level %LEVEL% - Clan: %CLANTAG% This pilot is offline.Level %LEVEL% - Clan: %CLANTAG% You are ignoring this pilot.Level %LEVEL% - Clan: %CLANTAG% This pilot wants to add you to their Contact list.Level %LEVEL% - Clan: %CLANTAG% You have sent these pilots invites.Your invite is still pending.Your invite was declined.This pilot is a member of your Clan.This pilot belongs to a friendly Clan.This pilot belongs to an enemy Clan.This pilot's Clan is also employed by your Company.You have sent an invite to %NAME%.%NAME% has been removed from your Contacts.%NAME% is now ignored.%NAME% will no longer be ignored.%NAME% rejected your invitation.%NAME% successfully added to your Contacts.There is no pilot named %NAME% on this server.%NAME% is already on your Contact list.You've already sent %NAME% an invite.%NAME% is ignoring all invites.%NAME% is not one of your Contacts, so you can't delete them from your Contacts.%NAME% is already in a group.%NAME% is already in your group.%NAME% has disabled private chat.Since you have ignored %NAME%, whispering is not allowed.Company InfluenceDepending on final Company Influence levels at the end of the Battle for Influence, Company-wide bonuses will be granted. The winning Company will benefit from additional bonuses!Personal InfluenceYour personal Influence determines which achievements and titles you may be awarded.Battle for Influence statusBattle for Influence statusYou have increased %FACTION%'s Influence by %POINTSEARNED% points!%FACTION% now ranks highest in the Battle for Influence, with %FACTIONPOINTS%! Excellent work; keep it up!%FACTION% now ranks second highest in the Battle for Influence, with %FACTIONPOINTS%! With a little push, we could be first!%FACTION% now ranks third highest in the Battle for Influence, with %FACTIONPOINTS%! Let's pick up the pace, here!Ultimate Battle ArenaVictories: %AMOUNT%Duels fought: %AMOUNT%Current score: %AMOUNT%Play a quick 1 vs. 1 duel against a random opponent.&lt;br /&gt;Once the duel is complete, you will be returned to the map you were on, with your HP and shield refilled.&lt;br /&gt;A tip: if you lose the duel, you will not lose any of your drones or resources.You’re too weak to fight in the Battle Arena. Toughen up, improve your equipment, and return to face the challenge!MatchmakingCancelYou CANNOT enter into this duel until you have finished your current combat.Ultimate Battle Arena: You may not deploy mines while waiting for your opponent. Nice try, though.Searching for an opponentContinue to play normally. You will be alerted as soon as an opponent is found.Opponent found!BEGIN this duel.You CANNOT enter into this duel until you have finished your current PvP combat.Fight!%COUNTDOWN%%COUNTDOWN%Wait for your opponentYour opponent is under attack.Your opponent has not yet accepted this duel.You cannot enter the Ultimate Battle Arena while you're in a Galaxy Gate or in an instanced PvP conflict.BEGIN this duel.Ultimate Battle Arena: You cannot attack another player while you're waiting for your duel to start. Patience.Your opponent has withdrawn from the duel.Opponent has left the game: %COUNTDOWN% Opponent has reconnected.This player cannot be attacked, as they're waiting to begin a duel in the Ultimate Battle Arena.You will be returned to the %MAP% map.The use of a Jump CPU isn't allowed in the Ultimate Battle Arena.The use of a Ship Warp isn't allowed in the Ultimate Battle Arena.You cannot enter the Ultimate Battle Arena while you are in a Galaxy Gate or a PvP Event game.ULTIMATE BATTLE ARENA TEMPORARILY CLOSED FOR CLEANING: our minesweeper trawlers are disposing of wreckage and debris. The Ultimate Battle Arena will re-open for duels shortly!You cannot use the Ultimate Battle Arena because you have registered for the Jackpot Arena, which will start shortly. You will be able to enter the UBA again once you're finished with it!The use of a Cloaking CPU isn't allowed in the Ultimate Battle Arena.Ultimate Battle Arena: You can't collect any items while waiting for an opponent.Ultimate Battle Arena ResultsVICTORYDRAWDEFEATDetailsPrizeAmountRounds wonScoreThis Domination Beacon was captured too recently by %companyname% and can not yet be retaken!%companyname% is no longer dominating the Battle Maps.Look out! Enemy ships are attacking our Domination Beacons on %mapname%!%CompanyName% is dominating the Battle Maps!A Gate between our home map and Map 4-4 has been activated. All Company members will now receive a discount in the Shop!Domination Event statusFor every %SECONDS% seconds that it dominates the Battle Maps during the event, your Company will receive %AMOUNT%x Influence Points.Company InfluenceYou've received %AMOUNT% Credits from the %MODULE% (Level %LEVEL%) Module at the %STATION% Battle Station.You've received %AMOUNT% Credits from the %STATION% Battle Station.Domination statusCollecting Demaner Freighter Cargo.Transactions remaining: UnlimitedPower UpgradeThe best-equipped starter ship available!Hunting TimeBetter, faster, and deadlier than ever!Time to Get SeriousDominate your sector with this set of drones!Time to Blast!Build a Galaxy Gate and unleash your wrath on the aliens within!Iron GiantA trophy from the Ultimate Battle Arena!Trade droneSell Ore without having to return to HQ!Independence DesignDeclare your independence in this sleek ship!Bonus box boosterDouble the bonus box contents for three days!Quest reward boosterDouble your mission rewards for three days!Feedback
 Trade EmpireSell Ore without having to return to HQ!Independence DesignDeclare your independence in this sleek ship!Bonus Box BoosterDouble the bonus box contents for three days!Mission BoosterDouble your mission rewards for three days!Feedback
 You’ve completed the LoW Gate. Great job!You did not reach this Gate’s required group size in time!You’re missing %MISSINGMEMBERCOUNT% members for this Gate group. You have %WAITINGTIME% seconds until the mission is cancelled!The relay stations can’t be brought online while pirates are on the map!You need to boot up the LoW Gate before the relay stations can be brought online!The LoW Gate has been brought online!No instance found! Create an instance for your group...Your group is the wrong size (Min.: %MINSIZE%, Max.: %MAXSIZE%).You have been sent back to your home map because you left your group before the Gate was brought online!Ultimate Battle Arena: You can't enter a Galaxy Gate while seeking a duel.Waiting for admin...Serum CPUAmount: %COUNT%Cures you of any infection or parasiteSerum CPU XLAmount: %COUNT%Cures you, and your target, of any infectionMust be uninfectedMust be infectedParasite TideParasite statusInfectedHealthyDamage at %DMG%%, speed at %SPEED%%, hull integrity at %HULL%% Gygerim approach progressGygerim arriving on map:%NPC_NAME% has been destroyed. Another will arrive soon!You crave the blessing of being a host.You want to be cured!You want to grant someone else the blessing of being a host.You want to deliver someone else from their infection!You want to spread the blessing of being a host!Cure someone of their infection.You must destroy a non-host!Destroy an infected person.Surprise! Look what you found!Switching between 2D and 3D requires a client restart. Do you want to reboot the game now?You can't lay these mines in the Ultimate Battle Arena!You can't use this ammunition in the Ultimate Battle Arena!You may not use PIB-100 in the Ultimate Battle Arena. Auto-selected ammo: %AMMO%.Your parasitic infection status. Check it to see if you're healthy... or infected.To lure in a Gygerim Mothership, destroy Gygerthralls until this progress bar is filled.Your personal score.Target is not infected!Anti-aliasingDetermines how much of your CPU's processing power will be dedicated to the display of anti-aliased edges.LightingDetermines the quality and level of detail of the lighting displayed.TexturesDetermines the quality and resolution level of the textures displayed.Texture SizeDetermines how much memory can be committed to the display of higher resolution textures, which defines their maximum size.EffectsDetermines the quality of the visual effects.Texture FilteringDetermines the quality and level of detail of the texture filtering used, which may affect the colors displayed.Choose 2D versionChoose 3D versionConfigure your menu and quickslot positions and preferences.BackgroundsDetermines the quality and level of detail of the background images displayed.ZonesDetermines the quality of the block zones displayed.3DNo thanks - I'll stick with the 2D version for now.Try DarkOrbit out in 3D! &lt;font color="#fbcc00"&gt;The new 3D client has arrived.&lt;/font&gt; Update your graphics card driver and your Flash player. You'll also need to enable Hardware Acceleration. (Right-click -&gt; Settings)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Play in 3D and become a &lt;font color="#fbcc00"&gt;"Multi-Dimensional Pilot"!&lt;/font&gt;DarkOrbit is now in 3D!The 3D experience is not available to you because either your Flash player is outdated, your graphics card doesn't support it, or hardware acceleration is deactivated.Learn more about the 3D version and system requirementshttp://www.bigpoint.com/darkorbit/board/threads/3d-faq.102621/ DarkOrbit has entered the next dimension - &lt;font color="#fbcc00"&gt;The new client has arrived.&lt;/font&gt; Unfortunately, we have detected that you can’t currently run the 3D version. Update your graphics card drivers, your Flash player, and enable Hardware Acceleration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Once your PC is ready, play in 3D and become a &lt;font color="#fbcc00"&gt;“Multi-Dimensional Pilot"!&lt;/font&gt;Play in 2DUltimate Battle Arena Season %SEASON_NAME%: you have received the %RANKING_POSITION% reward pack.%NAME% - Time left: %DATE%MatchPerformanceRewardsSeasonRankRewardsRank: %AMOUNT%Score: %AMOUNT%Arena Season ends in: 1 hourArena Season ends in: 5 minutesArena Season ends in: %MINS% minutes!Arena Season has endedNo Season currently runningThere is no Season running, and therefore no medals to winYou have received a Jump CPU 1Pro action barThe pro action bar gives you a quick access to those items that you don't use frequently enough to have them in the main action bar but to which you want to have a quick access to them in case of need. You can open and close it using SHIFT button, it also closes automatically once you have selected the item you needed. Of course you can set up it's look and position from the config mode in the game settings. While the pro bar is open the shortcuts keys you regularly use only affect this bar, so that by pressing SHIFT and then 1 you will trigger the item you had in that slot.AssemblyChoose any item from the list and click the Assemble button once you have all the necessary components and collectibles!Display pro action barUse key bindings for pro action barAuto hide pro action barShow/Hide Pro Action BarAttention all Streuner in or near the Kuiper Belt! We are under attack! This is not a drill. Prepare defensive measures at once: Code 1701 Delta!Stranger, I don't know who you are - but let's talk civilly, human to human. ...What, has fear struck you dumb? Don't be too hard on yourself: my soldiers Shock and Awe often have that effect!What exactly are you trying to prove, here? Are you after fame? Credits? I warn you, if you keep coming - we Streuners stick together! And we'll unite against any invaders!See these turrets? You might recognize their design... Donations from our highly esteemed patrons! And after all, we Streuners can't look gift allies in the mouth.This is your last warning. Reverse course, or face the consequences. This is our home, and we'll defend it to the very last Streuner!Emperor Erreet Falard to unidentified ship: you are out of warnings. Streuners, to me! I'll take care of this corporate lapdog personally.That idiot Erreet's fleet is coming apart. Streuners can be useful if they're properly armed, but I suppose breeding tells: sooner or later, human filth is still human filth. &lt;br/&gt;What? You dare attack me?! Then come and get it, vermin!Kuiper Galaxy Gate successfully completed.Play a quick 1 vs. 1 duel against a random opponent.&lt;br /&gt;Once the duel is complete, you will be returned to the map you were on, with your HP and shield refilled.&lt;br /&gt;A tip: if you lose the duel, you will not lose any of your drones or resources. Nanohull and Ore update won´t be available during UBA matches.AssemblyAssembleCollectAssembly unavailable: you already own the maximum amount of the selected item(s).Get any missing parts now!You have no items available to be assembled at the moment. The Assembly allows you to combine raw materials and collectibles to produce free ships, equipment, and items!Assembling %item%. Please stand by.Assembly complete in: %time%A new item is available at the Assembly: %item%You already own the following: %item%. The following resources and collectibles have been refunded:Assembled %item%Single-use blueprint consumed.No items found under the selected filter.FilterAssembly of %recipename% is now complete.%itemname% retrieved from the Assembly.The following items and/or collectibles were consumed to assemble %recipename%:%count% %lootId%(s) were consumed.Collected the %recipename% and received the following item(s):%recipename% is no longer available to be assembled. Your resources and collectibles have been refunded.No items found under the selected filter.%recipename% assembly is now under way.This blueprint can only be used once.Thank you for taking part in the survey. You've just received your gift of 250 Extra Energy.Turn Game into retro modeTime left for this offerYou can only Warp ships that are marked as your favorites!For renaming your P.E.T.:Poison Pusat designPoison Spectrum designPoison Pusat drone designPoison Spectrum drone designPoison A-Elite designPoison A-Elite drone designPoison A-Elite P.E.T designLegend A-Elite designLegend Spectrum BlueprintAwesome gear on offer!Only available now!Time to get revenge, pilot!Damn those alien hordes!Tactically astute enemy kill!Mankind loves a true hero.RegistrationEXITLeaving Refractions.You cannot enter Refractions when in combat!JUMP NOW!It takes a short time for your nav-computer to plot your exit from Refractions.ConfirmationRefractionsYou've been waiting for:QUEUE NOW!RefractionsCANCELREFRACTION TEMPORARILY CLOSED FOR CLEANING: our minesweeper trawlers are disposing of wreckage and debris. The Refraction will re-open for duels shortly!Enter RefractionsWe've reserved your spot for the next jump to Refractions.Refractions is unstable. Wait for it to stabilize or leave!Refractions will close in:Your nav-computer needs to connect to Refractions to plot your course there.Permafrost Fissure AssembliesThis is how it works!Gather valuable Proxium from the Permafrost Fissure using the Subglacial CPU and create the other exotic elements to get hold of an Unstable LF-4. Burn a new hole in the galaxy!Damage from a minimum of 128 to a maximum of 220.Your Proxium Doubler Booster expires in %HOURS% hours.Your Proxium Doubler Booster expires in %MINUTES% minutes.Your Proxium Drop Booster expires in %HOURS% hours.Your Proxium Drop Booster expires in %MINUTES% minutes.Equipment boosterWeekly MissionsAccept MissionEasyMediumHardMy systems identify that you cannot take a new weekly quest at the moment. Weekly quests become available on Monday, each week.Show All BoostersHatching Out!CollectRestartEvent Ends in:ProgressSourcesNext Reward:15 Khyalon and 50 Bifenon40 Khyalon and 60 TetrathrinTime left:Help remove the viral infection by collecting Viral Purge points. The more you collect, the better the rewards. With factions agreeing to award all who complete the process an LF-4. The more times you complete the process the more awards you will gain. So, its time to prepare for action.You can collect Viral Purge points from: Eggs, Gygerthralls, Killing the HITAC, Event Missions and Alpha, Beta and Gamma Gates.ProgressGet it Now!Exclusive Discount!You've won, pilot! Quarantine Zone successfully completed.Quarantine Zone activated.Sorry, it's not possible to attack other pilots when in the Quarantine Zone.Access denied - your group needs at least %COUNT% members to enter the Quarantine Zone.Access denied - you must be at the same stage as the group leader.Quarantine Zone server is at maximum capacity. Consider joining or creating a new group.Activation canceled – all group members must remain in the activation zone to start the gate.Access denied - Your group already completed the Quarantine Zone.Plague Alert!Kill Progress%AMOUNT% %KILL_NAME% kills until the next %SPAWN_NAME% spawn.Current %NPC_NAME% on the map: %AMOUNT%Plague Alert!There are currently %AMOUNT% %NPC_NAME% on the map!A fine selection of prizes can be found in the Apocalypse Box. Grab it now, pilot!The Red Booty Box is stocked full of treasures. Open it with a Red Booty Key!The Blue Booty Box is stocked full of treasures. Open it with a Blue Booty Key!You need an Immunizer CPU and a group to access the Quarantine Zone.Your ship cannot go to warp while queuing for Refractions.Your ship cannot go to warp during entry confirmation to Refractions.Pirate Hunt RewardsCONGRATULATIONS!We are delighted to reward you for your actions protecting humanity.We are delighted to reward your clan for your actions in protecting humanity.ACCEPTYou are No. #%POSITION%OVERVIEWPOINTSREWARDSTime Left:Player PointsClan PointsIf you want to compare your position with others, check out the Hall of Fame.HALL OF FAMEOpens a new browser tabPREYPOINTSPLAYER REWARDSCLAN REWARDSRewards for %POSITION% positionClan rewards for %POSITION% position<item name="desc_questwin_no_weekly_event_quests_available_NYX"><![CDATA[My systems identify that you cannot take a new weekly quest at the moment. Weekly quests become available on Monday, each week.]]></item>
    <item name="booster_filter_show_all"><![CDATA[Show All Boosters]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_title"><![CDATA[Hatching Out!]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_button_confirmation_collect_rewards"><![CDATA[Collect]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_button_confirmation_collect_restart"><![CDATA[Restart]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_label_event_ends"><![CDATA[Event Ends in:]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_tabbar_eventprogress"><![CDATA[Progress]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_tabbar_explanation"><![CDATA[Sources]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_label_nextreward"><![CDATA[Next Reward:]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_tooltip_package01_hatching_out"><![CDATA[15 Khyalon and 50 Bifenon]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_tooltip_package02_hatching_out"><![CDATA[40 Khyalon and 60 Tetrathrin]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_label_timeleft"><![CDATA[Time left:]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_label_description"><![CDATA[Help remove the viral infection by collecting Viral Purge points. The more you collect, the better the rewards. With factions agreeing to award all who complete the process an LF-4. The more times you complete the process the more awards you will gain. So, its time to prepare for action.]]></item>
    <item name="window_event_progress_label_event_collection_points_hatchingout_event"><![CDATA[You can collect Viral Purge points from: Eggs, Gygerthralls, Killing the HITAC, Event Missions and Alpha, Beta and Gamma Gates.]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_event_progress"><![CDATA[Progress]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_buy_button"><![CDATA[Get it Now!]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_headline"><![CDATA[Exclusive Discount!]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_gg_completed_quarantine_zone"><![CDATA[You've won, pilot! Quarantine Zone successfully completed.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_quarantine_zone_get_ready"><![CDATA[Quarantine Zone activated.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_quarantine_zone_no_pvp"><![CDATA[Sorry, it's not possible to attack other pilots when in the Quarantine Zone.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_quarantine_zone_not_in_group"><![CDATA[Access denied - your group needs at least %COUNT% members to enter the Quarantine Zone.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_quarantine_zone_wrong_gate_stage"><![CDATA[Access denied - you must be at the same stage as the group leader.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_quarantine_zone_max_players_reached"><![CDATA[Quarantine Zone server is at maximum capacity. Consider joining or creating a new group.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_quarantine_zone_activation_cancelled"><![CDATA[Activation canceled – all group members must remain in the activation zone to start the gate.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_quarantine_zone_already_completed"><![CDATA[Access denied - Your group already completed the Quarantine Zone.]]></item>
    <item name="title_plague_kill_progress_window"><![CDATA[Plague Alert!]]></item>
    <item name="kill_progress_window_headline"><![CDATA[Kill Progress]]></item>
    <item name="kill_progress_window_kills_left"><![CDATA[%AMOUNT% %KILL_NAME% kills until the next %SPAWN_NAME% spawn.]]></item>
    <item name="kill_progress_window_npc_count"><![CDATA[Current %NPC_NAME% on the map: %AMOUNT%]]></item>
    <item name="kill_progress_window_plague_alert"><![CDATA[Plague Alert!]]></item>
    <item name="kill_progress_window_npc_count_2"><![CDATA[There are currently %AMOUNT% %NPC_NAME% on the map!]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_apocalypse_box"><![CDATA[A fine selection of prizes can be found in the Apocalypse Box. Grab it now, pilot!]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_red_bootybox"><![CDATA[The Red Booty Box is stocked full of treasures. Open it with a Red Booty Key!]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blue_bootybox"><![CDATA[The Blue Booty Box is stocked full of treasures. Open it with a Blue Booty Key!]]></item>
    <item name="jumpgate_failed_no_key_activated"><![CDATA[You need an Immunizer CPU and a group to access the Quarantine Zone.]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_no_warp_queue_rzone"><![CDATA[Your ship cannot go to warp while queuing for Refractions.]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_no_warp_confirmation_rzone"><![CDATA[Your ship cannot go to warp during entry confirmation to Refractions.]]></item>
    <item name="title_event_rewards_window"><![CDATA[Pirate Hunt Rewards]]></item>
    <item name="event_rewards_window_headline"><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS!]]></item>
    <item name="event_rewards_window_message"><![CDATA[We are delighted to reward you for your actions protecting humanity.]]></item>
    <item name="event_rewards_window_message_clan"><![CDATA[We are delighted to reward your clan for your actions in protecting humanity.]]></item>
    <item name="event_rewards_window_confirmBtn"><![CDATA[ACCEPT]]></item>
    <item name="event_rewards_window_place"><![CDATA[You are No. #%POSITION%]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_overview"><![CDATA[OVERVIEW]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_points"><![CDATA[POINTS]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_rewards"><![CDATA[REWARDS]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_overview_timeleft"><![CDATA[Time Left:]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_overview_playerpoints"><![CDATA[Player Points]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_overview_clanpoints"><![CDATA[Clan Points]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_overview_hint"><![CDATA[If you want to compare your position with others, check out the Hall of Fame.]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_overview_button"><![CDATA[HALL OF FAME]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_overview_button_ttip"><![CDATA[Opens a new browser tab]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_points_headline_prey"><![CDATA[PREY]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_points_headline_points"><![CDATA[POINTS]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_rewards_headline_playerrewards"><![CDATA[PLAYER REWARDS]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_rewards_headline_clanrewards"><![CDATA[CLAN REWARDS]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_rewards_tooltip_playerrewards"><![CDATA[Rewards for %POSITION% position]]></item>
    <item name="alienhunt_tab_rewards_tooltip_clanrewards"><![CDATA[Clan rewards for %POSITION% position]]></item>
    <item name="msg_groupgate_finished"><![CDATA[You’ve completed the LoW Gate. Great job!]]></item>
    <item name="msg_groupgate_not_enough_players_in_group"><![CDATA[You did not reach this Gate’s required group size in time!]]></item>
    <item name="msg_groupgate_waiting_for_group_members"><![CDATA[You’re missing %MISSINGMEMBERCOUNT% members for this Gate group. You have %WAITINGTIME% seconds until the mission is cancelled!]]></item>
    <item name="msg_groupgate_cant_activate_relay_because_npcs_are_alive"><![CDATA[The relay stations can’t be brought online while pirates are on the map!]]></item>
    <item name="groupgate_cant_activate_relay_because_map_not_started_yet"><![CDATA[You need to boot up the LoW Gate before the relay stations can be brought online!]]></item>
    <item name="groupgate_map_started"><![CDATA[The LoW Gate has been brought online!]]></item>
    <item name="groupgate_map_created"><![CDATA[No instance found! Create an instance for your group...]]></item>
    <item name="groupgate_group_size_mismatch"><![CDATA[Your group is the wrong size (Min.: %MINSIZE%, Max.: %MAXSIZE%).]]></item>
    <item name="groupgate_kick_for_not_in_group"><![CDATA[You have been sent back to your home map because you left your group before the Gate was brought online!]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_traininggrounds_cannot_join_gg"><![CDATA[Ultimate Battle Arena: You can't enter a Galaxy Gate while seeking a duel.]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_custom_tournament_waiting_for_admin"><![CDATA[Waiting for admin...]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_antiz1_cpu"><![CDATA[Serum CPU]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_antiz1_cpu_count"><![CDATA[Amount: %COUNT%]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_antiz1_cpu_desc"><![CDATA[Cures you of any infection or parasite]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_antiz1-xl_cpu"><![CDATA[Serum CPU XL]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_antiz1-xl_cpu_count"><![CDATA[Amount: %COUNT%]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_antiz1-xl_cpu_desc"><![CDATA[Cures you, and your target, of any infection]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_be_healthy"><![CDATA[Must be uninfected]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_be_infected"><![CDATA[Must be infected]]></item>
    <item name="title_spaceplague"><![CDATA[Parasite Tide]]></item>
    <item name="plague_window_headline"><![CDATA[Parasite status]]></item>
    <item name="plague_window_infected"><![CDATA[Infected]]></item>
    <item name="plague_window_healthy"><![CDATA[Healthy]]></item>
    <item name="plague_window_label_buffs"><![CDATA[Damage at %DMG%%, speed at %SPEED%%, hull integrity at %HULL%% ]]></item>
    <item name="plague_mothership_progress"><![CDATA[Gygerim approach progress]]></item>
    <item name="plague_window_summon_info"><![CDATA[Gygerim arriving on map:]]></item>
    <item name="msg_summoning_boss_killed"><![CDATA[%NPC_NAME% has been destroyed. Another will arrive soon!]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_infect_self"><![CDATA[You crave the blessing of being a host.]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_cure_self"><![CDATA[You want to be cured!]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_infect_other"><![CDATA[You want to grant someone else the blessing of being a host.]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_cure_other"><![CDATA[You want to deliver someone else from their infection!]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_infect_any"><![CDATA[You want to spread the blessing of being a host!]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_cure_any"><![CDATA[Cure someone of their infection.]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_kill_healthy_players"><![CDATA[You must destroy a non-host!]]></item>
    <item name="plague_condition_kill_infected_players"><![CDATA[Destroy an infected person.]]></item>
    <item name="msg_easter_egg_found"><![CDATA[Surprise! Look what you found!]]></item>
    <item name="label_switch_2d3d_restart"><![CDATA[Switching between 2D and 3D requires a client restart. Do you want to reboot the game now?]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_inactive_mine_training_ground_map"><![CDATA[You can't lay these mines in the Ultimate Battle Arena!]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_inactive_laser_training_ground_map"><![CDATA[You can't use this ammunition in the Ultimate Battle Arena!]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_traininggrounds_prohibit_ammo_pib100"><![CDATA[You may not use PIB-100 in the Ultimate Battle Arena. Auto-selected ammo: %AMMO%.]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_plague_header"><![CDATA[Your parasitic infection status. Check it to see if you're healthy... or infected.]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_plague_center"><![CDATA[To lure in a Gygerim Mothership, destroy Gygerthralls until this progress bar is filled.]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_plague_footer"><![CDATA[Your personal score.]]></item>
    <item name="plague_cure_cpu_no_target"><![CDATA[Target is not infected!]]></item>
    <item name="setting_antialiasing"><![CDATA[Anti-aliasing]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_antialiasing"><![CDATA[Determines how much of your CPU's processing power will be dedicated to the display of anti-aliased edges.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_lights"><![CDATA[Lighting]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_lights"><![CDATA[Determines the quality and level of detail of the lighting displayed.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_texture_quality"><![CDATA[Textures]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_texture_quality"><![CDATA[Determines the quality and resolution level of the textures displayed.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_texture_size"><![CDATA[Texture Size]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_texture_size"><![CDATA[Determines how much memory can be committed to the display of higher resolution textures, which defines their maximum size.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_quality_effects"><![CDATA[Effects]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_quality_effects"><![CDATA[Determines the quality of the visual effects.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_texture_filtering"><![CDATA[Texture Filtering]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_texture_filtering"><![CDATA[Determines the quality and level of detail of the texture filtering used, which may affect the colors displayed.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_use2D"><![CDATA[Choose 2D version]]></item>
    <item name="setting_use3D"><![CDATA[Choose 3D version]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_open_config_mode_window"><![CDATA[Configure your menu and quickslot positions and preferences.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_quality_background3D"><![CDATA[Backgrounds]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_quality_background3D"><![CDATA[Determines the quality and level of detail of the background images displayed.]]></item>
    <item name="setting_quality_zones3D"><![CDATA[Zones]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_setting_quality_zones3D"><![CDATA[Determines the quality of the block zones displayed.]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_3d"><![CDATA[3D]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_2d"><![CDATA[No thanks - I'll stick with the 2D version for now.]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_info"><![CDATA[Try DarkOrbit out in 3D! <font color="#fbcc00">The new 3D client has arrived.</font> Update your graphics card driver and your Flash player. You'll also need to enable Hardware Acceleration. (Right-click -> Settings)<br/><br/> Play in 3D and become a <font color="#fbcc00">"Multi-Dimensional Pilot"!</font>]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_headline"><![CDATA[DarkOrbit is now in 3D!]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_3d_not_available"><![CDATA[The 3D experience is not available to you because either your Flash player is outdated, your graphics card doesn't support it, or hardware acceleration is deactivated.]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_faq"><![CDATA[Learn more about the 3D version and system requirements]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_faq_link"><![CDATA[http://www.bigpoint.com/darkorbit/board/threads/3d-faq.102621/ ]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_info_no_3d"><![CDATA[DarkOrbit has entered the next dimension - <font color="#fbcc00">The new client has arrived.</font> Unfortunately, we have detected that you can’t currently run the 3D version. Update your graphics card drivers, your Flash player, and enable Hardware Acceleration.<br/><br/> Once your PC is ready, play in 3D and become a <font color="#fbcc00">“Multi-Dimensional Pilot"!</font>]]></item>
    <item name="client_selection_continue_2d"><![CDATA[Play in 2D]]></item>
    <item name="msg_reward_trainingArenaSeason_package_received"><![CDATA[Ultimate Battle Arena Season %SEASON_NAME%: you have received the %RANKING_POSITION% reward pack.]]></item>
    <item name="label_traininggrounds_season"><![CDATA[%NAME% - Time left: %DATE%]]></item>
    <item name="button_tas_match"><![CDATA[Match]]></item>
    <item name="button_tas_stats"><![CDATA[Performance]]></item>
    <item name="button_tas_rewards"><![CDATA[Rewards]]></item>
    <item name="label_TAS_Season"><![CDATA[Season]]></item>
    <item name="label_TAS_Rank"><![CDATA[Rank]]></item>
    <item name="label_TAS_Rewards"><![CDATA[Rewards]]></item>
    <item name="label_traininggrounds_rank"><![CDATA[Rank: %AMOUNT%]]></item>
    <item name="label_traininggrounds_score"><![CDATA[Score: %AMOUNT%]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_tas_end_warning_less_1_hour"><![CDATA[Arena Season ends in: 1 hour]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_tas_end_warning_less_5_mins"><![CDATA[Arena Season ends in: 5 minutes]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_tas_end_warning_on_login"><![CDATA[Arena Season ends in: %MINS% minutes!]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_tas_end_of_season"><![CDATA[Arena Season has ended]]></item>
    <item name="label_traininggrounds_no_season"><![CDATA[No Season currently running]]></item>
    <item name="label_TAS_no_season_ranking"><![CDATA[There is no Season running, and therefore no medals to win]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_gather_jump-cpu_p"><![CDATA[You have received a Jump CPU 1]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_hintwindow_title_proActionBar"><![CDATA[Pro action bar]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_hintwindow_message_proActionBar"><![CDATA[The pro action bar gives you a quick access to those items that you don't use frequently enough to have them in the main action bar but to which you want to have a quick access to them in case of need. You can open and close it using SHIFT button, it also closes automatically once you have selected the item you needed. Of course you can set up it's look and position from the config mode in the game settings. While the pro bar is open the shortcuts keys you regularly use only affect this bar, so that by pressing SHIFT and then 1 you will trigger the item you had in that slot.]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_hintwindow_title_assembly"><![CDATA[Assembly]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_hintwindow_message_assembly"><![CDATA[Choose any item from the list and click the Assemble button once you have all the necessary components and collectibles!]]></item>
    <item name="setting_pro_action_bar_enabled"><![CDATA[Display pro action bar]]></item>
    <item name="pro_action_bar_keyboard_input_enabled"><![CDATA[Use key bindings for pro action bar]]></item>
    <item name="setting_auto_hide_pro_action_bar_enabled"><![CDATA[Auto hide pro action bar]]></item>
    <item name="keyboard_action_show_pro_action_bar"><![CDATA[Show/Hide Pro Action Bar]]></item>
    <item name="streuner_gate_narrative_map1"><![CDATA[Attention all Streuner in or near the Kuiper Belt! We are under attack! This is not a drill. Prepare defensive measures at once: Code 1701 Delta!]]></item>
    <item name="streuner_gate_narrative_map2"><![CDATA[Stranger, I don't know who you are - but let's talk civilly, human to human. ...What, has fear struck you dumb? Don't be too hard on yourself: my soldiers Shock and Awe often have that effect!]]></item>
    <item name="streuner_gate_narrative_map3"><![CDATA[What exactly are you trying to prove, here? Are you after fame? Credits? I warn you, if you keep coming - we Streuners stick together! And we'll unite against any invaders!]]></item>
    <item name="streuner_gate_narrative_map4"><![CDATA[See these turrets? You might recognize their design... Donations from our highly esteemed patrons! And after all, we Streuners can't look gift allies in the mouth.]]></item>
    <item name="streuner_gate_narrative_map5_1"><![CDATA[This is your last warning. Reverse course, or face the consequences. This is our home, and we'll defend it to the very last Streuner!]]></item>
    <item name="emperor_streuner_speech_streuner_gate"><![CDATA[Emperor Erreet Falard to unidentified ship: you are out of warnings. Streuners, to me! I'll take care of this corporate lapdog personally.]]></item>
    <item name="emperor_sibelon_speech_streuner_gate"><![CDATA[That idiot Erreet's fleet is coming apart. Streuners can be useful if they're properly armed, but I suppose breeding tells: sooner or later, human filth is still human filth. <br/>What? You dare attack me?! Then come and get it, vermin!]]></item>
    <item name="log_msg_gg_completed_streuner"><![CDATA[Kuiper Galaxy Gate successfully completed.]]></item>
    <item name="label_traininggrounds_general_description"><![CDATA[Play a quick 1 vs. 1 duel against a random opponent.<br />Once the duel is complete, you will be returned to the map you were on, with your HP and shield refilled.<br />A tip: if you lose the duel, you will not lose any of your drones or resources. Nanohull and Ore update won´t be available during UBA matches.]]></item>
    <item name="title_assembly"><![CDATA[Assembly]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_button_ready"><![CDATA[Assemble]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_button_collect"><![CDATA[Collect]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_build_not_possible_unique_max"><![CDATA[Assembly unavailable: you already own the maximum amount of the selected item(s).]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_item_tooltip_shop"><![CDATA[Get any missing parts now!]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_build_unavailable"><![CDATA[You have no items available to be assembled at the moment. The Assembly allows you to combine raw materials and collectibles to produce free ships, equipment, and items!]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_build_crafting_item"><![CDATA[Assembling %item%. Please stand by.]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_recipe_available_time"><![CDATA[Assembly complete in: %time%]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_new_items"><![CDATA[A new item is available at the Assembly: %item%]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_refund"><![CDATA[You already own the following: %item%. The following resources and collectibles have been refunded:]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_label_collect"><![CDATA[Assembled %item%]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_recipe_not_recurrent"><![CDATA[Single-use blueprint consumed.]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_no_items_for_filter"><![CDATA[No items found under the selected filter.]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_label_filter"><![CDATA[Filter]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_recipe_ready_to_collect"><![CDATA[Assembly of %recipename% is now complete.]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_item_collected"><![CDATA[%itemname% retrieved from the Assembly.]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_item_deduction"><![CDATA[The following items and/or collectibles were consumed to assemble %recipename%:]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_item_deducted"><![CDATA[%count% %lootId%(s) were consumed.]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_recipe_collected"><![CDATA[Collected the %recipename% and received the following item(s):]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_recipe_disabled"><![CDATA[%recipename% is no longer available to be assembled. Your resources and collectibles have been refunded.]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_no_item_for_filter"><![CDATA[No items found under the selected filter.]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_recipe_build_process_started"><![CDATA[%recipename% assembly is now under way.]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_build_not_possible_already_used"><![CDATA[This blueprint can only be used once.]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_motivational_survey_reward_booked"><![CDATA[Thank you for taking part in the survey. You've just received your gift of 250 Extra Energy.]]></item>
    <item name="settings_pixelationMode"><![CDATA[Turn Game into retro mode]]></item>
    <item name="assembly_item_timer_ttip"><![CDATA[Time left for this offer]]></item>
    <item name="desc_shipwarp_only_favourite_ships_info"><![CDATA[You can only Warp ships that are marked as your favorites!]]></item>
    <item name="log_message_assembly_pet_rename_compensation"><![CDATA[For renaming your P.E.T.:]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_poison_pusat_design"><![CDATA[Poison Pusat design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_poison_spectrum_design"><![CDATA[Poison Spectrum design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_poison_pusat_drone_design"><![CDATA[Poison Pusat drone design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_poison_spectrum_drone_design"><![CDATA[Poison Spectrum drone design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_a_elite_poison"><![CDATA[Poison A-Elite design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_a_elite_poison_drone"><![CDATA[Poison A-Elite drone design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_a_elite_poison_pet"><![CDATA[Poison A-Elite P.E.T design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_a_elite_legend"><![CDATA[Legend A-Elite design]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_blueprint_box_legend_spectrum_design"><![CDATA[Legend Spectrum Blueprint]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_description_opening_line"><![CDATA[Awesome gear on offer!]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_description_closing_line"><![CDATA[Only available now!]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_pvp_death_title"><![CDATA[Time to get revenge, pilot!]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_pve_death_title"><![CDATA[Damn those alien hordes!]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_pvp_kill_title"><![CDATA[Tactically astute enemy kill!]]></item>
    <item name="targeted_offer_galaxygate_completed_title"><![CDATA[Mankind loves a true hero.]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_registration"><![CDATA[Registration]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_leave"><![CDATA[EXIT]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_on_r_zone"><![CDATA[Leaving Refractions.]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_hint_bottom"><![CDATA[You cannot enter Refractions when in combat!]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_jump"><![CDATA[JUMP NOW!]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_on_r_zone_help"><![CDATA[It takes a short time for your nav-computer to plot your exit from Refractions.]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_confirmation"><![CDATA[Confirmation]]></item>
    <item name="title_rzone_ui"><![CDATA[Refractions]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_time_in_queue"><![CDATA[You've been waiting for:]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_register"><![CDATA[QUEUE NOW!]]></item>
    <item name="httip_rzone"><![CDATA[Refractions]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_cancel"><![CDATA[CANCEL]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_registration_unavailable"><![CDATA[REFRACTION TEMPORARILY CLOSED FOR CLEANING: our minesweeper trawlers are disposing of wreckage and debris. The Refraction will re-open for duels shortly!]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_queueing"><![CDATA[Enter Refractions]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_confirmation_help"><![CDATA[We've reserved your spot for the next jump to Refractions.]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_closing_help"><![CDATA[Refractions is unstable. Wait for it to stabilize or leave!]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_closing_time"><![CDATA[Refractions will close in:]]></item>
    <item name="rzone_registration_help"><![CDATA[Your nav-computer needs to connect to Refractions to plot your course there.]]></item>
    <item name="window_assembly_explanation_windowtitle"><![CDATA[Permafrost Fissure Assemblies]]></item>
    <item name="window_assembly_explanation_header"><![CDATA[This is how it works!]]></item>
    <item name="window_assembly_explanation_description"><![CDATA[Gather valuable Proxium from the Permafrost Fissure using the Subglacial CPU and create the other exotic elements to get hold of an Unstable LF-4. Burn a new hole in the galaxy!]]></item>
    <item name="window_assembly_explanation_iteminfo"><![CDATA[Damage from a minimum of 128 to a maximum of 220.]]></item>
    <item name="reward_booster_hours"><![CDATA[Your Proxium Doubler Booster expires in %HOURS% hours.]]></item>
    <item name="reward_booster_minutes"><![CDATA[Your Proxium Doubler Booster expires in %MINUTES% minutes.]]></item>
    <item name="dropchance_booster_hours"><![CDATA[Your Proxium Drop Booster expires in %HOURS% hours.]]></item>
    <item name="dropchance_booster_minutes"><![CDATA[Your Proxium Drop Booster expires in %MINUTES% minutes.]]></item>
    <item name="boosterName_30"><![CDATA[Equipment booster]]></item>
    <item name="tab_questwin_weekly_missions"><![CDATA[Weekly Missions]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_questwin_weekly_mission_exclude_explanation"><![CDATA[Accept Mission]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_questwin_icon_daily1"><![CDATA[Easy]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_questwin_icon_daily2"><![CDATA[Medium]]></item>
    <item name="ttip_questwin_icon_daily3"><![CDATA[Hard]]></item>
</resource>
