<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resource>&lt;strong&gt;You've fought valiantly, pilot!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now sit back, relax, and gather your strength.&lt;br /&gt; We've got just the thing: a&lt;strong&gt; Happy Hour, from now until the next time the minute hand stands at 12!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOGO uridium - 2 for 1&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt; get twice the uridium for the regular price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; (using any payment option except a bank transfer)!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get your hands on &lt;/strong&gt; 60,000 Uridium instead of just &lt;strong&gt;30,000 Uridium&lt;/strong&gt;, for example!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blast off into the next battle fully charged!&lt;strong&gt;It's time for action!&lt;/strong&gt;The countdown's begun! For the next full hour, we're rolling out the big guns:&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;ul style="margin-left: 20px;"&gt;
    &lt;li style="list-style-type:disc"&gt;Two for the price of one&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style="list-style-type:disc"&gt;60,000 Uridium now for the price of 30,000&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style="list-style-type:disc"&gt;Valid for all payment methods except for bank transfers     &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reel in double the Uridium now!&lt;/strong&gt;GET THE &lt;strong&gt;TRIPLE&lt;/strong&gt; AMOUNT OF URIDIUM NOW!SAVE NOWOffer not valid if paying by bank transfer&lt;strong&gt;Prepare for battle!&lt;/strong&gt;The Mega Happy Hour in all its glory has begun. For the next full hour, stake your claim of the Uridium:&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightYellow"&gt;     &lt;ul style="margin-left: 20px;"&gt;
    &lt;li style="list-style-type:disc"&gt;Snag massive amounts of Uridium: 3 for 1&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style="list-style-type:disc"&gt;Bank 90,000 Uridium instead of 30,000&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li style="list-style-type:disc"&gt;Pay with any payment method except by bank transfer&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/span&gt;HELIX PRICE HACKHELIX CYBER-ATTACK!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;UNTIL COMPANY SECURITY REBOOTS IN %TIMELEFT%, YOU CAN GET %DISCOUNT% URIDIUM FOR THE USUAL PRICE!YOINK!&lt;strong&gt;Upgrading Bonus Hour&lt;/strong&gt;Save big by upgrading now!Available only within the hour: &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;25% discount&lt;/span&gt; when upgrading. With every upgrade-attempt that you start within the hour, you save 25%!&lt;strong&gt;Act now and upgrade for a discounted rate!&lt;/strong&gt;Remaining time:&lt;strong&gt;You've fought bravely so far!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So why don't you chill out and save up your energy?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It's Happy Hour - from now until the next full hour.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Order Uridium and get 2 for 1: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twice the Uridium for the same price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(for all payment methods)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;e.g. &lt;/strong&gt; get an awesome &lt;strong&gt;60,000 Uridium&lt;/strong&gt;instead of just 30,000&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enter the next battle fully charged!Users from all over the world either play on their own national server in their own native tongue or on the global server in many different languages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;At the very beginning, you'll be assigned to a server &lt;font color="#FFFFFF"&gt;in your own native language.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can click on another &lt;font color="#FFFFFF"&gt; PLAY&lt;/font&gt; button, if you wish to use a different server in another language.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;font color="#FFFFFF"&gt;Please remember &lt;/font&gt; that the recommended server will always have the best connection.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color="#FFFFFF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please select a server:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;StartHomeHangarTradeLabSkylabClanUridiumMissionsHelpLogoutForumSupportShopMailProfileGalaxy gatesSupportUser ID: EP: Level:Jackpot: Credits: Uridium:Users onlineGALAXY GATESSKILL TREEPILOT BIOOVERVIEWOverviewOverviewOVERVIEWEQUIPMENTEquipmentEquipmentEQUIPMENTSHIPSShipsShipsSHIPSWEAPONSWeaponsWeaponsWEAPONSAMMOAmmoAmmoAMMOGENERATORSGeneratorsGeneratorsGENERATORSEXTRASExtrasExtrasEXTRASDRONESDronesDronesDRONESBOOSTERSBoostersBoostersBOOSTERSDESIGNSDesignsDesignsDESIGNSCUSTOMIZATIONCustomizationCustomizationCUSTOMIZATIONAUCTIONSAuctionsAuctionsAUCTIONSCOMPLETEDCompletedCompletedCOMPLETEDREFININGRefiningRefiningREFININGUPGRADEUpgradeUpgradeUPGRADEAUTOMATIC REFININGAutomatic refiningAutomatic refiningAUTOMATIC REFININGBANKINGBankingBankingBANKINGBALANCEBalanceBalanceBALANCEEXCHANGEExchange Uridium for CreditsExchangeEXCHANGEURIDIUM PLUSUridium Plus PackUridium PlusURIDIUM PLUSSUBSCRIPTIONSManage subscriptionsSubscriptionsSUBSCRIPTIONSLOTTERYLotteryLotteryLOTTERYPepsiPEPSIGutscheinVOUCHERSVOUCHERSPlease enter your voucher code here to redeem it:Voucher codeVOUCHER CODEThe code has the following pattern: %MUSTER% RedeemRedeem the voucher code that has been entered.Error: %FEHLER% Code successfully redeemed.LogbookThe items you have received with your voucher code can be found in the logbook.Enter voucher code hereVoucher code redeemedYou received %AMOUNT% UridiumYou received %AMOUNT% CreditsYou received %AMOUNT% CreditMardi Gras eVoucher code redeemedRedeemed Razer voucher code:&lt;br /&gt;1 x Nostromo&lt;br /&gt;1 x Goliath Design "Razer-G"&lt;br /&gt;1 x Nostromo Design "Razer-N"&lt;br /&gt;9000 x UCB-100&lt;br /&gt;500 x PLT-2021&lt;br /&gt;100 x Razer Fireworks&lt;br /&gt;1 x Damage BoosterCongratulations!The following items have been booked to your account: %ITEMLIST%&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Please check your inventory!Your items have been booked.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Please check your inventory!The voucher code you have entered is not valid.This voucher code has already been redeemed.&lt;span class="eVoucher_success fliess11px-green"&gt;Voucher successfully redeemed!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;span class="eVoucher_success_payment fliess11px-gelb"&gt;Click here to take advantage of your benefits!&lt;/span&gt;The UBA expo has gifted you a free hangar slot.PREMIUM DEALPremium DealJOINJoinJoinJOINFOUNDFoundFoundFOUNDINFORMATIONInformationInformationINFORMATIONMEMBERSMembersMembersMEMBERSADMINISTRATIONAdministrationAdministrationADMINISTRATIONMESSAGESMessagesMessagesMESSAGESDIPLOMACYDiplomacyDiplomacyDIPLOMACYBattle StationBattle StationBattle StationBATTLE STATIONCOMPANYCompanyCompanyCOMPANYJOBSJobsJobsJOBSSTORYStoryStorySTORYCHALLENGESChallengesChallengesCHALLENGESSKYLABSkylabSkylabSKYLABTECH CENTERTech CenterTech CenterTECH CENTERITEM UPGRADINGItem upgradingEVENTEventEventEVENTSG3Summer Games 3SG3SG3SPECIALSSpecialsSpecialsSPECIALSWINTER GAMESWINTER GAMES 2009Winter Games 2009WG09WINTER GAMES 2009SUMMER GAMESSUMMER GAMES 2010Summer Games 2010SG10SUMMER GAMES 2010LocationLanguageServerStatusPlayRecommendedError messageCLOSE&lt;br /&gt;Once a month you have the chance to win up to £10,000. The player who wins the Jackpot battle receives all the Jackpot pounds they collected from bonus boxes - paid out in cold, hard cash.&lt;strong&gt;DarkOrbit will keep you coming back for more!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Explore the infinite expanses of outer space in one of the best browser-based, action-packed space shooters ever made. Fly into the face of danger and go where nobody has ever gone before - either on your own or with others. Set a course to discover new galaxies and new lifeforms.&lt;br /&gt;Join one of the three DarkOrbit companies in their struggle to gain control over the universe. Gear up for battle and fight to the bitter end to gain wealth and power in this browser game.&lt;br /&gt;Stock up your ship and transform it from a simple Starjet to the universe's most feared battlecruiser: Fulfill your destiny!© Bigpoint - All rights reservedFree online games - Win €10,000Legal informationCreditsDarkOrbitThe action-packed Space MMO for your browserProducerProject ManagerGame DesignDevelopmentGraphicsQuality AssuranceCommunity ManagementInternsSpecial thanks toMore information about DarkOrbitTerms &amp; ConditionsGamesNow online:Registered:LOGINForgot your password?Username:Password:RegisterLanguage:ScreenshotsDetailsTrailerPrizesIn-game videoInfoDarkOrbit – The best browser-based space shooter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Play now against thousands of real players&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lots of action and fun&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No download or installation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Win up to £10,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;DarkOrbit – The best browser-based space shooter&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Play now against thousands of real players!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DarkOrbit is an action-packed space adventure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Browser games: no download, no installation!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;The free massively multiplayer online space gameDarkOrbit is a top multiplayer online game and one of the best games that browser games have to offer. If you're a fan of action games, then you're really going to love DarkOrbit: Your mission here is to hunt enemies in outer space and shoot them down on behalf of your company. The universe is brimming with thousands of real opponents for you to compete against! DarkOrbit isn't just any ordinary online game: It's a truly irresistible online game for fans of space games!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of real players fight to the bitter end in this multiplayer online game which can be played right in your browser. That's why online games such as DarkOrbit are often called browser games: They are Internet games with substance and a whole lot of action.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space games with the same caliber as DarkOrbit are revolutionizing the world of browser games. Navigate your spaceship from the bridge in action-packed space battles with your mouse or keyboard. Join alliances: Browser games make it possible for you to play with and against thousands of real players in real time.Other terms from the browser game DarkOrbit:Online games – more than %s million people play DarkOrbit!DarkOrbit - the great online space game from ScifiJoin millions of other star pilots to battle alien and player spaceships. DarkOrbit – The popular scifi MMO Browser Game where adventure is at the heart of the action.Browser games, DarkOrbit, Space shooter games, Games, Free, Online games, Action game, ShooterStarter Pack 1Starter Pack 2Starter PackSavings Pack 1Savings Pack 2Savings Pack 3Savings Pack 4Savings PackReactivation bonusLaser Starter PackGenerator Starter PackBattery Starter PackRocket Starter PackOre Starter PackShip Starter PackLaser Savings PackGenerator Savings PackBattery Savings PackRocket Savings PackMine Savings PackOre Savings PackShip Savings PackChallenger Savings Pack purchased Elite Savings Pack purchased Pro Savings Pack purchasedVengeance Starter Kit purchasedGoliath Starter Kit purchasedLeonov Starter Kit purchasedDaredevil Paket purchasedHigh-Flyer Paket purchasedSpace Rogue Paket purchasedAlien Fighter Paket purchasedMaintenance Paket purchasedBattle Enhancement purchasedSurvivor's Strongbox purchasedExtra Energy Mega Discount purchasedExtra Energy Mega Discount L purchasedExtra Energy Mega Discount XL purchasedBooty Key Mega Discount purchasedBooty Key Mega Discount L purchasedBooty Key Mega Discount XL purchasedParasite Pack purchasedAnti Poison Pack purchasedPoison Pack purchasedDeluxe Pack purchasedAscension Booster Pack purchasedAscension Pro Booster Pack purchasedAscension Deluxe Booster Pack purchasedPoison A-Elite Set purchasedPoison A-Elite Drone Design purchasedPoison A-Elite P.E.T. Design purchasedPoison A-Elite Design purchasedReady for Action purchasedFrozen Mirage purchasedPromethean Honor purchasedSpectrum Chroma purchasedPusat Chroma purchasedPhantom Chimera purchased10 Prometheus Fragments30 Prometheus Fragments300 Prometheus FragmentsSaimon&lt;br /&gt;killDevolarium&lt;br /&gt;damageMordon&lt;br /&gt;killSibelon&lt;br /&gt;damageSpace&lt;br /&gt;marathonStreuner&lt;br /&gt;killProtegite&lt;br /&gt;killLordakium&lt;br /&gt;damageVariety&lt;br /&gt;killLordakia/&lt;br /&gt;Saimon killLordakium/&lt;br /&gt;Sibelon damageVariety&lt;br /&gt;killVariety&lt;br /&gt;kill/damage&lt;strong&gt;Saimon kill day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In today's event your mission is to destroy as many &lt;strong&gt;Saimon&lt;/strong&gt; ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;Every &lt;strong&gt;ship destroyed&lt;/strong&gt; is worth 10 points. You can also receive up to 10 bonus points depending on the type of your ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-3 and X-4 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Devolarium damage day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your mission in today's event is to cause as much damage to &lt;strong&gt;Devolarium&lt;/strong&gt; ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;Every &lt;strong&gt;damage point&lt;/strong&gt; shot is worth 1 point. You can also receive up to a 100% bonus depending on your type of ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-3 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Mordon kill day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your assignment in today's event is to destroy as many &lt;strong&gt;Mordon&lt;/strong&gt; ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;Every &lt;strong&gt;ship destroyed&lt;/strong&gt; is worth 10 points. You can also receive up to 10 bonus points depending on the type of your ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-3 and X-4 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Sibelon damage day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your mission in today's event is to cause as much damage to &lt;strong&gt;Sibelon&lt;/strong&gt; ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;Every &lt;strong&gt;damage point&lt;/strong&gt; shot is worth 1 point. You can also receive up to a 100% bonus depending on your type of ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-4 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Space marathon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your assignment in today's event is to fly back and forth between the two home bases as often as possible.&lt;br /&gt;You'll receive &lt;strong&gt;10 points&lt;/strong&gt; for every round trip you make.&lt;br /&gt;You can also receive up to 10 bonus points depending on the type of your ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll find these bases on the X-1 and X-8 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Streuner kill day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's up to you in today's event to destroy as many Streuner ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;Every ship shot down is worth 10 points. You can also receive up to 10 bonus points depending on the type of your ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-1, X-2, X-8 maps (Streuner).&lt;strong&gt;Protegite kill day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your assignment in today's event is to destroy as many Protegite ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;Every ship shot down is worth 10 points. You can also receive up to 10 bonus points depending on the type of your ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-6 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Lordakium damage day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your mission in today's event is to cause as much damage to Lordakium ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;For every shot which causes damage you'll receive one point. You can also receive up to a 100% bonus depending on your type of ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-5 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Variety kill day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's up to you today to &lt;strong&gt;destroy&lt;/strong&gt; as many ships as possible.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All NPCs&lt;/strong&gt; count. Every ship destroyed is worth &lt;strong&gt;10 points&lt;/strong&gt;. You can also receive up to &lt;strong&gt;10 bonus points&lt;/strong&gt; depending on your type of ship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The goal here is to shoot down as many opponents as possible!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For every additional type of opponent's ship destroyed, the multiplier increases by a factor of 1. If you destroy another opponent of this type, the multiplier will be reset to 1 and the multiplying process starts over again. Always make sure that you shoot down each type of opponent only once.&lt;strong&gt;Lordakia/Saimon kill day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your mission in today's event is to shoot down as many &lt;strong&gt;Lordakia and Saimon&lt;/strong&gt; ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;Every ship destroyed is worth &lt;strong&gt;10 points&lt;/strong&gt;. You can also receive up to &lt;strong&gt;10 bonus points&lt;/strong&gt; depending on your type of ship. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-2, X-3, X-4 and X-5 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Lordakium/Sibelon damage day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your assignment in today's event is to cause as much damage to &lt;strong&gt;Lordakium and Sibelon&lt;/strong&gt; ships as possible.&lt;br /&gt;For every shot which causes damage you'll receive &lt;strong&gt;1 point&lt;/strong&gt;. You can also receive up to a &lt;strong&gt;100% bonus&lt;/strong&gt; depending on your ship type. The competition ends at midnight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ships can be found on the X-4 and X-5 maps.&lt;strong&gt;Variety Kill Day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's up to you today to &lt;strong&gt;destroy&lt;/strong&gt; as many ships as possible.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All &lt;strong&gt;NPCs and real players&lt;/strong&gt; count. Every ship destroyed is worth &lt;strong&gt;10 points&lt;/strong&gt;. You can also receive up to &lt;strong&gt;10 bonus points&lt;/strong&gt; depending on your type of ship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This score will be multiplied by the &lt;strong&gt;number of opponent types&lt;/strong&gt; to calculate the &lt;strong&gt;total score&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For every additional type of opponent's ship destroyed, the multiplier increases by a factor of 1. If you destroy another opponent of this type, the multiplier will be reset to 1 and the multiplying process will start over again.&lt;strong&gt;Variety Kill and Damage Day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In today's event, you need to &lt;strong&gt;destroy&lt;/strong&gt; as many ships and &lt;strong&gt;achieve&lt;/strong&gt; as many &lt;strong&gt;hit points&lt;/strong&gt; as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All NPCs and real players&lt;/strong&gt; count. Every ship shot down is worth &lt;strong&gt;40,000 points&lt;/strong&gt;. Depending on your type of ship, you can also receive up to &lt;strong&gt;40,000 bonus points&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition, for every shot which causes damage you'll receive &lt;strong&gt;1 point&lt;/strong&gt;. Depending on the type of ship, you can receive up to a &lt;strong&gt;100% bonus&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This score will be multiplied by the &lt;strong&gt;number of opponent types&lt;/strong&gt; to calculate the &lt;strong&gt;total score&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For every additional type of opponent's ship destroyed, the multiplier increases by a factor of 1. If you destroy another opponent of this type, the multiplier will be reset to 1 and the multiplying process will start over again.Today:Yesterday:Overall 1st Place:A-BC-DE-FG-HI-KL-MN-OP-QR-ST-VW-XY-Z0-!Message was sent to Support ...Checking message ...This clan name is not allowed!This clan tag is not allowed!Incoming messageDon't show again Incoming message%s min. leftmaximumDo you really want to buy this item?PaymentYou forgot to log out last time. Please use the logout button every time you leave DarkOrbit.Always use the logout button to leave the space map. This ensures that your ship is logged out correctly.Welcome to DarkOrbit!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start your engines: Lots of adventure and fun await you here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Important: You're currently playing with a &lt;b&gt;guest account&lt;/b&gt; which doesn't require you to &lt;b&gt;register&lt;/b&gt; for the game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So that you can hold onto your current winnings, you must register &lt;a href="indexInternal.es?action=internalFinishGuestSignUp"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Your game status will be saved and you can pick up where you left off the next time you log in.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note: You'll need to complete registration for a free account if you wish to continue playing after level 2.&lt;span class="guestBold"&gt;Welcome to DarkOrbit!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start your engines: Lots of adventure and fun await you here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IMPORTANT: You're currently playing with a guest account which &lt;span class="guestBold"&gt;doesn't require you to register for the game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="guestBold2"&gt;You're now leaving your guest account!&lt;/span&gt;So that you don't lose your current level of success, register right here and now.So that you don't lose your current level of success, register right here and now:Your current game status will be saved and the next time you log in, you can start playing where you left off. Your current game status will be saved and the next time you log in, you can start playing where you left off.Play for freeRegister now for freeTake DarkOrbit for a test drive with a guest account: Click here to start playing now.Use the guest account and get into the game.Note: You'll need to complete registration for a free account if you wish to continue playing after level 2.Note: You'll need to complete registration for a free account if you wish to continue playing after level 2.Play in guest accountContinue to play in the guest accountAn error occurred, please refresh the page. If the error continues to occur, please contact Support.Unable to equip. Fly back to your space station first.Equipping not possible. You must be at a location with a Hangar facility.You cannot equip that now, because you are either or both: &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not close enough to a Station with a Hangar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Waiting for a duel in the Ultimate Battle Arena&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;Switching Hangars is not possible, because you are either or both:&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Too far from a Station with a Hangar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Waiting for a duel in the Ultimate Battle Arena&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;Repairs not available! The Module has been installed in a Battle Station.You may not sell anything until you are logged out of the client.Add DarkOrbit to your browser favorites, so that next time you can start playing in just a few clicks.Click here and add DarkOrbit to your favorites.CloseCLOSETDMTeam DeathmatchDateTime%MM%.%DD%.%YYYY% %HH%:%mm%PositionPos.UserCompanyGamesGames playedplayedWonLostPointsLongest winning streakHighest simultaneous number of gamesMy gamesGame reportGame reports%COMPANY1% versus %COMPANY2%Final score%PLAYER% destroyed%PLAYER% survivedWinner:Loser:DrawTDM - Overall Company RankingTDM - Overall User RankingTDM - Daily User RankingSmall "4th of July" fireworksMedium "4th of July" fireworksLarge "4th of July" fireworksSmall fireworksMedium fireworksLarge fireworksUserCompanyClanNew here? Try out DarkOrbit!Choose a name for yourself and try out DarkOrbit!Already registered?To the LoginTo the RegistrationBackOpen ID URL:BuyYou are a %RANK%. Your rank is calculated as follows:You need approx. %RANKPOINTS_ABOVE% rank points to reach the next rank of %RANK_ABOVE%.The rank directly below yours is that of %RANK_BELOW%. Space pilots with this rank have approx. %RANKPOINTS_BELOW% rank points.You currently have the highest rank in your company.You currently have the lowest rank.You're the administrator and that's why you don't have a rank.&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; The rank is only calculated once a day. The figures listed here are only meant as a rough estimate. There is no guarantee that you'll automatically change ranks if you've reached a certain number of points, since the values of the other players are also constantly changing.Greetings &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_USERNAME%&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Your current position in the ranking is &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_POSITION%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You have &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_EP%&lt;/strong&gt; experience points and &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_HONOURPOINTS%&lt;/strong&gt; honor points.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Your current level is &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_LEVEL%&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You destroyed &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_DESTROYED_SHIPS%&lt;/strong&gt; spaceships and &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_DESTROYED_ALIENS%&lt;/strong&gt; aliens.Your clan &lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_YOUR_CLAN% [%PRIVATE_YOUR_CLANTAG%]&lt;/strong&gt; is ranked #&lt;strong&gt;%PRIVATE_YOUR_CLAN_RANK%&lt;/strong&gt; in the clan ranking.You're not a member of a clan.&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you really want to switch companies?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;         &lt;br /&gt;         &lt;p class="popup_changeFaction_faction"&gt;&lt;strong id="factionName"&gt;Company name&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;p&gt;In order for your company to let you go peacefully, you have to pay 5,000 Uridium. Since you're switching to a rival company, the new company will only recognize half of your current honor points - negative honor points will remain the same.&lt;/p&gt;RankingMembersEPHonorShips destroyedAliens destroyed&lt;p&gt;Switch company&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Select which company you want to switch to from the other two companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cost: %PRICE_FOR_CHANGE% Uridium&lt;/p&gt;New to the MMO?New to the EIC?New to the VRU?Then get yourself the perfect rookie ship: the LEONOV!&lt;br&gt;It'll let you get ahead on your home map.The ship with the home advantageGet the rookie ship!StandardComprises all maps except the home maps.Home mapsComprises maps %COMPANY_ID%-1 to %COMPANY_ID%-4Maps %COMPANY_ID%-1 to %COMPANY_ID%-4With home advantage ** The home advantage is only valid for the maps %COMPANY_ID%-1 to %COMPANY_ID%-4 since they are within the energy supply area of your home base.Today:Daily ranking:Ranking:Top 3:Top 10:Top 100:EventEventsDaily eventSummer GamesSummer Games 3Summer Games awardSummer Game ChampionshipsChampionship rankingChampionship pointsSG3 Championship rankingSG3 daily rankingSG3 daily rankingsSG3SUMMER GAMES 3Greetings Space Pilot!&lt;br&gt; It's time to kick off the third round of the DarkOrbit Summer Games.&lt;br&gt; Hop in your cockpit, become the SG3 Champion and rake in the rewards!&lt;strong&gt;DarkOrbit Summer Games 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; The time has finally come: The DarkOrbit Summer Games have officially opened!&lt;br&gt; Gear up for action, fun and adventure in the battle for highly coveted medals and the title of the &lt;strong&gt;Summer Games Champion&lt;/strong&gt;. Be there when the games begin: Fight either alone or with your company for &lt;strong&gt;honor, glory and a whole bunch of wicked prizes&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt; There will be a new event each day for you to compete in and test your skills against the galaxy's best space pilots to see who can take home the prize.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; - Your account will be credited with points for every daily event.&lt;br&gt; - Your 10 best results from the daily events will determine your overall standing in the Summer Game Championships.&lt;br&gt; - The player who has collected the most Championship points by the end of the Summer Games will take home the main prize: an entire month's subscription to an &lt;strong&gt;indestructible #9 drone&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Pilots ranked in &lt;strong&gt;positions 2 to 100&lt;/strong&gt; will also receive &lt;strong&gt;great prizes&lt;/strong&gt; for their outstanding performances.&lt;br&gt; Don't miss out on the action - fight for your spot in the &lt;strong&gt;event of the summer&lt;/strong&gt;: the &lt;strong&gt;DarkOrbit Summer Games 3&lt;/strong&gt;.SBSBPlease turn off your pop-up blocker!AmountNo Credits or Uridium left? No problem!&lt;br /&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt; to get more.Don't show again.Buy nowBuy now&lt;strong&gt;The Delta Gate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; With a little bit of blood, sweat and tears, our space pilots were able to recover pieces of an ancient device from existing gates in outer space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The advancements made exploring the Alpha, Beta and Gamma maps is finally paying off: A new generator was developed which only produces parts for the Delta gate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The Delta gate leads into the legendary Delta galaxy where not one single member of the three companies has ever been able to penetrate thus far. Nobody knows what exists there! Be the first brave soul to enter this brand new world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; You can find the Delta gate under "Galaxy gates" – you can't miss it!Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An invasion is headed your way! And it just couldn't come at a worse time: On the &lt;b&gt;999th and 1,000th day anniversary of DarkOrbit&lt;/b&gt;! We don't know how the blasted aliens were able to do it, but on each company's home map there is now an &lt;b&gt;Invasion gate&lt;/b&gt; which leads to a separate galaxy where the invasion map is located. Evil invaders from outer space are just lying in wait on this map, ready to descend on your home map!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But this primitive group of aliens made a big mistake: They didn't think it was possible to enter the &lt;b&gt;Invasion map&lt;/b&gt; with a whole armada &lt;b&gt; of space pilots&lt;/b&gt; - but it is!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Those who click on "Jump" first will be among the first to fight! All other pilots will have to wait until one of the fighters from the armada has been shot down and then it will be their turn to move up and take over a position fighting the enemy!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In order to remain in the succession list and attack the alien slime, make sure not to leave your home map, or else you'll have to go to the back of line and wait all over again. Each alien who is destroyed will earn you one point for your company.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All three companies are under threat of attack: The company which destroys the most aliens and therefore gathers the most points &lt;b&gt;from September 5-6, 2009&lt;/b&gt; will be rewarded with a 10% damage bonus for 1 whole week. The companies in 2nd and 3rd place will receive a 5% or 3% damage bonus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to this fight, whoever has enough power left over will also be rewarded with a special excursion to the &lt;b&gt;Anniversary Galaxy Gate&lt;/b&gt;! This gate will be set up close to your home base: The only requirement is that you log into the star chart on September 5th or 6th. The gate will be active for a maximum of one month, until you've accomplished the quest there. &lt;b&gt;It will be closed for good at the latest on October 6, 2009&lt;/b&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During these two days of special quests, space pilots will also find bonus boxes with twice the content and payment multipliers!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Any questions? Please take a look at the attached FAQ.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blast off for battle, space pilots! Make your company proud: They're counting on you!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Company Board of Directors&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;FAQ&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why is there a 999/1,000-day event? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DarkOrbit is turning 999 and 1,000 days old. And to celebrate, a huge anniversary event is being thrown. The DarkOrbit team can't wait to celebrate this memorable occasion with you, and hopes that you'll stick around to see the next big event for 2,000 days of DarkOrbit. As a token of our appreciation, we'd like to thank you for your loyalty and bravery over the years with this especially challenging event!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is the 999/1,000 Gate? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 999/1,000 Gate works exactly the same way as a normal galaxy gate. Every player, regardless of their level or equipment, can access this gate and play. In order to access the gate, all you have to do is fly to it and activate the portal jump. Just remember to equip your ship as much as possible before you enter the gate. Your performance in the 999/1,000 Gate will be recorded in a ranking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What exactly is the Invasion gate?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Invasion gate can only materialize every 1,000 days. Take heed, pilots! The largest threat the universe of DarkOrbit has ever encountered lurks behind this gate. You'll see that one gate has materialized on each of the company's maps, and which can only be accessed by the members of that company. A limited number of company members can use the gate at the same time in order to fight against the extremely hostile alien invaders. If there are already too many users who have passed through this gate, you'll be put in a waiting list if you try to activate the portal jump. As soon as the aliens defeat your fellow combatants and blow them to pieces, then you'll be transported through the gate one by one as reinforcements for your company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;How can my company win the 10% bonus?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The company which has collected the most points on the invasion map by the end of the event will receive a 10% damage bonus for the entire next week. The second- and third-placed companies will be rewarded accordingly with a bonus of 5% (2nd place) and 3% (3rd place) for one whole week.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;What happens if I'm blown to smithereens on the Invasion map?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're destroyed on an Invasion map, you can repair your ship for free and your drones can't be damaged at all there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Space pilots, just remember: Fortune favors the bold with the greatest honor of all. So fight on behalf of your company!&lt;b&gt;Insta-Repair at DarkOrbit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From zero to hero in the blink of an eye: Push the limit at the speed of lightning!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's time for you to stop putting up with guff from others and fight back with the brand-new Insta-Repair which allows you to strike back quickly with a vengeance. Those who cause you damage better beware, because with the Insta-Repair you've got an ace up your sleeve!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is how it works:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whoever has less than their maximum number of hit points may use the Insta-Repair.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can activate it at your home base.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Within a second, you'll be able to repair your ship back to its maximum number of hit points!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Insta-Repair usually costs 10 repair credits … but honestly, it's worth collecting all the repair credits for this item. The moment where you catch your opponent off guard by fighting back at full tilt is all too sweet to resist – the Insta-Repair is the perfect joker for you to take revenge!&lt;b&gt;Breaking news: Make room for something new!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introducing a new feature for you to sell your ammo!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What can you do with your extra ammo? Throwing it away would be a down-right shame, but it's not like you can use it either. So that's why we came up with a solution for you to sell your ammunition for Credits, fill up your account and get your hands on the ammunition you really need!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go to the hangar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Select the menu item &lt;i&gt;Equipment&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click on the ammo and then hit &lt;i&gt;Sell&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The first aid kit for ammo-hoarding pilots: Out with the old and in with the new. Get rid of all that old ammunition, such as rockets, mines, and laser batteries, which is just collecting dust on the shelves. Starting now, there's no need for you to throw your old trash over board; trade them in and earn some cold hard cash!In useBuy nowTech FactoryYou may construct the item in the tech factory.Tech FactoryBuy nowBidPlease waitSpeedRocketsHit pointsLasersRocket launchersCargoExtrasGeneratorsBatteriesDo you really want to buy the &lt;strong&gt;%SHIP_NAME%&lt;/strong&gt; ship for &lt;strong&gt;%SHIP_PRICE%&lt;/strong&gt;?Do you really want to buy the &lt;strong&gt;%MODEL_NAME%&lt;/strong&gt; design for &lt;strong&gt;%MODEL_PRICE%&lt;/strong&gt;?When you buy a new spaceship, the old ship will be scrapped,&lt;br&gt;but you can keep all equipment on board even if you buy a smaller ship.NOTE: Activate purchased designs for your current ship in HANGAR -&gt; EQUIPMENT.DamageShield strengthDo you really want to buy the &lt;strong&gt;%DRONE_NAME%&lt;/strong&gt; drone for &lt;strong&gt;%DRONE_PRICE%&lt;/strong&gt;?Do you really want to buy the &lt;strong&gt;%LASER_NAME%&lt;/strong&gt; laser for &lt;strong&gt;%LASER_PRICE%&lt;/strong&gt;?How many &lt;strong&gt;%WEAPON_NAME%&lt;/strong&gt; rocket launchers do you want to buy for &lt;strong&gt;%WEAPON_PRICE%&lt;/strong&gt;?How much &lt;strong&gt;%BATTERY_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; laser ammo do you want to buy?How many &lt;strong&gt;%ROCKET_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;%WEAPON_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; do you want to buy?How many &lt;strong&gt;%ROCKET_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;rockets&lt;/strong&gt; do you want to buy?How many &lt;strong&gt;%ROCKET_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;mines&lt;/strong&gt; do you want to buy?How many &lt;strong&gt;%ROCKET_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;fireworks&lt;/strong&gt; do you want to buy?How many &lt;strong&gt;%ROCKET_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;units&lt;/strong&gt; do you want to buy?How many &lt;strong&gt;%ROCKET_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;torpedoes&lt;/strong&gt; do you want to buy?How much &lt;strong&gt;%ORE_TYPE%&lt;/strong&gt; ore do you want to buy?Do you really want to buy the &lt;strong&gt;%GENERATOR_NAME%&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;%GENERATOR_PRICE%&lt;/strong&gt;?Do you really want to buy the &lt;strong&gt;%SPECIAL_NAME%&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;%SPECIAL_PRICE%&lt;/strong&gt;?Laser roundsHangar hallPremium1 week of Premium advantagesPremium for 2 weeks1 month of Premium3 months of PremiumShop-Discount %DISCOUNT%%ShipDronesHit pointsMax. hit pointsNanohullMax. NanohullLasersLaser ammoRocketsRepair creditsJump creditsBooty KeysGreen Booty KeysRed Booty KeysBlue Booty KeysSilver Booty KeysSpeed generatorsMax. speedShield generatorsDamage distributionShield/hullDronesDroneFlax/IrisDamagePointsLevelMax. speedDamage distribution(Shield/Hit points)(Flax/Iris)Next levelNextPreviousNext level%VALUE% Credits%VALUE% C.%VALUE% Uridium%VALUE% U.TutorialGreetings Space Pilot,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This here is your launching pad to start exploring the undiscovered galaxies of DarkOrbit. To get off to a flying start, just click on &lt;strong&gt;Start&lt;/strong&gt; and watch this tutorial. Follow the directions described on the screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to leave the tutorial, go to the &lt;strong&gt;Missions&lt;/strong&gt; section and close the tutorial.  You can continue playing it in &lt;strong&gt;Jobs&lt;/strong&gt; at any time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Godspeed, captain!This here is your launching pad to start exploring the undiscovered galaxies of DarkOrbit. To get off to a flying start, just click on &lt;strong&gt;Start&lt;/strong&gt; and watch this tutorial. Follow the directions described on the screen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click on &lt;strong&gt;Cancel&lt;/strong&gt; at the bottom if you wish to stop the tutorial. If you want to continue with the tutorial, just click on &lt;strong&gt;Accept&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Godspeed, captain!&lt;strong&gt;Greetings Space Pilot,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Your DarkOrbit journey will lead you to far-off galaxies fraught with danger and mystery. Your first rule of thumb is not to panic!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; You can always get help here:If you can't find any answers to your questions contact %LINK_SUPPORT_START%Support%LINK_SUPPORT_END%.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Godspeed, captain!Visit our %LINK_FORUM_START%Forum%LINK_FORUM_END%.Answers to the most frequently asked questions can be found in the %LINK_FAQ_START%FAQ%LINK_FAQ_END%.Read the %LINK_HELP_START%Help%LINK_HELP_END%.Upon buying this ship you can trade in your old ship and save &lt;strong&gt;%SCRAPPAGE_BONUS% Uridium&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;h3&gt;DarkOrbit's 3rd Anniversary - Capture the Beacon&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt; Celebrate DarkOrbit's 3rd Anniversary by joining in the fun and playing &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Capture the Beacon&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;! &lt;em&gt;Capture the Beacon&lt;/em&gt; is similar to the popular classic &lt;em&gt;Capture the Flag&lt;/em&gt;, which you may or may not already know from other games. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the rules:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each company has a special zone on the X-2 map. In this zone, there are two &lt;em&gt;beacons&lt;/em&gt;, each belonging to one enemy company, which you need to protect.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;At the same time you must try to retrieve your own beacons from the enemy X-2 maps.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;You'll receive one point as soon as your company brings its own beacon into its own zone and you prevent the enemy teams from capturing their beacons.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The player who has captured a beacon will show up on the mini map and won't have any attack protection during this time. If this player is using his/her cloaking device, it will be deactivated. The current score of a match and the position of the beacons can be seen on the star chart.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Multiple CTB matches will be played throughout the day. The company who wins a CTB match will receive their reward during the next hour. A reward will also be presented at the end of the day to the company who wins the most matches.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Have a blast playing Capture the Beacon. For those of you who don't want to play CTB, we've got some other special surprises planned for you today!&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Kick off the new year with a bang&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yet another year is coming to an end, and to celebrate, DarkOrbit is throwing a huge party with a spectacular display of fireworks!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We went all out this year, getting our hands on every type of firework we could scrounge up:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You'll find three different sizes of fireworks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;They can be bought in the hangar, and also found in small quantities in bonus boxes on the map.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;And the best thing of all is that the fireworks won't take up any room in your armory!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can buy these special explosives from Dec. 28, 2009 to Dec. 31, 2009, but you won't be able to start your "symphony of fire" until Dec. 31, 2009!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Position up to five fireworks wherever you want on the map, and click on the button to detonate!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warning: According to intergalactic space law, each ship can only carry up to 9,999 fireworks on board to minimize the risk of explosion. Any fireworks which you collect above this number will be launched out into space and join the rest of the space debris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We wish you a Happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;/p&gt;%LINK_AGB_START%Terms &amp; Conditions%LINK_AGB_END% and %LINK_HELP_START%Game rules%LINK_HELP_END% read and accepted.Please confirm that you have read and accepted the Terms and Conditions and the game rules.&lt;h2&gt;New DarkOrbit client&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Amazing design, large field of vision, personalized HUD plus much, much more.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jump-start your new year and blast off with us as the brand-new DarkOrbit client goes live on January 20, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the successful client testing of the beta server, we tracked down and removed all bugs we could find. Now that everything's been perfected and fine-tuned, it's time for the new client to make its grand debut by becoming your new panoramic window into outer space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new client has:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;a large field of vision&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;adjustable resolution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;amazing lighting effects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;mind-boggling explosions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;personalized HUD&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;more information on the star chart&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now you'll be able to see all the information you need at one glance. Have a blast with the new client!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the new design, a number of changes were made to the new client, using cutting-edge programming to make the game more responsive. But that's not all we've got planned. We've set our sights on adding more maps, more NPCs and other great features in upcoming game updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're not yet ready to explore the next frontier, you can continue to use the old client until the next big game update is made. Just remember that we won't be able to incorporate the features we have planned for the future into the old client, so you'll have to say good-bye to the old client for good once the next big update is made. Don't worry, as soon as we know when this will happen, we'll make sure to inform you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the year 2010: Seek out alien life in strange, new worlds using state-of-the-art technology!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Test out the brand-new client today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;/p&gt;;Breakthrough in rocket research!After a long development phase and exhaustive testing, the rocket research department is proud to present two groundbreaking new items. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now available at the hangar: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket CPU&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: If you have less than 100 rockets on board, this CPU will automatically buy 500 rockets of the selected rocket type. You'll never run out of rockets again!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;PLT 3030&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: A long-range rocket with impressive firepower. Combine it with the Tech Center's precision targeter to make up for its limited accuracy and enjoy a higher kill ratio than ever before.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both innovations are on sale now at the hangar – don't wait!&lt;br /&gt;Weather on Zula 31During the day:&lt;br /&gt;Blistering cold temperatures with occasional sulfur-laden flurries and a maximum high of approx. -87°. The southerly Zanziwinds will pick up in the afternoon resulting in a drop in temperature.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overnight:&lt;br /&gt;Expect the mercury to plummet, last week's record low is about to be broken. Meteorologists warn of a cold snap and predict -124° weather. Local sulfuric snowstorms with severe electric activity may also occur. Please exercise extreme caution when leaving the atmosphere.Massive meteor impact imminentThe moon known as Gora is about to be hit by a meteor. The last few attempts to divert the path of Ganibar 16 failed. The meteor is about the size of a Class 3 generator, and scientists were unable to destroy this seemingly impervious projectile because of its dense titanium surface. The Polaris system's barely inhabited satellite has been completely evacuated. The scientists were the last inhabitants to abandon their research and leave the surface. Billions of Uridium in damage are expected.Power-packed attackThe DMG-BO1 damage booster catalyzes rocket and laser energy, thereby increasing their damage output by 10%. Ten percent may not seem like a lot, but it might just save your butt! The DMG-BO1 is just one of eight available boosters. It'll serve you faithfully in battle. Give it a whirl today and add some oomph to your attack with the damage booster.The ace up your sleeveQuadroForce's latest development: the SAB 50 shield absorber. A must-have in the daily defense against enemies. It drains energy from your enemy's shields and transfers it to your shield generators. If you find yourself in a sticky situation, the SAB 50 might just save the day. It's your ace up your sleeve!Expand your horizonsUpgrade your ship with up to six additional CPU slots and expand your possibilities. CPUs and other extras make life as a space pilot much easier, but there are only a limited number of slots on each ship. The SL CPU series offers you slot expansions in four different sizes. Expand your horizons today with the SLO3 CPU!Hellstorm season is in full swing!Attention Space Pilots!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rocket launcher was released onto the market only a short while ago, but it's already become standard equipment for every successful fighter pilot. And its popularity continues to soar as new technology is developed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting today, two new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;high-tech rockets&lt;/b&gt; are available for the rocket launcher.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UBR-100&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was designed to inflict massive damage on aliens and is equipped with state-of-the-art warheads which are at least 80% more effective against aliens than conventional HSTRM-01 rockets.*&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ECO-10 rocket&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was designed to be economical, giving you better value for your money.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the perfect rocket for every situation, you can get the most out of your rocket launcher - whether you're taking down aliens with the UBR-100 or saving cash with the ECO-10.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perfect tactics require ... the right rockets!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;* The UBR-100 rocket is only available for a limited time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get it now: More slots for even more possibilities!Not enough slots on board? Get your hands on the power expansion for your ship: The SL04 CPU gives you more slots for more possibilities! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equip your ship with &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;ten additional slots for CPUs and extras&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;The SL CPU series offers &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;slot expansions in four different sizes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The more slots you have on board, the more &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;extras and CPUs&lt;/span&gt; you'll be able to use.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Keep ahead of your competition! More CPUs and extras make your life as a space pilot that much easier. Don't wait - maximize your potential today with the SLO4 CPU.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Skylab's new addition: The Tech Center!Check out the new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tech Center&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the Skylab. Produce new weapons of war and get the one-up on your competition with the new Tech Center!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collect &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;raw materials&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to produce new items. If you don't have all the required materials, just use Uridium instead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use all your new Tech Center CPUs, weapons and items &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;right away.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expand the Tech Center with extra &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;production facilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and produce multiple items simultaneously.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt; From the energy leech to the chain impulse and backup shields: There's something here for every battle situation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Win the arms race: Take down your enemies!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paron-1's rings are shrinkingBased on planet readings and research, scientists have determined that the rings surrounding Paron-1 are shrinking. Dr. Geewicki and his team of experts declared that in the last five years the diameter of the planet's rings has decreased by approx. 144 centimeters. Paron-1's large mass is the likely cause for this drastic change in size. It's not the shrinking rings that pose a great threat to Paron-1, but rather its very dense atmosphere, which protects the planet from meteors.Endurium found on X3-MRFThe PSR expedition team reports that significant supplies of Endurium have been found on a newly discovered asteroid. According to geologists, the minor planet X3-MRF in the Strium 7 solar system holds non-disclosed but considerable amounts of Endurium. Located close to a spiral nebula, it is very difficult to reach. To prevent others from getting their hands on these resources, the PSR has imposed an embargo, cutting off all normal space traffic to the area.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Endurium can often be found in the form of small asteroids floating around in known space. But to make the resource's extraction worthwhile, Endurium must be uncontaminated and abundant. Supplies of such purity and abundance have never before been discovered, and PSR has not yet determined how best to process the ore. The conventional neutron radiators currently equipped on almost every modern vessel are way too small for a job of this magnitude. PSR has not disclosed any further information - only time will tell what is to be made of X3-MRF.New DarkOrbit client&lt;h3&gt;Amazing design, large field of vision, personalized HUD plus much, much more!&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jump-start your new year and blast off with us as the brand-new DarkOrbit client goes live on January 20, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the successful client testing of the beta server, we tracked down and removed all bugs we could find. Now that everything's been perfected and fine-tuned, it's time for the new client to make its grand debut by becoming your new panoramic window into outer space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new client has:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;a large field of vision&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;adjustable resolution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;amazing lighting effects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;mind-boggling explosions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;personalized HUD&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;more information on the star chart&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now you'll be able to see all the information you need at one glance. Have a blast with the new client!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the new design, a number of changes were made to the new client, using cutting-edge programming to make the game more responsive. But that's not all we've got planned. We've set our sights on adding more maps, more NPCs and other great features in upcoming game updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're not yet ready to explore the next frontier, you can continue to use the old client until the next big game update is made. Just remember that we won't be able to incorporate the features we have planned for the future into the old client, so you'll have to say good-bye to the old client for good once the next big update is made. Don't worry, as soon as we know when this will happen, we'll make sure to inform you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the year 2010: Seek out alien life in strange, new worlds using state-of-the-art technology!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Test out the brand-new client today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;/p&gt;Out with the old, in with the newGreetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's never been a better time to retire your old ship from active duty in exchange for a brand-new Leonov.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've got a Leonov and are thinking of buying a Vengeance or Goliath, then do it now! We'll give you a discount on your new ship in exchange for your old scrap metal. Just trade in your Leonov and you'll get 2,500 Uridium off a new Venegeance or 5,000 Uridium off a new Goliath. It's out with the old, in with the new!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your DarkOrbit TeamShip with home advantageScientific breakthrough in the research labs: Powerful new alloy for the Leonov class&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Loyal employees of the company,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our research labs have just made an exciting announcement! They've successfully outfitted the Leonov-class ships with a revolutionary Promerium alloy. Welded in extreme conditions, this alloy makes it possible for the Leonovs to receive a high-energy beam which is transmitted from home base. This beam drastically increases the ships' capabilities when navigating on their own company's first four maps (X-1 bis X-4).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more details, head for the "Ships" area in the hangar. Ships receiving the beam will be surrounded by a blue haze. This will make it easier to identify them as stronger adversaries. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, a cost-effective way for new pilots to better defend themselves from stronger enemy ships! All previously purchased Leonovs have already been outfitted with the new alloy - at no extra cost to their owners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wishing you prosperity&lt;br /&gt;The DirectorNew Year's fireworks&lt;p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yet another year is coming to an end, and to celebrate, DarkOrbit is throwing a huge party with a spectacular display of fireworks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We went all out this year, getting our hands on every type of firework we could scrounge up:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You'll find three different sizes of fireworks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;They can be bought in the hangar, and also found in small quantities in bonus boxes on the map.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;And the best thing of all is that the fireworks won't take up any room in your armory!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can buy these special explosives from Dec. 28, 2009 to Dec. 31, 2009, but you won't be able to start your "symphony of fire" until Dec. 31, 2009!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Position up to five fireworks wherever you want on the map, and click on the button to detonate!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warning: According to intergalactic space law, each ship can only carry up to 9,999 fireworks on board to minimize the risk of explosion. Any fireworks which you collect above this number will be launched out into space and join the rest of the space debris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We wish you a Happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;/p&gt;Travel through time and spaceThe JP02 CPU is an engineering marvel: It lets you jump back to your home base no matter how far you've traveled, saving you time and helping you avoid the myriad of dangers facing you on your return journey.New laser ammo: Use the RSB-75 to wreak even more havocWe are proud to present the Rapid salvo battery, the result of years of backbreaking R&amp;D! The new Rapid salvo battery makes your laser cannons even more deadly. Load your laser with this ammo and rain death on your enemies when you fire off a rapid salvo. Your targets won't know what hit them!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is one type of ammo you just can't do without!Countdown to the Galactic GamesThe fun begins on February 12: While sub-zero temperatures keep things locked in a deep-freeze out on the planet's surface, fierce competition will heat things up at DarkOrbit. The bravest space cowboys from all three companies will go head-to-head in a variety of skill-testing, death-defying disciplines: Spaceball, Capture the Beacon, Team Deathmatch, Invasion Gates... no matter where your talents lie, there's sure to be something that's right for you.&lt;br /&gt;Until February 28, 2010, players will be competing in different disciplines to bring home coveted prizes.&lt;br /&gt;Make a note in your logbooks: from Feb. 12-28, there'll be battles, battles and more battles - take part, have fun, and compete against top-class medal contenders.SkylabAttention all space pilots!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We're proud to announce DarkOrbit's latest update: The Skylab!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to this technological wonder, you can now use and refine your ores in ways you never imagined possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can upgrade the Skylab with different &lt;b&gt;modules&lt;/b&gt; and thereby activate new functions or accelerate existing ones.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Skylab also contains &lt;b&gt;ore collectors&lt;/b&gt; from which you can get the precious substances you need to refine.&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to the Skylab, you'll soon be able to get your hands on the legendary &lt;b&gt;Seprom&lt;/b&gt;, which can currently be used for two purposes:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you equip your lasers or rockets with 1 unit of Seprom, every 10 units will receive a 60% damage bonus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you equip your shield generators with 1 unit of Seprom, their resistance will increase by 40% for 10 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For a complete Skylab guide, visit the &lt;b&gt;FAQ section of the forum&lt;/b&gt;, where you'll find a complete list and explanation of all the Skylab's functions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your DarkOrbit TeamThe new group system&lt;h3&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you all know, there's strength in numbers. To help you achieve your goals, we're introducing an group system to DarkOrbit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll now be able to form temporary groups with your in-game friends in order to accomplish quests and achieve a common purpose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So get out there and join an existing group, or form your own: and guide them to victory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks to the group system, your intergalactic adventures will be more action-packed and exciting than ever - fighting in groups is more thrilling and more effective.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are you waiting for? Round up your group and take on more than ever before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;/p&gt;DarkOrbit's Spring Fight&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get in on the action and start this season off right - DarkOrbit's Spring Fight is just around the bend. Satisfy your need for adventure with one of the many Spring Fight events from March 31 to April 5, 2010.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;Supersonic Space Hunt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sound the alarms, it's hunting season! Stock up on weapons and fight on behalf of your company in the Supersonic Space Hunt from March 31 to April 5. There will be three new titles for your company to get during this time. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The goal of the Supersonic Space Hunt is to win all of these titles: The company with all three titles on Monday at 11:00pm wins! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Keep your eyes peeled for the following titles: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MMO Spring Fighter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EIC Spring Fighter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VRU Spring Fighter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br&gt; This year spring is bound to be better than ever with additional surprises such as the Capture the Beacon tournament and Spaceball events.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buckle up for adventure!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;/p&gt;DarkOrbit's Spring Fight - Capture the Beacon&lt;p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don't miss out - Capture the Beacon is back! A Capture the Beacon tournament will begin on the hour every hour. Start your engines and move fast to get the beacons! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The winning company of a CTB round will receive their reward at some time during the next hour. The company with the most wins will take home the prize of the day. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Here's a recap of CTB rules: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each company has a special zone on the X-2 map. In this zone, there are two enemy company beacons which you need to protect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At the same time you must try to retrieve your own beacons from the enemy X-2 maps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You'll receive one point as soon as your company brings its own beacon into its own zone and you prevent the enemy teams from capturing their beacons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The player who has captured a beacon will be clearly displayed on the mini map and will be unprotected no matter where he/she is during this time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If this player is using his/her cloaking device, it will be deactivated. The current score of a match and the position of all beacons can seen on the star chart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;DarkOrbit's Spring Fight Finale - Spaceball &lt;p&gt;Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Give it your all one last time, the end is near. The final Spring Fight event is here: Spaceball! The company that wins Spaceball will win the day and all its members will receive a 15% experience point bonus. Members of the second-placed company will receive a 5% EP bonus. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Here's a breakdown of the rules: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A spaceball will be placed in the middle of the 4-4 map. Each company will have a goal-gate on this map. (Requirement to play: Level 9)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's your goal to try to shoot the spaceball through your company's gate. You'll get one point per goal. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shoot at the spaceball and watch it go hyperactive. The more you damage the spaceball, the faster it will move towards your company's gate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in seven days, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in one day, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in two days, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in three days, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in four days, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in five days, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in six days, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Spring cleaning countdown at DarkOrbit - we're shutting down the old client!It's spring cleaning time: The old client will be taken offline in seven days, marking the beginning of a new era not only for DarkOrbit but for all space pilots. Those of you who want to check out the new group system now can switch to the new client in the Help section. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Playing on the new DarkOrbit client is the only way for you to form groups and collaborate to fight off common enemies!&lt;/strong&gt;Get strategic with the plasma chargerTop-secret weapon plans found at the company labs: The discovery of preliminary weapon blueprints has burst onto the DarkOrbit scene! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; But it looks like we weren't the first ones there: other spies have tampered with the information. Although we don't know which company is behind these devious plans, we do know that the plasma charger will allow you to take down your enemies' systems with space distortion!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The plasma charger fills your rockets with plasma.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upon exploding, the rockets will form a molecular cloud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The molecular cloud will temporarily affect your enemies' weapons systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br&gt; These weapons will wreak major havoc on your enemies' accuracy, making it possible for you to take them out while their systems are compromised.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Use the plasma charger strategically: You can only re-use it once it has been refilled, and it will take a heavy toll on your generator. But it also means lights out for your enemies! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Booster Happy Hour on Sunday: 50% damage boosters for the galaxy gatesGreetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; It's the opportunity of a lifetime: Play the galaxy gates this Sunday and clean up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; From &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;2:00pm to 8:00pm, when you enter a galaxy gate, you'll get a 50% damage booster&lt;/span&gt;. It'll only be active during this time and in a galaxy gate universe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; This is your chance to play a galaxy gate through to the end. Don't miss out!Action for all: The new Invasion gates are here!Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; This just in: DarkOrbit is introducing Invasion gates for pilots of all levels! In the past, many of you haven't had the shadow of a chance in the Invasion gate, but now all pilots, regardless of their level, will have a fair shot at scoring cool bonus items and downing enemy ships in exciting space fights. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; In the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Invasion Gate Event on this coming Saturday from 4:00pm to 10:00pm, &lt;/span&gt;there will be 3 level groups: newbies, experienced fighters and seasoned space professionals. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Each level group will have a different map: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Level 1-6&lt;/span&gt; pilots will play on the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;x-1 map&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Level 7-12&lt;/span&gt; pilots will play on the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;x-3 map&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pilots at &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Level 13 and above&lt;/span&gt; will play on the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;x-5 map&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The Invasion gates will only be playable from the assigned level. Make your way to your gate early to beat the rush. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; We wish all pilots the best of luck in their interstellar pursuits!New delivery of Skylab robots!The Skylab just received a delivery of new robots for you to use to boost your productivity and increase the Skylab's efficiency. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on Productivity in the individual windows to get the robots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each robot increases your productivity without using any additional resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; You can only have a certain number of robots for each building.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Tip: Make sure to pay attention to how many robots are being used and how long they've been working - even the best robots won't last forever. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Move fast and improve your productivity with these tiny tinkerers!The thrill of the chase: the PvP Bounty Hunt extravaganza!Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This Wednesday to Sunday, you'll be the hunter and the hunted - during DarkOrbit's &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Bounty Hunt&lt;/span&gt;, every pilot is fair game!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fire away at friends and foes in this &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;PvP free-for-all&lt;/span&gt;. You'll get points no matter who your victim works for, but your company will get extra points when you down pilots from enemy companies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Players will be spread out over all maps: It's up to you to chase them down and blow them up. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But no feeding on the small fry! You'll only get points for shooting down players of equal strength. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your own points and the top ten will be posted in the stats on the website. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; For the duration, you can forget friendship, alliance and mercy - everyone will have their eyes on the prize. Each day's winner will be granted the unique title of &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;PvP Hunter of the Day&lt;/span&gt; for the following day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The overall winner will receive the title &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;PvP Bounty Hunter&lt;/span&gt; until the next Bounty Hunt event.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Happy hunting, pilots!Customize your DarkOrbit gameplay with 25 new skillsGreetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our top scientists have discovered a way to decipher log-disks salvaged from wrecked spaceships. The log-disk recordings have helped us to expand our knowledge of the universe and develop new technologies. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Collect log-disks and support your company in its endeavor to stay on the cutting-edge. You'll be able to trade in your collected log-disks for pilot points that can be used to learn new skills in three different categories: offense, defense and production. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Here's how it works:&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;log-disks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exchange the log-disks for &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;pilot points&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use your pilot points to upgrade the skills listed in your &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;pilot bio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Give it a try, it's really quite simple. Just collect log-disks for pilot points and use your pilot points to learn new skills and expand your horizons.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's up to you decide what skills you want to learn. There are &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;25 awesome skills&lt;/span&gt; for you to choose from to customize your gaming style. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Take this chance to sharpen your skills and blast light-years ahead of the competition!Massive graphics update: A new look for all shipsGreetings Space Pilots,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's time for change at DarkOrbit, and we've revamped your spaceships in the framework of a massive &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;graphics update&lt;/span&gt;.  &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Something new for every ship: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Pimped-up classics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; The most popular ships will be keeping the same basic shape, we've just spiffed them up and made a few small changes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;The next generation in ship design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; A few ship models have been fully overhauled and now have a completely new look. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Curious? Then head to the space maps, see what's new, and take the company war to the next level in your new ship.An awesome new design + increased firepower for your GoliathOur engineers worked on this project for a full year, and it's finally finished and available at the hangar: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;The new Combat Goliath design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; For the first time ever, when you buy this new design, you'll be able to keep your old design and switch between them in the equipment area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get your hands on the new Combat Design.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Equip your Goliath with it in the equipment area of the hangar.&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Not only will your ship look different, you'll receive a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;5% damage bonus on all your weapons&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Get the new Combat Design, head out to the space maps and blast away your enemies with 5% more damage!Let your enemies feel your wrath with the Vengeance Damage Design: the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;REVENGE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DarkOrbit proudly presents the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;REVENGE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, the new Vengeance battle design.&lt;br&gt; - Now available at the hangar -&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get yourself the Damage Design and pay your enemies back in pain. With the brand-new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;REVENGE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; design for your &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Vengeance&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, your spaceship's never been so stylish, and it's never packed a bigger punch!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new and improved look for your Vengeance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increased capability - 5% more damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easy design switch in the equipment area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br&gt; With the new design, your weapons systems will become even more deadly. Get yourself the Revenge and pay your enemies back tenfold! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Equip your Vengeance with the new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;REVENGE&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; design in the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hangar equipment area&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Not only will your ship have a brand-new look, your weapons will also inflict an &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;awesome 5% more damage!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Launch a counterstrike with the EMP burst - your secret weapon!Surrounded by enemies? In a dead-end situation? Then use the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;EMP burst&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! An electromagnetic impulse wave will temporarily interfere with your enemies' onboard instruments, short-circuiting their targeting devices and quite possibly damaging their cloaking devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The EMP burst is like an expanding force field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is emitted from your ship and expands outwards to deactivate the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;targeting devices&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of all ships within range.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you use the EMP burst, nobody will be able to target you for &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;3 seconds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the EMP burst carefully, it has a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;35-second cool-down time.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Without a clever strategy, you might end up at the mercy of your enemies!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br&gt; Get ready for a big bang - take down enemy targeting devices, uncloak their ships and blow 'em out of space. Your time has come!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reload in a flash with the rocket launcher!&lt;b&gt;Bring out the big guns&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: It's time for drastic measures! With the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;rocket launcher&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you can bombard the enemy with a cataclysmic surge of destruction. Releasing 3 or 5 rockets at once, both types of rocket launcher will make sure your enemies go down in a blaze of fire.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Use the launcher's specially designed rockets, batter your enemy with a broadside of missiles and light up the sky with a shower of rockets! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rain of fire: Get yourself the rocket-launcher CPU!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;The automatic CPU for your rocket launcher: &lt;br&gt;Launch a Hellstorm attack the easy way.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you like to make it rain rockets? Then get the most from your rocket launcher with the new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket-launcher CPU.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This CPU automatically reloads your rocket launcher, allowing you to fire off volleys as quickly as possible to really rain down destruction upon your enemies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to inflict as much damage as possible by firing a continuous flow of rockets without lifting a finger? Then get yourself the Rocket-launcher CPU and unleash devastation on a massive scale.More means more: A rush of rockets for your rocket launcherEquip the rocket launcher with its &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;specially designed rockets&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and give the command to unleash a world of pain. Deadly rocket broadsides will rock your enemies' defenses with their destructive force. The rockets will rip through their hulls from all sides, leaving no surface untouched and blowing them to pieces.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Independence Day fireworksWelcome to the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;biggest Independence Day celebration&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the universe. Play to win your own fireworks and help us transform the sky into a colorful mosaic of red, white and blue on &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 4th of July is a very important date for the people of space: It celebrates the most important technological breakthrough of all time - the jump portal. With this technology, pilots were able to cover long distances in a fraction of a second for the first time ever and were able to explore strange new worlds and new galaxies, thus freeing themselves from their dependency on individual planets and solar systems. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Put on your protective eyewear and buckle up for a spectacular display of fireworks: On July 4th the rockets will streak through the sky in red, blue and white!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Don't miss out on the action: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;June 27 to July 4&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; collect as many fireworks as you can.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Launch your fireworks into the sky on July 4.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The space pilots who light up the sky the most will receive an &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;exclusive Independence ship design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; from their company!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Shed light in the dark universe of DarkOrbit: Join in the festivities and celebrate humanity's liberty and freedom to explore the vast expanses of space with the most spectacular galactic fireworks show.Collect as many fireworks as you can from June 27th to July 4th and launch them into orbit on July 4th.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Each company has 3 rankings, one for each fireworks size. Light the most fireworks and win the Independence design.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take part and become a real DarkOrbit firestarter!Galactic Championship 2010: May the best company win!June 16-July 11, 2010: During DarkOrbit's Galactic Championship, events such as Spaceball, Capture the Beacon and Team Deathmatch will take place every Wednesday, Friday and Sunday. The events will be held between 7pm and 9pm on Wednesdays and Fridays, and from 3pm to 5pm on Sundays.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An overall ranking will update you on your company's score.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During the 2010 Galactic Championship, your company will be rewarded for winning certain events.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Spaceball:&lt;br /&gt;10% more honor the day after the victory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CTB:&lt;br /&gt;10% more honor for one hour after the victory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The company that wins the 2010 Galactic Championship will get 10% more honor and experience points for 5 days and 10% more bonus-box content for 2 days.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;May the best company win!The strongest shield in orbitOur engineers have been working on a powerful new design for the Goliath Battlecruiser for eons.&lt;br /&gt;Now finally, we're proud to present the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;new Goliath Bastion design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you feel like your shield can't take the heat against enemy salvos? Get the new shield boosting design with &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;10% more shield strength&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This new design doesn't just give your ship a new look, it also gives it a 10% shield bonus!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boost your shields to 110% power and blast into action!Introducing the Avenger - the defensive Vengeance designOur engineers are proud to present the new Vengeance design: Meet the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Avenger, the new defensive design for your Vengeance starfighter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shields having a tough time holding up under enemy fire? Get them a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;10% power boost&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Avenger design advantages:&lt;br /&gt; This new design won't just change the look of your Vengeance, it'll also give you a 10% shield bonus!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blast into battle with the best shields you've ever had!NEW group gates and unknown galaxiesCalling all space pilots! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Head to the new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;group gates on the X-3 maps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; and fight your way through unknown galaxies. Bring a few friends along or else you won't stand a chance out there!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; These unexplored galaxies are millions of light years away and the gates only have enough energy to transport &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;up to 5 space pilots&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. Make sure all five of you are well-equipped!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Good luck!Summer Games 2010: Power up for the next roundGreetings Space Pilots,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wait is finally over: The next round of the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;DarkOrbit Summer Games&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt; is about to kick off.&lt;br&gt;Get ready for tons of fun, action and surprises.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take part and fight for glory and prizes, either alone or with your company. There will be one new discipline every day for you to enter&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt; and win.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You'll be awarded points for every &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;daily discipline&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your top ten results will count towards your &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summer Games Championship Total&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The pilot who amasses the most championship points by the end of the Summer Games will win the grand prize: &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;An indestructible ninth drone for one month&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; as well as many other awesome prizes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Places two through five will get Uridium, UCB-100 and Seprom, as well as a ninth drone for 15 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pilots who place sixth through one-hundredth will also reap rich rewards for their performance. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Fight your way to the top and earn your place in the event of the summer: Win the DarkOrbit Summer Games!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join the Giant Pumpkin FestivalFreaky frights and spooky delights, it's that time of year again - &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Halloween&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! Have a wicked time from October 25th to October 30th. Accept thrilling new quests for pros and newbies, and take part in the mother of all Halloween events on October 31st:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open fire and clear your way through the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Invasion Gate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to take on the evil pumpkin known as the Kucurbium.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect pumpkins in space and receive special treats &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; (extras)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scare the living daylights out of your opponents with &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WIZ rockets&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and transform yourself and your friends into big, mean aliens.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt; You'll also get to enjoy &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;five new special quests&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; on October 31st. Compete in the galaxy's eeriest event and have a Happy Halloween!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;December's Dark Winter!This year's &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dark Winter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a lot to offer! All December long there will be surprises left and right: Celebrate the season, enjoy lots of events and score &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;mountains of rewards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and presents.&lt;br /&gt;Get ready to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Defend outer space from an &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;unknown threat&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; growing in the darkness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Complete a &lt;b&gt;special quest&lt;/b&gt; every day from &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;December 1–24, 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and rack up serious rewards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Celebrate &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;DarkOrbit's 4-year anniversary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gear up, there's no time to lose! It's time for you to blast your way through winter surprises!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have fun and happy hunting this &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;December!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fire up for December's Dark Winter!Heat things up this December: Take part in DarkOrbit's &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dark Winter from Dec. 1, 2010 to Jan. 2, 2011 &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;and battle your way through the bitter cold! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dark Winter Events:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Get great prizes with the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Quest calendar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Complete a special quest each day and rack up awesome prizes from Dec. 1 to Dec. 24, 2010!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your engines running from Dec. 24, 2010 to Jan. 2, 2011 and take on &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;five special quests for pro pilots!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Celebrate DarkOrbit's &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;4th anniversary on Dec. 11, 2010&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Explore special anniversary gates!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stop 'em cold and save the galaxy from destruction: On Dec. 15, Orbit will be invaded by an &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;unknown enemy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Start the New Year off with a bang: Buy&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; fireworks from Dec. 31, 2010 to Jan. 1, 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look out for star-shaped boxes and gift boxes found floating around space and brighten up your Dark Winter with valuable rewards. &lt;br /&gt;Warm up your engines and take off for the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dark Winter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now available: Two brand-new Goliath designs!Think your Goliath Battlecruiser could use a new look? Want more experience and honor points? Then check out the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; Veteran and Exalted designs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the hangar!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Veteran&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: A sleek and glossy white design that will grant you a 10% bonus on all the experience points you collect!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exalted&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: An awesome red design that will strike fear in the hearts of your enemies while earning you 10% more honor points!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tip:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Can't decide which design you want? Then get the Rising Star Pack on the payment page - it'll cost you 50% less than if you bought both separately! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Get the new Goliath designs now and rise above your competition by collecting experience and honor more quickly than ever before! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now available: Two brand-new Goliath designs!Think your Goliath Battlecruiser could use a new look? Want more experience and honor points? Then check out the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; Veteran and Exalted designs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the hangar!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Veteran&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: A sleek and glossy white design that will grant you a 10% bonus on all the experience points you collect!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exalted&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: An awesome red design that will strike fear in the hearts of your enemies while earning you 10% more honor points!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tip:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Can't decide which design you want? Then get the Rising Star Pack on the payment page - it'll cost you 50% less than if you bought both separately! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Get the new Goliath designs now and rise above your competition by collecting experience and honor more quickly than ever before! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Introducing the Solace - 1 of 5 new designsGet the cool new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Solace design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for your Goliath Battlecruiser. Fly in style and security armed with the Solace design's high-tech &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nano-Cluster Repairer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Use it to repair your ship hull and the hulls of group members immediately!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a 10% shield bonus just like with the Bastion design andbuy this must-have now. &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Solace design is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;one of five&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; new designs. Buy &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;all five in a pack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and take on any challenge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introducing the Diminisher - 1 of 5 new designsFly above the rest and get the brand-new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Diminisher design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for your Goliath Battlecruiser. Cruise around in a cool new design and stir up space with the Diminisher's &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Weaken Shield&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.Reduce your enemies' defensive capabilities - then open fire with full force!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inflict 5% more damage (just like with the Enforcer design) and watch your career soar with the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Diminisher design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Diminisher design is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;one of five&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; new designs. Buy &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;all five in a pack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and take on any challenge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introducing the Spectrum - 1 of 5 new designsRevamp your Goliath Battlecruiser with the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spectrum design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and benefit from its high-tech &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;prismatic shielding&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; capability.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although this design will temporarily weaken your lasers, it will also render enemy laser attacks basically useless and give you a 10% shield bonus. Take off in the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spectrum design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; now!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Spectrum design is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;one of five&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; new designs. Buy &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;all five in a pack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and take on any challenge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introducing the Sentinel - 1 of 5 new designsSpruce up your Goliath Battlecruiser with the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sentinel design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Turn your ship into an unstoppable force with its &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;fortress&lt;/b&gt; capability&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Power up this design and make your ship shields basically impenetrable for a short period of time. And receive a 10% shield bonus too - just like with the Bastion design. Get the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sentinel design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; now and survive even the toughest laser attack!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Sentinel design is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;one of five&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; new designs. Buy &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;all five in a pack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and take on any challenge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Introducing the Venom - 1 of 5 new designsNavigate the vast expanses of space and heat up the action in a brand-new design for your Goliath Battlecruiser: the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Venom design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Activate the Venom's special &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;singularity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; function to inflict massive damage temporarily!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This design will also give your ship a 5% damage bonus - just like the Enforcer design. Get the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Venom design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; now and teach your enemies the true meaning of fear!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Venom design is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;one of five&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; new designs. Buy &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;all five in a pack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and take on any challenge!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New at the hangar: The HM7 trade droneEffective immediately, you'll be able to purchase the HM7 trade drone at the hangar in "Extras". This trade drone maintains a subspace link with your space station, making it possible for you to trade your raw materials and resources from anywhere in the galaxy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; An overview of HM7 advantages: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Trade where you want, when you want – cut down on travel time.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Use the HM7 100 times before its energy is exhausted.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;         &lt;br&gt; Save your time for the fun stuff: Get the HM7 trade zone in the hangar in the "Extras" section.&lt;br /&gt;The new armory upgrade is here!Head straight to the hangar and click on "Extras" to get the armory upgrade 3 and benefit from an unbelievable 150% extra capacity! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;li&gt;Gigantic: 150% more ammo capacity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt; Shoot broadsides like they're going out of style: Get yourself the armory upgrade 3, now available in "Extras" at the hangar!&lt;br /&gt;Pilot Bio gets brand-new features&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;pilot bio&lt;/span&gt; just got a big boost with brand-new features. In the future, you'll not only be able to learn skills, but create your own profile and receive awesome rewards for recruiting friends to the game. You'll also be able to check out your daily bonuses there:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;                 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Profile&lt;/span&gt;: Create your own personal profile here to describe who you are and show off all your accolades. For the moment, you'll be the only person able to see your profile, but soon all pilots will be able to see it!&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Invite friends&lt;/span&gt;: Find new DarkOrbit recruits and receive awesome gifts in return, including an exclusive Goliath design.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Daily login bonus&lt;/span&gt;: Check out which daily login bonus you've received!&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;                 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Test out the new pilot bio today – update your profile, recruit friends to the game and score some &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;valuable items&lt;/span&gt;! Just click on pilot bio and then on either "Profile" or "Friends &amp; Bonuses".                 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lust to kill: Valentine's Day in DarkOrbit&lt;p&gt;Not in the mood for romance, pilot? Then get your baby ready for a different kind of date!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; This Valentine's Day, cupid's arrow turns deadly in DarkOrbit:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;                     &lt;ul&gt;
                        &lt;li style="list-style-type:none"&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Take your baby out for a real treat: Today you can repair your ship for free!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;/ul&gt;                 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; There's no time for candlelit dinners or kissing between combat!                 Celebrate this Valentine's Day like never before: With lasers!                 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; From DarkOrbit with love.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Orbital Carnival&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;From March 3-8,&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Carnival is blasting into orbit! There'll be lots of explosive fun for everyone! Intense event games, colorful fireworks and sweet rewards – we've got it all:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;         &lt;li&gt;Loads of goodies: Collect &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Carnival boxes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with valuable objects inside&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Fire to play with: Get yourself some &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;fireworks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and shed some light on deep space&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Daily events: Every day &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;from 3pm to 6pm* Capture the Beacon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and fly &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;from 8pm to 11pm*&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; through the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Invasion Gate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt; Ready to start the party? Then get in your cockpit from &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;March 3-8,&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and don't miss out on this marathon of carnival madness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Get out there, fight hard, and have lots of carnival fun!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; * Local time of the server &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cloaking CPU XL: Stealth in bulkAttention space illusionists and stealth hunters: Blend into your surroundings and masterfully execute your prey with the NEW &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cloaking CPU XL&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;li style="list-style-type: none;"&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Once activated, the CPU will cloak your ship until you launch an attack yourself.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt; The Cloaking CPU XL allows you to cloak your ship an impressive&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; 50 times&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! Get your own one now in the hangar or the trading post and vanish before your opponents very eyes! &lt;br&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Three new mines for demolition expertsLuring an enemy into a trap isn't easy - but now it's worth it! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Three new mines are now available in the hangar until 11:59pm (local server time) Sunday March 20, 2011.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; After Sunday they'll only appear in the hangar on special occasions - so keep your eyes peeled!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anti-cloaking mine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: The EMP-M01 uncloaks enemy ships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anti-shield mine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: The SAB-M01 inflicts 50% shield damage to ships within its radius.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Direct-damage mine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Based on a ship's base HP and pilot-bio upgrades, the DD-M01 causes 20% direct damage, giving you the power to destroy ships.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt; It gets even better: The &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;basic cool-down time&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of all previous mine types and new mines is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;now just 30 seconds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brace yourself for more explosions, more strategy and more danger than ever before!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Reapers are on the move!!!Fight harder, pilots! Reaper sightings are on the rise across the universe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Pull out the big guns and give it all you got,or else no one is safe!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Invasion of the Reapers&lt;p&gt;&lt;img id="breakingnews_image" src="do_img/global/layer/pirates/ship_1_text.png" width="444" height="122"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Centuries ago, pirates called "The Reapers" waged a huge war for control of our galaxy and were pushed back to the outskirts of the known universe. We assumed they'd vanished forever, but we wrong!     They've been lurking in the shadows ever since, slowly rebuilding their fleet and pillaging anything that dares stray into their part of the galaxy; stripping it of anything, and anyone, that was useful.     &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Aggressive and relentless, these pirates will stop at nothing short of galactic domination. With ships made from scrap metal salvaged from our own defense fleets, they've perfected our own technologies and turned them against us, making themselves stronger than ever before.     Living on the outer edges of the galaxy taught the Reapers the importance of sticking together: They work in packs, with ships of different and unknown capabilities.     &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; In sector 4-5, what was previously thought to be a one-way wormhole, the Reapers are starting to mass their fleet! Hold them back before they can advance further into our space. This threat is going nowhere fast, and they're here to destroy us - one way or another! If we learned anything from the past, it's that they attack in waves. Prepare for the battle of a lifetime: This could be the start of a massive invasion!     &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Until now we've only been able to collect limited data on the Reapers' new ships. Here's what we know so far: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;Fighter class: Code name "Interceptor"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; Very fast and small, the Interceptors are the Reapers' first response. They attack in large numbers and try to eliminate any resistance before it reaches their main force. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;Pull yourselves together, space pilots. Let's take to the fight to this new threat!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Incoming shock wave!Red alert! We just detected the birth of a supernova on the outer edges of deep space. A &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;burst of radiation&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is now sweeping across the universe and is expected to hit &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;today&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Brace for impact! Once this baby hits, it'll play havoc on your electronic systems and make your enemy detection system completely unreliable. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br&gt; Don't let it play tricks on you. &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trust your instincts&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and play it safe out there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Over and out!&lt;br /&gt;The AnnihilatorBad news, space pilots!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm afraid we failed to drive back the Reapers in sector 4-5. It turns out they're smarter than we thought. They figured out how to use our jump portals and now they're starting to infest the X-5 sectors. It's as if they're looking for something that we don't know about. The good news however is that we managed to collect some intel on another one of their ships: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Destroyer class: Code name "Annihilator"&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;img id="breakingnews_image" src="do_img/global/layer/pirates/ship_2_text.png" width="444" height="133"&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; When it's heavy artillery the Reapers need, it's the Annihilators they call. Although slower than the other ships, the Annihilator makes up for its sluggishness with heavy defenses and devastating weaponry. The Reapers use this superior firepower to their advantage, dishing out major damage to anything that dares cross their path. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Man the battle stations and hold off the pirates as long as you can. In the meantime, we'll figure out a way to win back our territory!The BarracudaOur efforts are failing! The pirates have learned a trick or two since our last encounter, and have pushed through our defenses and infiltrated sectors X-6 and X-7. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The Reapers are advancing too quickly and in droves. We need to act fast and find a new way to combat them! Here's some helpful intel to help you in your fight: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bomber class: code name "Barracuda" &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;img id="breakingnews_image" src="do_img/global/layer/pirates/ship_3_text.png" width="444" height="133"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Produced in masses, the Barracuda is the Reapers' main line of defense thanks to its versatility in battle and effective performance. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Navigated by fearless fighters, Barracuda pilots have no problem giving their lives to serve the cause. When things get out of hand in battle and they see no way out, these kamikaze pilots will close in on their target and detonate special on-board explosives. Carelessness around the Barracuda will cost you your life. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Regain the upper hand and stop the Reapers before it's too late for us to undo the damage! &lt;br&gt;New Reaper ship sightedOur resistance has failed again. The Reapers have infiltrated our home bases in the X-8 sectors and are pushing forward at a rapid rate. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; There's only one solution: Group up and exterminate this plague! Among the ranks of the Reapers we've discovered a new class: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cruiser class: Code name "Saboteur"&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;img id="breakingnews_image" src="do_img/global/layer/pirates/ship_4_text.png" width="444" height="133"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The Saboteurs are quite possibly the most deadliest Reaper ships out there. They have special equipment to latch onto their prey and immobilize it. They then drag themselves in close making it impossible to damage them without damaging yourself. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Saboteurs may be the turning point in any battle, but you aren't completely helpless against them. We've determined a weakness: An EMP burst could disrupt their systems and set you free from their clutches. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Don't think you're out of the woods just yet. They'll learn from their mistakes, so only use this tactic when you truly must. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Join forces once more, pilots! Our survival depends on it!Retreat of the Reapers ... PSYCH!The Reapers are pulling out of our sectors. I don’t know what you did but whatever it was, it sure worked! Well done, pilots! After all that fighting, you sure deserve a well-earned break … &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; But wait … What's that? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Oh no, this isn't good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; It looks like the pirates only retreated to gather scrap from our battered and broken hulls in order to build a new base. The Reapers have taken and modified our warp technology and to turn it against us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; They've built one-way gates to ensure that there's no easy way out for pilots who venture into their space. They've set up gates in sector 4-5 that lead to their own territory; once on the other side, the only gate there will lead you back to sector 4-4.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; A deadly new enemy patrols the Reapers' base. And this is what we know about them:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mothership: Code name "Battleray"&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;img id="breakingnews_image" src="do_img/global/layer/pirates/ship_5_text.png" width="444" height="133"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The Battleray is the largest and most powerful ship in the Reaper fleet. It serves as a support vessel for the rest of the armada and is used as launch pad for smaller Reaper ships such as the Interceptors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; It can launch wave after wave of Interceptors into space and repair damaged Interceptors by by sending out a burst of energy. As long as there's a certain number of Interceptors in its vicinity, the Battleray is next to indestructible.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Team up and take on the Battleray - it's the only way you'll ever stand a chance! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pilot's best friend - the P.E.T 10Introducing a space revolution: The &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;P.E.T. 10&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a P.E.T. 10 you are never alone! It'll back you up when you're in a bind and take care of different jobs! Now's your chance to have &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;your own P.E.T. 10. Buy one in the hangar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and take advantage of its numerous perks:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;img src="do_img/global/layer/petLaunch/pet.png" width="406" height="154" style="margin:10px;" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Give your robotic companion&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; different skills&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Have it locate or track down enemies, or give it Kamikaze gear!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;AI protocols&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and enhance your P.E.T.'s performance with better armor, more storage and stronger lasers!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watch your P.E.T. 10 collect EP and evolve as it &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;levels up&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The P.E.T. 10 is the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ultimate companion in space&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, but also the ultimate weapon!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; yours now in the hangar!             &lt;br&gt;The hanger just got a whole lot better!Now appearing in a hangar near you: An impressive array of &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;new innovations&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! Not to mention the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;shop&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;equipment screen&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; have had a total makeover: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Better looking: The sleek &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;new look&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; makes the menus more stylish and clearly arranged!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More functional: Discover the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;new features&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, like the spacious inventory and item-filter possibilities!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even simpler: &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Improved handling&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;; just drag &amp; drop!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br&gt; The revamped equipment and shop screens will save you valuable time and get you back onto the battlefield faster. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Check out all the new improvements &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;now in the hangar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!Bring on the Spring FightSpring is here, and it's that time again! Time to relive last year's spring fights with a whole week of excitement, action and spectacular battles. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Gear up and get out there &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;from April 18-25, 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to score awesome rewards and rare titles: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pirate hunt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: The pirates grow stronger with each passing day. Fend them off and get your hands on cool prizes and titles!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Supersonic Space Hunt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Fly into the heat of the battle and go for the elusive Spring Fighter II title.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Capture the Beacon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spaceball&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: These good old classics are your chance to win prizes for your team!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hunt, fight, annihilate – &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;From April 18-25, 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, it's time for you to do some spring cleaning! For further info and game rules look in the forum: %FORUMLINK_START%&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Forum&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;%FORUMLINK_END% &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Ship out and enjoy Spring!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advanced Jump CPU - quantum leap through spaceAfter months of hard research, our scientists have done it again, and come up with another breakthrough in warp technology. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;li style="list-style-type: none;"&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advanced Jump CPU: Jump to any map in the known star system, except for home maps and locked maps!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br&gt; Buckle up for hyperjump and explore space faster than ever before. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The Advanced Jump CPU is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;now available to buy in the hangar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br&gt;Premium fun with Premium advantagesAre you a Premium player already? If not, consider it your ace up your sleeve: The Premium Pack puts you one step ahead of your adversaries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Put all the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Premium advantages&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to use: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Log out from the star chart in just five seconds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Enjoy more cargo room with 500 extra units of space&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get 5% off all Uridium items&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Have your spaceship repaired for free&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Save 50% on drone repairs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Have your resources automatically refined&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Make your repair bots twice as effective&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unlock all Radar CPU advantages&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cut the time it takes to load rockets in half&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br&gt; Become a Premium player now: With the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Six-Month Silver Pack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;One-Year Gold Pack&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Click on "Uridium" in the menu and then on "Banking" to get your pack today! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Happy Mothership Day!Honor to whom honor is due! Today we honor our motherships. Celebrate with us and score great rewards! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Power up your spaceships and join the action - &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;today only&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;5 brand-new&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and exciting &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;quests&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compete in some intense &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Invasion Gate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; matches &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;from 5-9pm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;metal flowers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; filled with valuable contents and&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; repair your ship for free&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br&gt; Enter the Mother's Day fray and emerge from battle a wealthy pilot! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Kill while the killing's good and &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;make your momma proud&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;!The new deceleration rocket: Stop your enemies in their tracksAre your opponents too fast? Are they just out of reach or constantly hot on your tail? The deceleration rocket will give you the help you need! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;li style="list-style-type: none;"&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The deceleration rocket: Hit your enemies with one of these to temporarily slow 'em down!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br&gt; Put the speed advantage back on your side! Don't let your prey squirm away when you're closing in for the kill. Or use them to give the most tenacious pursuers the slip. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; The deceleration rocket is &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;now available in the hangar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A space first: The repair robot 4More efficient, faster and better: The latest generation of repair bots are now available! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;li style="list-style-type: none;"&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Repair robot 4: Regenerates 75,000 hit points per minute&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br&gt; Faster repairs means a swifter return to the action! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Head to &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;the hangar&lt;/b&gt; and get your repair robot 4 now&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three new designs for your Vengeance StarfighterCould your Vengeance Starfighter use a new paint job? Then check out the Uridium page in the hangar right now. There you'll find &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;three brand-new designs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for this ship – including &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;for the first&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Vengeance skill design ever&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Each has its own awesome advantages: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adept design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Gives you a 10% bonus on all experience points gained!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Corsair design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Provides you with a 10% bonus on all honor gained!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lightning design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Helps you deal 5% extra damage. The design also includes a complete new look and the "Afterburner" ability. Activate it to use a unique turbo boost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br&gt; Buy the new designs now to get the edge in battle or move up the ranks faster. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;All three designs are available now in the hangar or on the Uridium page&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4th of JulyEvery year on the 4th of July all of mankind celebrates a giant breakthrough in space travel, the invention of the jump gate. This technology makes it possible to travel unimaginable distances in the blink of an eye and it ensures the independence of single planets throughout the universe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; So fold down your sun visor and out the sunscreen, because only one day of the year is so bright in the Orbit.         In order to celebrate this independence there will be special US fireworks available in the shop all day. On top of that there will be no repair costs for the entire 4th of July.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Enjoy this special day in spaceSummer Games 2011: Week IThe &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summer Games 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are blasting off! Check your ship's cooling system and activate your UV-protection mode: DarkOrbit is launching &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;several weeks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of fierce fighting and fantastic prizes!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Whether it's Capture the Beacon, Spaceball, Team Deathmatch or Invasion Gate – this &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;event marathon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has something for every pilot!         What, where, when? All the latest event info will be posted in the News section every Friday!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Coming up this week:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         &lt;ol&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Invasion Gate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 8 from 7 p.m to 10 p.m. and July 13 from 6 p.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Team Deathmatch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 9 from 3 p.m. to 5 p.m. and July 14 from 6 p.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spaceball&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 9 from 6 p.m. to 10 p.m. and July 12 from 5 p.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Capture the Beacon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 11 from 6 p.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Collection event&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Collect precious ores on all maps (from X-2 and above). You might just find some valuable items in the process. There are also three repeatable missions.                 The event starts on July 15 at 7 p.m. and on July 17 at 9 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ol&gt;         &lt;br&gt; And don't forget, there's also the regular &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jackpot Battle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; on Sunday. This is just the beginning of great things to come - the following week will be just as action-packed!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Go all out and have a blast during the Summer Games!Summer Games 2011: Week IIOne week into the Summer Games and the action's just starting to heat up. Don't give up now, shift into overdrive and compete in the fierce and fast-paced firefights of the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summer Games 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The fun's just kicking off - look forward to &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;weeks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of pure enjoyment! All the latest event info will be posted in the News section every Friday!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; This week, we've got Team Deathmatch, Capture the Beacon and Spaceball lined up for you! Blast off once again, stick it to your enemies and score some phenomenal bonuses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;             &lt;ol&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Team-Deathmatch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 18 from 6 p.m to 8 p.m. and July 21 from 7 p.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Capture the Beacon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 18 from 6 p.m to 8 p.m. and July 21 from 7 p.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spaceball&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 20 from 7 p.m. to 9 p.m. and July 22 from 6 p.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt; Don't miss out on any of these DarkOrbit classics. Show the other pilots who's got the big guns and rack up &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;rewards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in return.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; What are you waiting for? Ship out now and get in the game!Summer Games 2011: Week IIIThe &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summer Games&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are two weeks in and the action is starting to heat up. Make a move quickly for your chance to score sensational rewards and make your company proud!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; During the next seven days, you can be a part of &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;explosive fireworks events&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Capture the Beacon&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 23, 2011 from 3 p.m. to 5 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Invasion Gate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 23, 2011 from 7 p.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Team Deathmatch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 24, 2011 from 2 p.m. to 4 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spaceball&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: July 24, 2011 from 6 p.m. to 10 p.m. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt; After that we're going to kick start the festivities by hosting the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;NPC Hunt&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Starting on &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 25 to July 31, 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you can compete in three fast-paced NPC-hunting rounds, collect points and win &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;wicked prizes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The winners of each round will be picked based on different criteria: player, clan and company. Get ready to go hunting and snatch the following swag :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;All pilots of the winning company in the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;best-company&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; round will receive 5% more EP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All members of the winning clan in the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;best-clan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; round will get two weeks of free Premium status. The winning clan will also receive 250,000,000 Credits for its communal treasury.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;best player&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player round will be awarded six months of Premium advantages, 15,000 rounds of X-4 ammo, 10,000 Uriidum and each mine type 150 times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Second place to tenth place&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player ranking won't fly away empty-handed, they'll get 10,000 rounds of X-4 ammo, 7,500 Uridium and each mine type 50 times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;11th place to 30th place&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player ranking will score 7,500 rounds of X4 ammo, 3,000 Uridium and each mine type 25 times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;31st to 100th place&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player ranking will receive 1,500 rounds of X-4 ammo, 1,500 Uridium and each type of mine ten times.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt; A never-ending summer of fun: That's what awaits you in the weeks to come! Keep fighting and tune in next Friday for more details!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Hunt, shoot, and destroy: Track 'em all down - it's scorching time!Greetings Space Pilots!The Goliath trio is finally complete - welcome the slick new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jade Design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; aboard, pilots!         &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Attention all pilots of Amber and Sapphire designs - Listen up! Your designs have also been streamlined to be sleeker and better than ever before.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Make a smart move and &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;save an awesome 33% if you buy 'em all at once!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;         &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If you've already got the Amber or Sapphire Designs, then don't worry - you can just buy the Jade Design on its own!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Here's a couple of helpful hints and tactical tips for the epic battle in space:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         &lt;ol&gt;

        &lt;li&gt;Show your support for your company by sporting their trademark color!&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Switch design colors during special events, such as Jade for St. Patrick's Day, Amber for Halloween or Sapphire for your B-day! &lt;li&gt;Throw your enemies for a loop - just activate another design with a different company color and surprise attack them!&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ol&gt;         &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Starting now, the name of the game is "Friend or Foe": Don't just trust anyone - appearances can be deceiving!         When you buy a design, you'll receive the old design as well and can switch back to it at any time using the equipment client.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Act now and brighten up the dark expanses of space!VENGEANCE DESIGNSpecial bulletin: Valuable cargo chests dumped into space by the retreating pirates!The pirates have been successfully pushed back to their own sector of space and our star system is safely back in our hands.   &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The pirates were forced to hastily withdraw and left &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;valuable treasure chests&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in their wake. Unlike normal boxes, you'll need a key to open these chests which you can purchase in the hangar.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reports from the first pilots to open the chests are coming in and they appear to contain impressive contents, such as a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;new laser&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Help us keep these valuable items from falling back into the pirate hands and collect all the pirate chests.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Even normal NPCs didn't shy away from the battle against the pirates and managed to collect some of the chests for themselves. If you destroy these NPCs, you can claim the "Pirate Booty" for yourself.&lt;br /&gt;News about the P.E.T. 10We've taken into consideration your feedback on the P.E.T. 10 and have put it straight to use. Here's a list of the new changes:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;         &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Repair costs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; From level 1 to 2, it will now cost you nothing to repair your P.E.T. Starting at level 3, you'll have to start to pay for repairs. Costs will increase by ten Uridium for every level, capping off at 350 Uridium at level 15.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;P.E.T. speed&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; Up until now the P.E.T. 10 has been too slow for you to effectively use. That's why we increased its speed from 100% of the normal player speed to 130%.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Auto collection gear&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; In the past, when the P.E.T. was in collection mode, it would always attempt to collect the same boxes as the actual player. With a bit of technological magic, we've changed this so that the P.E.T. now collects much more efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;More power for higher levels&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; Now with five additional levels, the P.E.T. 10 will be more robust and aggressive in combat. Upon reaching level 15, it will also be given a new look.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hot keys&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt; Many players have asked for hot keys to help use the P.E.T. 10. To start off, we've created two new hot keys: The [E] key activates or deactivates the P.E.T. and the [R] key sets it in guard mode. This will allow you to defend yourself to the best of your ability the moment you're attacked.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;         &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; As you can see: Your ideas can make their way into the game, so please keep them coming. Just drop us a note in the forum! That's enough reading for now - get to it!         &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Your DarkOrbit Team&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stock up on ammo and get ready to fight, 'cuz it's pirate hunting time!&lt;br&gt; Help us defeat pirates from 7:00 pm on April 18, 2011 till 11:59pm* on April 25th, 2011 and earn valuable bounty points for every kill. Rack up as many points as you can and become the Pirate Hunt Champion.     Bounty points won't only count towards your score but they'll also be used to determine your company's ranking.&lt;br&gt; The company's Pirate Hunt ranking will be calculated by adding together the bounty-point scores of the company's top 300 killers and then dividing the total value by 300 to get a company average. The company scores will be displayed in a company counter which shows the number of downed pirates vs. the top 300 company fighters. That way each company will have a fair chance of winning the Pirate Hunt.&lt;b&gt;NPC Hunt&lt;/b&gt;Join the hunt from &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;July 25 to July 31, 2011&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Compete in three fast-paced hunting rounds, collect points and win &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;wicked prizes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.         The winners of each round will be picked based on different criteria: player, clan and company. Get in the game to get your hands on the following:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         &lt;ol&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;All pilots of the winning company in &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;best-company&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; round will receive 5% more EP.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;All members of the winning clan in the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;best-clan&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; round will get two weeks of free Premium status. The victors will also receive 250,000,000 Credits for its communal treasury.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;The&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt; best player&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player ranking will be awarded six months of Premium advantages, 15,000 rounds of X-4 ammo, 10,000 Uridium and each type of mine 150 times.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Second place to tenth place&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player ranking won't fly away empty-handed, they'll get 10,000 rounds of X-4 ammo, 7,500 Uridium and each type of mine 50 times.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;11th place to 30th place&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player ranking will score 7,500 rounds of X-4 ammo, 3,000 Uridium and each type of mine 25 times.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;31st to 100th place&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the best-player ranking will receive 1,500 rounds of X-4 ammo, 1,500 Uridium and each type of mine ten times.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get tips for the new client in the %LINK_OPEN%Guide to the New Client%LINK_CLOSE%.&lt;strong&gt;Return to the old game client&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want to continue using the old game client until the next major update, please check the box below: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;%CHECKBOX% Use old game clientWarning:%EVENTITEM% is available for a limited time only. Act now before it's too late!Your account has been suspended/banned for the next %DAYS_BLOCKED% days due to scripting or exploiting.Trade drone receivedSpring FightSFBasic moduleSolar moduleStorage moduleTransport moduleXeno modulePrometium collectorEndurium collectorTerbium collectorPrometid refineryDuranium refineryPromerium refinerySeprom refineryLevel %level% %module% upgrade startedNot enough UridiumNot enough CreditsNot enough PrometiumNot enough EnduriumNot enough TerbiumYour basic module level is too low.Your Xeno module level is too low.%module% upgrade in progressLevel %level% %module% upgrade started%module% upgraded to level %level% (%date%)Level %level% %module% upgrade acceleratedLevel %level% %module% upgrade canceled%module% was instantly upgraded to level %level%.%module% activated%module% deactivatedRaw material transfer to Skylab initiatedRaw material transfer to Skylab completedRaw material transfer to ship initiatedRaw material transfer to ship completedPlease enter an amount.A transport is already underway.Not enough cargo spacePlease enter the amount of raw materials/resources for transport.Not enough UridiumNo transport underwayNot enough space in storage moduleNot enough energy is being produced to activate the %module%.Not enough energy is being produced to activate the %module%.An error occurred, please try again.Finished inInstantNormalBuildInstant buildCancelInfoUpgradeMaximum upgrade level attainedEnergyEfficiencyProductionTotal energy consumptionActiveInactiveXenomit consumptionArriving inTransport underwaySendInstant sendConfirm upgrade?Confirm instant upgrade?Confirm transport?Confirm instant send?Upgrade SkylabInstant upgrade SkylabInstantly finish the upgrade for %AMOUNT% UridiumINSTANTCANCELSkylab transportArriving in:Warning: If you cancel this upgrade, all invested resources will be lost.To upgrade this building, you still need %prometium% Prometium, %endurium% Endurium and %terbium% Terbium. You can find these items floating around space. Click on START in the top right to go to the space map and start collecting raw materials.Before you upgrade your Prometid refinery, you should build Prometium and Endurium collectors so that you'll have enough raw materials to refine. These collectors are located on the left in the Skylab.Before you upgrade your Duranium refinery, you should build Endurium and Terbium collectors so that you'll have enough raw materials to refine. These collectors are located on the left in the Skylab.Before you upgrade your Promerium refinery, you should build Prometid and Duranium refineries as well as a Xeno module so that you'll have enough resources to refine. These refineries are located on the right in the Skylab.Before you upgrade your Seprom refinery, you should build a Promerium refinery so that you'll have enough resources to refine. This refinery is located on the right in the Skylab.Upgrade your collectors or collect raw materials on the space map. Click START to go to the space map.ProductivityEfficiencyBonusRobotsActivein storageBuyActive robotsSkylab robots boughtRefresh skylabHelpYou can skip %AMOUNT% minutes by watching a full video.Skip %AMOUNT% minutesCINEMAThere is currently no video available.You have to watch the full video to get an incentive. Please disable your adblocker!Skylab time bookedPvP eventPilot bioRanking1st place:2nd place:3rd place:&lt;strong&gt;50% EP Booster: Order 5,000 Uridium today and benefit from 50% more EP all day long!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt; Want to level up quicker? Then take advantage of this one-time deal TODAY ONLY and rake in more experience points! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For every 5,000 Uridium ordered today, you’ll receive 50% more EP for one full day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The more you order, the bigger the EP payoff: For every order of 5,000 Uridium, an extra day will be tacked on up to a maximum of five days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want five full days of extra EP? Then order 25,000 Uridium right off the bat and receive the 50% EP booster for the next five days!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Upon purchase, the 50% EP booster will be activated immediately (booster duration is calculated in real time). Order TODAY before it’s too late!&lt;strong&gt;50% honor booster: Order 5,000 Uridium today and benefit from extra honor for 24 hours straight!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your one-time deal for 50% more honor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For every 5,000 Uridium ordered, you'll receive 50% more honor for one full day!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An extra day will be tacked on for every 5,000 Uridium up to a maximum of five days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want five full days of extra honor? Then order 25,000 Uridium now!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Get 50% more honor for kills and missions and give your space pilot career a boost. Climb the ranks!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 50% honor booster will be activated immediately upon purchase (booster duration is calculated in real time).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get your hands on the honor booster TODAY!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New ship design for your Goliath&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt; Rise above the rest and stand out from all the other Goliath pilots with the brand-new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;blue Goliath&lt;/span&gt;. Not only does this design look great but it also comes equipped with a full month of free Premium advantages!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This unique design is on sale in the Payment area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You get one month of free Premium advantages with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you've ordered the blue Goliath, you can pick it up in the hangar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If you want this special design, then move fast - an offer like this only comes up once in a blue moon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Click here to get the new Goliath!&lt;strong&gt;Galaxy Gate Time: Score with every spin!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; For one hour, your chances of winning a galaxy gate part will be 50% higher!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; What are you waiting for? With lady luck on your side, you're way more likely to land a galaxy gate part. Seize your chance: Every whirl's a winner!*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Spin, win and build your galaxy gate: Prepare for the battle of a lifetime.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; * The likelihood of winning galaxy gate parts is increased for one hour, while the likelihood of winning ammo during this time is decreased by 7%.&lt;strong&gt;New ship design for your Goliath&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt; Rise above the rest and stand out from all the other Goliath pilots with the brand-new &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;blue Goliath&lt;/span&gt;. Not only does this design look great but it also comes equipped with a full month of free Premium advantages!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This unique design is on sale in the Payment area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You get one month of free Premium advantages with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you've ordered the blue Goliath, you can pick it up in the hangar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If you want this special design, then move fast - an offer like this only comes up once in a blue moon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Click here to get the new Goliath!Data Privacy PolicyEventWonPt.PtsTotalSELECT YOUR COMPANYMars Mining Operations is engaged in the overexploitation of galactic resources. Their #1 priority is to make a profit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You tough enough for the MMO? Then look no further: Determination will lead you down the path to success!Earth Industries Corporation believes in human ideals &amp; concepts. Their pilots benefit from being part of a big community. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Serve the community, further their cause and become the greatest EIC commander of all time!Venus Resources Unlimited doesn't only take good care of its employees, it also seeks to protect the galaxy and its inhabitants. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bring fame and fortune to the VRU and write space history with heroic feats of bravery!Select&lt;p&gt;Think you know everything there is to know about soccer? Then place your bets and you just might multiply all the Uridium you order in the &lt;strong&gt;24 hours before each game&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your &lt;strong&gt;Uridium&lt;/strong&gt; will be &lt;strong&gt;doubled (x2)&lt;/strong&gt; if you guess the winner, &lt;strong&gt;tripled (x3)&lt;/strong&gt; if you guess the &lt;strong&gt;winner AND the correct goal difference&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;quadrupled (x4)&lt;/strong&gt; if you guess &lt;strong&gt;the winner AND the correct score&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;BrazilGermanySpainArgentinaNetherlandsUruguayGhanaParaguayJapanPortugalCloseBetNo thanks.:-The final score is the one that counts (e.g. after the penalty shots).Your World Cup bet:ChangeInvalid betNo bet placedNo bet**final score* The bonus will only be applied to Uridium purchased in the payment area during the relevant time period.eurospoints€pts.EURPTSInvalid amountCurrency exchangedNot enough UridiumCurrency exchangedBankingExchangeExchange Uridium for Credits here and give your Credit account a boost, so you can get new ships, weapons, ammo and more.ExchangeCurrency exchangedUridiumCreditsThe BigBoy, one of DarkOrbit's strongest shipsSatellite drone, sells ore everywhereHST-2 rocket launcher, fires off rocket salvos100 Hellstorm rockets for your rocket launcher1 LF-3 laser, the strongest laser around18 MP1 lasers, the best-performing laser cannons4 flax drones, for even more weapon slotsPlease select if you're already a DarkOrbit player or if you want to create a new account. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Your account will also be valid for the Bigpoint portal and other Bigpoint games.You can only use one bonus code per account!Username:Password:Bonus code:Legal informationTerms &amp; ConditionsAchievement Special: 1 LF-2 laser cannonAchievement Special: 1 SG3N-B01 shield generatorAchievement Special: 3,000 UridiumAchievement Special: 2,500 MCB-50Achievement Special: 1 G3N-7900 speed generatorAchievement Special: 1 LF-3 laser cannonAchievement Special: 500 PLT-2021 rocketsAchievement Special: 5 repair creditsAchievement Special: 1 flax dronePack: Trade dronePack: BigBoy DefensivePack: BigBoy OffensivePack: PremiumPack: Log-disksTrade Drone Advantage Pack orderedBigBoy Defensive Advantage Pack orderedBigBoy Offensive Advantage Pack orderedPremium Advantage Pack orderedLog-disk Advantage Pack orderedDesign Independence Pack orderedVorteilspaket Design Glory gebuchtTrade Drone Advantage Pack orderedVorteilspaket Quest Belohnung gebuchtVorteilspaket Bonus Box gebuchtVorteilspaket Blast Time gebuchtReceived Iron GoliathVorteilspaket Serious gebuchtVorteilspaket Power Upgrade gebuchtVorteilspaket Hunt gebuchtReceived the Ultimate Battle Arena Season Iron Goliath Package50% Honor Booster: Order 5,000 Uridium today and benefit from 50% more honor points all day long!TODAY ONLY: Take advantage of this one-time deal and rake in more honor points! &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For every 5,000 Uridium ordered today, you’ll receive 50% more honor for one full day.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;The more you order, the bigger the payoff: You can have the booster for up to five days. For every 5,000 Uridium, an extra day will be tacked on!&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Want five full days of extra honor? Then order 25,000 Uridium right off the bat and receive the 50% honor booster for the next five days!&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt; The 50% honor booster will be activated immediately upon purchase (booster duration is calculated in real time). Act now before it’s too late!DarkOrbit Reloaded | MMO &amp; space shooterDarkOrbit Reloaded | MMO &amp; space shooterDarkOrbit | ClansDarkOrbit | PETDarkOrbit | ShipsDarkOrbit | UridiumDarkOrbit | Tech FactoryDarkOrbit | HangarDarkorbit | AchievementsDarkorbit | ShopDarkorbit | Galaxy GatesDarkorbit | SkylabDarkOrbitDarkorbit | Game ClientJoin the intergalactic struggle for control of the galaxy! ✰ In the terrifying vacuum of space, outmaneuver your enemies to amass fame and fortune. √ &lt;h1&gt;DarkOrbit - the browser-based, action-packed space game.&lt;/h1&gt;         Experience awesome adventures in a far-away galaxy. Play with thousands of real players in the Bigpoint browser game DarkOrbit.         Make a name for yourself: Choose one of three companies, join a clan and earn power and resources in this browser game. Fight side by side with your allies and work together to end the DarkOrbit war.         But even flying solo, you'll never be bored, thanks to an astonishing variety of challenging missions! DarkOrbit missions can include research, collection and battle. One thing's for sure: browser game fans will definitely find something to shout about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Galaxy gate livesGalaxy gatesTech itemsTech itemsProductionProductionConstructionConstructionUnder constructionAn error occurred. Please try again.No production facilities availableTech Center: Facility construction startedTech Center: Facility construction completeTech Center: Facility builtTech Center: Production completedProduce instantlyPRODUCE INSTANTLYBuy nowBUY NOWProducePRODUCEEffect:Duration:Cooldown:ImmediatelyCancel&lt;br /&gt;productionProduction canceledTech item availableDelete techDelete tech itemsTech deletedTech items deletedEnergy leechThe energy leech transforms %TECH_VALUE%% of the UCB laser damage you cause into HP and transfers it back to your ship. Only works with UCB Laser Ammo!Transforms %TECH_EFFECT%% of laser damage into HP and transfers it back to your ship%TECH_DURATION% minutes%TECH_COOLDOWN% minutesChain impulseAn energy pulse which locks onto one target and then onto up to seven other enemies, thereby causing a chain reaction of shield damage to each and every one.Can inflict up to %TECH_EFFECT% damage on a maximum of %TECH_ENEMIES% targetsImmediately%TECH_COOLDOWN% minutePrecision targeterThe precision targeter is a highly accurate targeting system that increases the hit ratio of normal rockets by %TECH_VALUE%% for a certain time.%TECH_EFFECT%% hit ratio15 minutes%TECH_COOLDOWN% minutesBackup shieldsThe backup shields will bring your ship's shields back up immediately.%TECH_EFFECT% shield strengthImmediately%TECH_COOLDOWN% minutesBattle repair botWhen the battle repair bot is activated, it repairs %TECH_VALUE% HP per second. It can be used even in the toughest battle situations.%TECH_EFFECT% HPImmediately%TECH_COOLDOWN% minutesSpeed leechThe speed leech sucks energy from your enemy's speed generators and reroutes it to your ship. Your target will fly 25% slower for %TECH_DURATION% seconds, and your ship will fly 25% faster for %TECH_DURATION% seconds.Your target's speed decreases by 25% and yours increases by 25%.5 seconds%TECH_COOLDOWN% minutesEffect:%PRICE% Uridium%PRICE% U.%TIME_SECONDS% seconds%TIME_SECONDS% sec.%TIME_MINUTES% minutes%TIME_MINUTES% min.%TIME_HOURS% hours%TIME_HOURS% hr.%TIME_HOURS% hr. %TIME_MINUTES% min.%TIME_HOURS% hr. %TIME_MINUTES% min.Production time:ReadyTech activatedwaiting ...Cooling down ...Tech boughtTech production startedFacility builtNot enough Uridium availableNot enough Credits availableNot enough Seprom availableNot enough log-disks availableProduction facility builtTech production startedTech purchasedTech production canceledTech deletedWant to buy this tech item now?&lt;br /&gt;No Credits, Seprom or log-disks will be used.Tech Center info&lt;/span&gt;             &lt;p&gt;The Tech Center is a factory where you can use various materials to produce hi-tech defense and attack items, including &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="#faq_techs"&gt;Tech items&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and drones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;             &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Select an item to produce from the left-hand menu in the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="#faq_tf"&gt;Factory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Click on Produce to make the item: Make sure you have all the required &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="#tf_resources"&gt;materials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for production.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Build extra &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="#tf_factory"&gt;production facilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to produce multiple items simultaneously.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;             Or:&lt;br&gt;             &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Select a drone type in the Factory&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;and build the drone instantly for Uridium.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;In the pirate booty you'll sometimes find pieces of the blueprints. The advantage: You can build a drone with them without additional costs.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Tip: Each piece of the blueprints that you find reduces the price for buying it immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt; Use tech items in &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="#tf_factory"&gt;battle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; directly on the space map. Start now and turn your ship into the ultimate spacefighter!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; For more information, take a look in our &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="#faq_tf"&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;             &lt;br class="linecountSix"&gt;&lt;a name="faq_tf" &gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;What exactly is the Tech Center?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tech Center is a factory where you can produce hi-tech items that can be used to acquire new skills or enhance existing ones. There are many different tech items available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;Where is the Tech Center located?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 &lt;p&gt;The Tech Center can be found in the Skylab. Click on Skylab in the main menu and the Skylab page will open. There are two tabs on this page: One for the Skylab and one for the Tech Center. Click on the Tech Center tab to go there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="faq_techs"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;What type of tech items can be produced?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 &lt;p&gt;There are many different items that can be produced in the Tech Center, such as:&lt;a name="help_subnav_ELA_1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="text_subheadline"&gt;Energy leech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;Plain and simple: The more damage you inflict on your enemy, the more the energy leech will repair your ship.&lt;br&gt; This item transforms a certain percentage of the laser damage you cause into HP and transfers it back to your ship in the form of energy, thus allowing you to repair your ship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="help_subnav_ECI_1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="text_subheadline"&gt;Chain impulse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;When you shoot at an enemy with the chain impulse, it emits an energy pulse which inflicts damage on your target. The pulse then ricochets to your next adversary, and the next one, causing each one less damage than the one before.                    It can inflict damage on a maximum of 7 opponents, after which it dissipates, becoming too weak to damage further ships. The chain impulse penetrates through all shields, causing direct damage to the ships in its path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="help_subnav_RPM_1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="text_subheadline"&gt;Precision targeter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;This tech item increases your hit ratio to 100% for a certain amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="help_subnav_SBU_1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="text_subheadline"&gt;Backup shields&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;The backup shields are a type of reserve shield. If your regular shield is destroyed in battle, the backup shields will replace some of your shield defenses instantly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="help_subnav_BRB_1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="text_subheadline"&gt;Battle repair bot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;The battle repair bot functions like a normal repair bot, but it was developed for use in battle situations. It can resist enemy fire for a short time, repairing 10,000 HP per second for 10 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="help_subnav_SL_1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="text_subheadline"&gt;Speed leech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                    &lt;p&gt;The speed leech sucks energy from enemy speed generators and transfers it to your ship. Your target's speed decreases by 25% and yours increases by 25% for 5 seconds. The speed leech is an effective accessory in fight or flight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;How many tech items can be produced?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 &lt;p&gt;At the beginning, you can only produce one tech item at a time. If you build multiple production facilities, you can produce multiple items simultaneously. Once your Tech Center has been completely expanded, you'll be able to produce three tech items at once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="tf_resources"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;What materials are needed to produce tech items?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 &lt;p&gt;The materials needed to make tech items are Credits, Seprom and log-disks. Credits and log-disks can be collected in the game and Seprom has to created in the Skylab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;Can tech items be produced if all required materials aren't available?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                 &lt;p&gt;Yes. In this case, you can replace the missing materials with Uridium. Uridium helps to speed up the production process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name="tf_factory"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;Where do the finished tech items go? How can they be used?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                &lt;p&gt;Your tech items will appear in a special box on the space map once they have been manufactured. There you'll be able to see how long you can use them for and how long the cool-down time is. Click on the tech item symbol to use the item.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="text_headline"&gt;Can I use multiple tech items at once?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;                &lt;p&gt;Yes. Using multiple tech items at once will turn your ship into an ultimate starfighter. Remember to use your tech items effectively: Combine different types of tech items for a killer effect. Combining the same type of tech items won't do much for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="text_info"&gt;Note: All materials required for production of this tech will be lost if it is deleted or its production is canceled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="text_info"&gt;Note: All tech items of this kind will be deleted from this production hall.&lt;/span&gt;Are you sure you want to delete this production facility's tech items?Precision targeter usedChain impulse usedEnergy leech usedBackup shields usedBattle repair bot usedOKCancelYou've already built the %DRONE% drone.You do not have enough Uridium or parts to construct the %DRONE% drone.Daily Login BonusBonusCongratulations!You got today's login bonus!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in two days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in three days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in four days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in five days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in five days in a row again!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the same bonus another time.10,000 Credits&lt;br /&gt;50 PLT-2026 rockets&lt;br /&gt;1 extra energy300 MCB-25 ammo&lt;br /&gt;25,000 Credits&lt;br /&gt;1 extra energy50 PLT-2021 rockets&lt;br /&gt;1 jump Credit&lt;br /&gt;1 extra energy250 MCB-50 ammo&lt;br /&gt;1 repair credit&lt;br /&gt;1 extra energy1 log-disk&lt;br /&gt;200 Uridium&lt;br /&gt;1 extra energy10,000 Credits&lt;br /&gt;50 PLT-2026 rockets&lt;br /&gt;1 Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt;1 Kuiper Gate part300 MCB-25 ammo&lt;br /&gt;25,000 Credits&lt;br /&gt;1 Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt;1 Kuiper Gate part50 PLT-2021 rockets&lt;br /&gt;1 Jump Voucher&lt;br /&gt;1 Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt;2 Kuiper Gate parts250 MCB-50 ammo&lt;br /&gt;1 Repair Voucher&lt;br /&gt;1 Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt;2 Kuiper Gate parts1 log-disk&lt;br /&gt;200 Uridium&lt;br /&gt;1 Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt;2 Kuiper Gate partsOKDay 1 login bonus receivedDay 2 login bonus receivedDay 3 login bonus receivedDay 4 login bonus receivedDay 5 login bonus receivedDay 5+ login bonus receivedSpecial login bonus received!Incentive bonusIncentive bonus&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bigboy Battlecruiser:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of DarkOrbit's strongest ships&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Goliath Battlecruiser:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of DarkOrbit's toughest ships&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Slot CPU 3:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;More space for extras on board&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;HST-2 rocket launcher:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapidly fires off rocket salvos&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;100 UBR-100 rockets:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keeps the rocket launcher fully loaded&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rocket launcher CPU:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Automatically reloads your rocket launcher&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Jump CPU 1:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teleports you home in a hurry&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;3 Flax drones:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drones with one slot each&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;4 flax drones:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drones with one slot each&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;3 LF-3 laser cannons:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strongest laser cannons available&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;10 MP-1 laser cannons:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quick and effective laser shots&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;3,000 rounds of MCB-25:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big blasts guaranteed&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;5,000 rounds of MCB-50:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big blasts guaranteed&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;10 SG3N-A02 shields:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shields for your ship&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Two months of Premium status:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benefit from two whole months of advantages for freePlease select if you're already a DarkOrbit player or if you want to create a new account.Please enter your username, your password and a bonus code.Username:Password:Bonus code:Legal informationTerms &amp; ConditionsDesign Pack receivedPlease select how many boosters to buy:Note:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can't use this bonus code because one has already been used for this account. Tip: Try using your bonus code on one of the other servers.&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;1 50% EP booster:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;50% more experience points&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;5 booty keys:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Booty keys for valuable pirate crates&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;5,000 Uridium:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;5,000 extra Uridium&lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;1,500 rounds of UCB-100:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Super explosive laser ammo &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;One month of Premium status:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free Premium advantages for one full monthTTNET bonusYou successfully invited your first friend and received a reward.One of your friends reached level 7. Here's a reward for you!A friend you recruited has reached level 10. You've earned a reward!Five of your friends reached level 7. Here's a reward for you!5 of your friends have reached level 10. You've earned a reward!Ten of your friends reached level 7. Here's a reward for you!10 of your friends have reached level 11. You've earned a reward!25 of your friends reached level 7. Here's a reward for you!25 of your friends have reached level 12. You've earned a reward!Incentive bonusIncentive bonusReceive prize from Hitac Moon LotteryCollect your winnings from the Hitac Frost Lottery.Collect your winnings from the Capsule Converter.Rewards received from the Hitac Lottery: %ITEM% (%AMOUNT%x)PROFILEACHIEVEMENTSSKILL TREEFRIENDS &amp; BONUSESBONUSESNamePlayer statsUser since:User since:Player activity:Player activity:Rank:Rank:Ranking:Ranking:Clan statsClan:None availableMembers:Player infoCountry:Pilot name:City:Age:Gender:Interests:Contact:StatusShow player profileShow clan profileEdit profilehrs.Changes acceptedChanges not acceptedChanges not acceptedNo changes madeSaveminutes%hours% hours%hours% hour%hours% hrs%hours% hrDate of birth:daymonthyearContact dataMaleFemaleSaveOpt. image resolution: 115 x 125 pixelOptimum resolution: 115 x 125 pixelInvite friendsINVITE MORE FRIENDSDaily Login BonusWait for friends to register and reach level 7Your friend registered and has now reached level 10.Collect rewardInvitedAccepted:Level:Bonuses received:Send inviteI know the people I'd like to invite.CancelorDaily invite statsInvite ticker for this instanceInvite limit reached?Yes?No?# of invites for all instancesMax. number of invites reached?Invite infoInvites sent:Open invites:E-mail invites sent:Accepted invites:Open e-mail invites:Remaining invites today:Bonus receivedBonus limit reachedCloseYour bonus when a friend reaches level 7:Your bonus for recruiting a player who has reached level 10:Bonus logbookNo infoBonusDateRewardInvite your friends to DarkOrbit and receive rewards5 repair credits1 CLO4K CPU10 log-disks5 log-disksrepair creditslog-disksItemsNostromo Diplomat Ship140,000 HP and 900 cargo spaceNostromo Envoy Ship10 laser slots, 160,000 HP, and 1,000 cargo spaceNostromo Ambassador Ship12 laser slots, 12 generator slots, 220,000 HP, and 1,500 cargo space1 month of Premium1,000 UCB-100 rounds10,000 UCB-100 Ammunition1 EP booster500 RSB-75 rounds10000 RSB-75 Ammunition200 EMP-1sDamage and Honor Boosters for 10 hoursDamage, Shield, and Honor Boosters for 10 hours2 LF-4 Lasers1 Havoc drone design200 extra energy10 booty keysA special new ship design that isn't available to purchaseBy the first inviteA player can receive up to 25 rewards for inviting friends.Reward for 5 friends who have reached at least level 7Reward for recruiting 5 players who have reached at least level 10Reward for 10 friends who have reached at least level 7Reward for recruiting 10 players who have reached at least level 11Reward for 25 friends who have reached at least level 7Reward for recruiting 25 players who have reached at least level 12Invite more friends and get more rewards!Never show againThe battle in space rages on and many space pilots have already lost their lives. Each of the three companies desperately needs new recruits. Invite your friends to DarkOrbit and your company will reward you handsomely.Here's how it works:Invite your friends to DarkOrbitReceive a reward for each friend you invite who registers and reaches at least level 7.For every friend who registers and reaches at least level 10, your Company will give you a reward.Recruit 5, 10 or 25 friends and get even greater rewards for your loyalty!Invite 5, 10, or even 25 friends to receive special Nostromo ships in acknowledgement of your loyalty.Your bonus for recruiting 25 friendsInviting 25 friends or more will get you many rewards, including this unique Goliath ship that you won't be able to get in the hangar!The Nostromo Ambassador is the most powerful ship of the Nostromo class. A classic reward for a sassy pilot!Invite your friends now to get this awesome design and many more rewards! Please enjoy 1 month of Premium access, two LF-4 lasers, 1 Havoc drone design, 200 extra energy, 10 Booty Keys, 10,000 RSB-75 ammunition, 200 EMP-01 Charges, and 10 hours of Damage, Shield and Honor boosters! Reward for 5 friends who have reached at least level 7Reward for 10 friends who have reached at least level 7Reward for 25 friends who have reached at least level 71 booty key10 extra energy1250 UCB-100 rounds500 RSB-75 rounds2 booty keys15 extra energy1500 UCB-100 rounds750 RSB-75 rounds4 booty keys20 extra energy 1500 UCB-100 rounds750 RSB-75 roundsA special drone formation not available for purchase.For a limited time only - Big-time special bonuses! Invite your friends now!The clock is ticking...Invite your friends to DarkOrbitInvite your friends before time runs out. For every friend that reaches level 7 within the time allotted, your company will give you a special reward.No invite goes unrewarded - if your friends reach level 7 after the time allotted, you'll receive the standard bonuses.Invite 5, 10, or even 25 friends to receive generous commissions in acknowledgement of your loyalty.Bonus for 25 friends reaching level 7:If 25 of your friends reach level 7 in the time allotted, you will receive numerous valuable rewards and a one-of-a-kind drone that is not available for purchase.Invite your friends now and get bonuses today!Do not show againDaily Login BonusYou can receive a Daily Login Bonus by logging into DarkOrbit several days in a row. The more you log in, the higher your bonus will be. If you've already reached the highest bonus, then you will continue to receive that bonus for every day you log in further. However, if you don't log in for one day you will not receive a bonus and the bonus will begin again at the lowest level.Next bonusLog into DarkOrbit tomorrow to open the %Stufe% bonus level and receive the %Boni% bonus.You've reached the maximum bonus level. For every day that you continue to log in, in a row, you will to receive the max. bonus.Bonus 1Bonus 2Bonus 3Bonus 4Bonus 5For every day that you continue to log into DarkOrbit you will be rewarded with a login bonus.The value of this bonus will increase daily until you reach the highest bonus level. However, if you don't log in for one day, you will not receive a bonus and the bonus will begin again at the lowest level.You got today's login bonus!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in two days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in three days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in four days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the next one.You got the bonus for logging in five days in a row!&lt;br /&gt;Log back in tomorrow to get the same bonus another time.50 million space pilotsA huge community of 50 million space pilots now navigate the infinite expanses of outer space - an amazing feat which we've just got to celebrate with a special event! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Crazy binary bots known as 1100101's are causing havoc in outer space: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get out there and shoot down these extremely hostile &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;binary bots&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; as soon as you cross their path.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take on &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;15 special new quests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fly through the &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Group gate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; which will re-open soon and stay open permanently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt; &lt;br&gt; Fire up your engines, space pilots. It's time for you to complete quests, take down aggressive bots and rack up awesome rewards!  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This mission can only be started once all open missions are closed.You were caught using a bot.The following was deducted from your account:&lt;br&gt;     &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;20% EP&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;10% honor&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;33% Credits&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;100% Jackpot money&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;100% galaxy gate energy&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;     &lt;br&gt;Additionally: For the next seven days, you will only be able to collect bonus boxes and cargo boxes once every 30 seconds.The following was deducted from your account:&lt;br&gt;     &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;50% EP&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;50% honor&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;50% Credits&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;100% Jackpot money&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;100% galaxy gate energy&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;     &lt;br&gt;Additionally: For the next seven days, you will only be able to collect bonus boxes and cargo boxes once every 60 seconds.Your account will be permanently banned.Your account has been banned until %datetime%.Your account is banned for another %HOURS% hours.Please enter the following code to reactivate your account and then click "Close":Invalid code entered. Account not reactivated.Account reactivated. Login available once again.LoginYour bonusCD bonusCreate new accountUse existing accountBackLoginContinueNews from %date%Follow us onFOLLOW US ONPirate HuntPHPirate Hunt - User rankingPirate Hunt - Clan rankingXXX% lower transport costsThis server has already reached its user limit.&lt;br /&gt;Try again later or pick another server.Sorry, this server isn't available right now.&lt;br /&gt;Please pick another server.This item can't be equipped to this slot.P.E.T. bonus S receivedP.E.T. bonus M receivedP.E.T. bonus XL receivedP.E.T. weekend dealAttention pilots!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Starting today until the end of this weekend only, we've got a very special offer for you: The P.E.T. weekend deal!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; When you purchase Uridium Packs this weekend, we'll give you one of three P.E.T. bonuses.Buy a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;75,000 Uridium Pack&lt;/span&gt; and receive a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;P.E.T. bonus S&lt;/strong&gt; for FREE.Buy a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;150,000 Uridium Pack&lt;/span&gt; and receive a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;P.E.T. bonus M&lt;/strong&gt; for FREE.Buy a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;330,000 Uridium Pack&lt;/span&gt; and receive a &lt;span class="breakingNewsHighlightBlue"&gt;P.E.T. bonus XL&lt;/strong&gt; for FREE.&lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;P.E.T. 10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;P.E.T. 10&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;10 G-REP1 P.E.T. repairer (Level 1)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;10,000 fuel - 100 P.E.T. fuel&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;3000 Uridium for the P.E.T renaming fee&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;P.E.T. 10&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 G-EL1 enemy locator (Level 1)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 AI-R1 radar protocol (Level 1)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;10 G-REP1 P.E.T. repairer (Level 1)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;20,000 fuel - 100 P.E.T. fuel&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;3,000 Uridium for the P.E.T renaming fee&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;To receive a P.E.T. bonus, you must buy one of the three Uridium Packs for 75,000, 150,000 or 330,000 Uridium. Once the transaction is complete, you'll automatically be given a P.E.T. bonus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; This offer is only valid this weekend - so act fast and become the proud owner of a P.E.T. 10 today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Over and out!Drones repaired.Do you really want to buy this item for %amount% Credits?Do you really want to buy this item for %amount% Uridium?Jump creditJump credit usedYou have received a jump credit.You have received jump credits.You've received an Upgrade Voucher.You've received an Upgrade Voucher.You received P.E.T. fuel.DarkOrbitDarkOrbitDarkOrbit will keep you coming back for more! Explore the infinite expanses of outer space in one of the best browser-based, action-packed space shooters ever made. Fly into the face of danger and go where nobody has ever gone before - either on your own or with others. Set a course to discover new galaxies and new lifeforms.Event box collectedYou received the following generator: %ITEMNAME%You received the following generators: %ITEMNAME%You received the following laser: %ITEMNAME%You received the following lasers: %ITEMNAME%You received the following CPU: %ITEMNAME%You received the following CPUs: %ITEMNAME% D-All&lt;strong&gt;Rising Star Pack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This pack will get you the following designs for your Goliath:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Veteran (10% XP bonus)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Exalted (10% honor bonus)CD-All&lt;strong&gt;All-In-One-Pack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With this pack you get the following Designs:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- 1x Spearhead Veteran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;- +5%-Bonus on honor&lt;br&gt;- +5%-Bonus on XP&lt;br&gt;- Cargo: 500&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- 1x Aegis Veteran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;- +5%-Bonus on honor&lt;br&gt;- +5%-Bonus on XP&lt;br&gt;- Cargo: 2000&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1x Citadel Veteran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;- +5%-Bonus on Honor&lt;br&gt;- +5%-Bonus on XP&lt;br&gt;- Cargo: 4000&lt;br&gt;CD-ALL-EL&lt;strong&gt;All-in-one Elite Pack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll receive the following designs in this pack:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- 1x Spearhead Elite &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;5% more damage&lt;br&gt;Cargo Space: 500&lt;br&gt;Rocket Space: 1,000&lt;br&gt;Laser Ammo Space: 7,000&lt;br&gt;50% active duration increase for Ultimate Cloak&lt;br&gt;50% active duration increase for Recon&lt;br&gt;25% active duration decrease for Target Marker&lt;br&gt;15% increase of the JAMX cooldown&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- 1x Aegis Elite &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;5% more damage&lt;br&gt;Cargo Space: 2,000&lt;br&gt;Rocket Space: 6,000&lt;br&gt;Laser Ammo Space: 17,000&lt;br&gt;50% active duration increase for Repair Pod&lt;br&gt;20% active duration decrease for Shield Repair&lt;br&gt;10% active duration decrease for HP&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- 1x Citadel Elite &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;5% more damage&lt;br&gt;Cargo Space: 4,000&lt;br&gt;Rocket Space: 8,000&lt;br&gt;Laser Ammo Space: 22,000&lt;br&gt;50% active duration increase for Protection&lt;br&gt;50% active duration increase for Draw Fire&lt;br&gt;25% active duration decrease for Fortify&lt;br&gt;15% active duration decrease for Travel&lt;br&gt;SD-All&lt;strong&gt;Special Design Pack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy this pack and get the following Skill Designs for your Goliath:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Solace (immediate ship hull repairs and 10% shield power bonus)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Diminisher (weakens enemy shields and boosts damage by 5%)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Spectrum (weakens all laser attacks and provides 10% shield power bonus)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Sentinel (increases shield strength and boosts shield power by 10%)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Venom (increases damage dealt and 5% extra damage bonus)D-HAR&lt;strong&gt;Harvest Design Pack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This pack will get you the following designs for your Vengeance:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Adept (10% XP bonus)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 Corsair (10% honor bonus)D-CORP&lt;strong&gt;Corporation Design Package&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For serious collectors! This pack will get you the following designs for your Goliath: All three designs grant a 5% Bonus on Influence points and an additional 7% extra damage against enemy pilots. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1 x Vanquisher (MMO)&lt;br /&gt;1 x Sovereign (EIC)&lt;br /&gt;1 x Peacemaker (VRU)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;D-TRID-TRI DescPusat EssentialsA stripped-down package for pilots who know that you can't go wrong when you stick to the essentials. Act now, and secure a Pusat for yourself while this offer lasts!Pusat DeluxeFor high flying pilots who like having many options at their fingertips, this Deluxe package offers you a Pusat design with all the bells and whistles: everything you need to embark on the adventure of a lifetime aboard this unique ship! Hurry - this is a limited time offer! You'll receive the Pusat ship design along with the High Flyer starter pack.S-DS-01State of the Art Sale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Lunar Industries, Titan Technologies, and the Kepler Foundries have all come together to create unprecedented deals for the discerning pilot who demands the best. Combining next-gen techniques and ultra-modern styling, these ships are being offered at astonishing prices. S-TRINITY&lt;strong&gt;S-TRINITY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Aegis&lt;br&gt;- Citadel&lt;br&gt;- SpearheadS-OS-01Classic Collector's Sale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Rediscover refurbished classic ships in this exclusive offer for the discerning collector. They don't make them like this any more! Admire the lines of these limited edition, hard to find, and discontinued ships - Yamato and Defcom are back! S-PT-01Special P.E.T. Deal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Mad scientists may know what’s best for their P.E.T.s, but they don’t always know how to control them. Don’t make the same mistake! Get company-approved upgrades for your P.E.T. for unbeatable prices instead!BeaconBeacon drone design&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; When you buy this unique Beacon drone design, you're doing your part towards helping refugees all over the world. All revenue from their sales go directly to the UNHCR.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Find more information, in the &lt;a href="http://www.bigpoint.com/darkorbit/board/threads/109329/" target="_blank"&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;.P.E.T. gear item expired: %ITEMNAME%P.E.T. gear items expired: %ITEMNAME%P.E.T. protocol expired: %ITEMNAME%P.E.T. protocols expired: %ITEMNAME%Banking MultiplierUridium Plus Pack ordered300 Hellstorm SAR deal bought.800 Hellstorm SAR deal bought.Upgrade Voucher Deal S completed.Upgrade Voucher Deal M completed.Upgrade Voucher Deal L completed.Trinity Pack bought.All information regarding time are based on the Central European Time - UTC+1All information regarding time are based on the Central European Summer Time - UTC+2Greetings Space Pilots,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Starting now, we're introducing a new system that will help us crack down on players who use illegal software applications (bots) to run automated tasks to gain an advantage in the game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Game accounts using a bot younger than four weeks will be immediately deleted without warning.         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Users who have game accounts with a bot older than four weeks will be penalized based on our new system with different penalty levels.         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Level 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The player will be banned for one day. Afterwards the player will be able to log back into DarkOrbit using a so-called CAPTCHA code. As a penalty, the player will have the following deducted from their account:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;20% EP&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;10% honor&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;33% Credits&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;100% Jackpot money&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;100% galaxy gate energy&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Level 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If the user continue to use the bot after the first warning and penalty has been issued, their account will be banned for seven days. Afterwards they will be able to log back into DarkOrbit using a so-called CAPTCHA code. As a penalty, the player will have the following deducted from their account:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;50% EP&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;50% honor&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;50% Credits&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;100% Jackpot money&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;100% galaxy gate energy&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Level 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If the user continues to use the bot after the second warning and second penalty has been issued, their account will be banned forever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reward received for the NPC Hunt - Lordakia: (%section%)Reward received for the NPC Hunt - Mordon: (%section%)Reward received for the NPC Hunt - Saimon: (%section%)CompanyUserClanGet the Adobe Flash PlayerIn order to play DarkOrbit, you need the latest version of Flash Player. Just install it to start playing!Download the Flash Player here for free: &lt;a href="%FLASHDOWNLOADLINK%" style="text-decoration: underline; color:#A0A0A0;"&gt;Download Flash Player&lt;/a&gt;Booty key usedGreen booty key used.Red booty key used.Blue booty key used.Used a Silver Booty Key.Used an Apocalypse Booty Key.Used a Prometheus Booty Key.Used an Obsidian Microchip.Booty key collected.Green booty key collected.Red booty key collected.Blue booty key collected.Apocalypse booty key collected.Prometheus Fragment collected.Obsidian Microchip collected.%COUNT% booty keys collected.%COUNT% green booty key(s) collected.%COUNT% red booty key(s) collected.%COUNT% blue booty key(s) collected.%COUNT% Apocalypse booty key(s) collected.%COUNT% Prometheus Fragment(s) collected.%COUNT% Obsidian Microchip(s) collected.Log-disk collected.%COUNT% log-disks collected.Part received for the Kronos Gate.Your loyalty reward: Rockets BDR-1212Congratulations! You completed the Birthday Gate.Congratulations! You completed the Birthday Gate.You withstood the Devolarium attack.Caution!You still have an open Premium Deal. Click the Uridium Plus button to put all of your advantages to use.Uridium PlusBankP.E.T. WeekPWReach the high score in as many high-score gates as you can within %time% minutesDestroy as many %npc_name%s as you can within %time% minutesCollect as much %resource_name% as you can within %time% minutesToday's challengeToday's high scoresYour pointsPoints: %score%&lt;strong&gt;Progress&lt;/strong&gt;ProgressYou found a piece of the drone blueprints.You found a piece of the drone blueprints, which will decrease the price to immediately build your 9th drone.You found a piece of the drone blueprintsYou're still missing a piece of the drone blueprints!Produce instantlyPRODUCE INSTANTLYBuildBUILDBuy nowBUY NOWDrone constructionEvery now and then you can find sections of the Apis drone blueprints in pirate booty. Once you have all the sections, you can build the drone. You can also build the drone instantly but this requires Uridium. Each part of the blueprints you find reduces the price of instantly building the drone.Occasionally you can find sections of the Zeus drone blueprints in the pirate booty. Once you have all the sections, you can build the drone. You can also build the drone instantly but this requires Uridium. Each piece of the blueprints that you find reduces the price of instantly building the drone.Here you can see how many pieces of the blueprints you already have.APISApis drone receivedApisApis drone with two slotsBD-03 AEpic droneApis droneZEUSZeus drone receivedZeusZeus drone with two slotsED-04 ZEpic droneZeus droneP.E.T. week rewardGroup reward&lt;strong&gt;200 log-disk&lt;/strong&gt; deal completed&lt;strong&gt;600 log-disk&lt;/strong&gt; deal completed&lt;strong&gt;600 log-disk XL&lt;/strong&gt; deal completed&lt;strong&gt;40 booty keys&lt;/strong&gt; deal completed&lt;strong&gt;120 booty keys&lt;/strong&gt; deal completed&lt;strong&gt;120 booty keys XL&lt;/strong&gt; deal completedDeal &lt;strong&gt;500 extra energy&lt;/strong&gt; completed.Deal &lt;strong&gt;1500 extra energy&lt;/strong&gt; completed.Deal &lt;strong&gt;1500 extra energy + 15 booty key&lt;/strong&gt; completed.Deal &lt;strong&gt;200 jump coupons&lt;/strong&gt; completed.Deal &lt;strong&gt;600 jump coupons&lt;/strong&gt; completed.Deal &lt;strong&gt;600 jump coupons + 15 booty key&lt;/strong&gt; completed.Deal made for &lt;strong&gt;20 red booty keys&lt;/strong&gt;.Deal made for &lt;strong&gt;40 red booty keys&lt;/strong&gt;.Deal made for &lt;strong&gt;40 XL red booty keys&lt;/strong&gt;.Deal made for &lt;strong&gt;10 blue booty keys&lt;/strong&gt;.Deal made for &lt;strong&gt;20 blue booty keys&lt;/strong&gt;.Deal made for &lt;strong&gt;20 XL blue booty keys&lt;/strong&gt;.250 Extra Energy for completing the motivational surveyAll fueled up&lt;strong&gt;10 silver Booty Keys&lt;/strong&gt; purchased.&lt;strong&gt;20 silver Booty Keys&lt;/strong&gt; purchased.&lt;strong&gt;20 silver and 10 green Booty Keys&lt;/strong&gt; purchased.P.E.T. Deal M completedP.E.T. Deal L completedP.E.T. Deal XL + fuel up completedADVERTISEMENTAdvertisementIT PAYS TO SHOP AT OTTO: AN AWESOME BONUS PACK JUST FOR YOU!OTTO is sponsoring space pilots!         Treat yourself to something nice - whether it be clothes, multimedia or sports items - and profit in return. Purchase a voucher worth at least €20 at Otto and get your very own DarkOrbit Power Pack!Here's what you'll get with your OTTO voucher:&lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;4 booty keys&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;4,500 rounds UCB 100 ammo&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;4,500 Uridium&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;ACT NOW: GET YOUR DARKORBIT PACK TODAYSHOP ONLINE NOWOTTO DealReceive two weeks of Start PremiumReceive four weeks of Start PremiumReceive one month of Start PremiumReceive two months of Start PremiumReceive three months of Start PremiumReceive one week of PremiumReceive 90 days of PremiumReceive 60 days of PremiumReceive 30 days of PremiumReceive one day of PremiumReceive three days of Premium30 day premium extension successful.*All time zones are in %TIMEZONE_SERVER_NAME% UTC%TIMEZONE_SERVER_OFFSET%. You are currently playing in the following time zone: %TIMEZONE_USER_NAME% UTC%TIMEZONE_USER_OFFSET%Add one hour to the times in order to determine your local time.Add %OFFSET_HOURS% hours to the times in order to determine the local time.Subtract one hour from the times in order to determine your local time.Subtract %OFFSET_HOURS% hours from the time in order to determine your local time.Your chance: the ZEUS droneAct now before it's too late: Blueprints for the 10th drone just found!... and then there were 10! Introducing the new DO drone - code name: ZEUSOur spies have out done themselves! They've discovered plans for new pirate drones amongst the loot: the &lt;b class="bn_highlight"&gt;ZEUS drone&lt;/b&gt;!         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;         &lt;div id="teaserImage"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;         &lt;b&gt;Golden pirates' booty with the chance of getting a ZEUS drone&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Apparently, pirates have lost a hefty load of this golden booty on one of their sporadic smuggler runs! This pirates' booty can be opened with the usual booty keys. It is even more valuable, though, because components for the ZEUS drone blueprints are hidden amongst the loot.         &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;Get going! Gather the valuable golden pirates' booty!&lt;/b&gt; Our technicians already have everything retooled so you can have the ZEUS drone built like the system of the APIS drones in the tech center.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; If you're smart, you'll move fast: The amount of pirates' booty seems to be limited. Be the first one to grab the valuable blueprints and you'll become the proud owner of the 10th drone: ZEUS!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;b&gt;Employ the pirates' technology now and use it wisely!&lt;/b&gt;Get going, pilots!ScoremageddonScoremageddon rankingUsername:Points:Score:Your points:InfiltrationINFILTRATIONUPCOMINGUPCOMINGComplete RankingHall of FameReward received for Scoremageddon.Reward for placing %RANK% in ScoremageddonYou have survived Scoremageddon.You were destroyed and have been eliminated from Scoremageddon.You have completed Scoremageddon with %AMOUNT% points.Your chance: the APIS droneAttention space pilot!Another chance for your company to hit it big: The pirates just lost precious cargo filled with finished apis drones!As a result, your chances of finding a complete apis drone among the pirate booty is three times higher than usual.         Tip: For a limited time only, the companies are reducing the prices of instantly built apis drones by 25%!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Act now - you never know when a chance like this will come along again!Reward for winter quests receivedBirthday gift receivedChristmas gift received.Gift receivedBonus receivedExtra energyThe auction ends in &lt;span id="counter"&gt;hh:mm&lt;/span&gt; min(s) Ended onDescription%USERNAME% - click for detailsClick for detailsAdd as friendCreate messageDisplay player profileAdd pilots to your blacklistThis pilot is on your blacklist.This pilot has been added to your blacklist.The pilot has been removed from your blacklist.This pilot does not accept contact requests.Contact clanDateActionNo entriesDateActionAmountNo entriesShopSHOP%VALUE%% Bonus HourTake advantage of this great offer! During this very hour you'll receive massive savings on every upgrade thanks to the %VALUE%% Bonus Hour!Hello Space Pilots,Aliens everywhere are trying to take over our server.         Our team of repair robots are working hard to fix the problem and get the server up an running shortly.Please excuse this brief interruption!You cannot change spaceships until the cool-down has been completed. Cool-down: %COOLDOWN% sec.You cannot switch spaceships until you have reached a space station.You cannot switch ships, because you are currently engaged in battle.Error! You may not enter the space map without a spaceship. The hangar you selected has not been equipped with a ship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Please select a ship and then restart.Trinity Pack bought.Need more Uridium? Click here to add some more Uridium!Ship warp completed%SHIP_NAME% warp to map %MAP_NAME% completedGoliath ship purchasedVengeance ship purchasedCitadel ship purchasedAegis ship purchasedSpearhead ship purchasedLaser Pack M purchasedLaser Pack L purchasedLaser pack XL purchasedShield Pack M purchasedShield Pack L purchasedShield pack XL purchasedStart-up help pack purchasedBattle pack purchasedSlot 4 CPU purchasedKick ship design purchasedReferee ship design purchasedGoal ship design purchasedPusat Essentials Pack bookedPusat Deluxe Pack bookedAs a premium customer you are entitled to a &lt;br /&gt;5% discount &lt;br /&gt; on all Uridium purchases.With the rebate advantage pack you &lt;br /&gt; profit from a 25% discount &lt;br /&gt; on all Uridium purchases.Premium customers with a &lt;br /&gt; rebate advantage pack&lt;br /&gt; are entitled to a 30% discount&lt;br /&gt; on all Uridium purchases. Dir wird ein ein spezieller&lt;br /&gt;Uridium-Rabatt von %SHOPDISCOUNT%% gewährt.One drawing entry posted.%AMOUNT% drawing entries posted.5 additional drawing entries received You received a Module for a Battle Station: %MODULENAME%.Your pack is being processed. Please wait.You have entered in the maximum amount of&lt;br&gt;codes allowed.System bonus: 1 day PremiumSystem bonus: 7 days PremiumSystem bonus: 14 days PremiumSystem bonus: 1 month PremiumSystem bonus: 2 months PremiumSystem bonus: 3 months PremiumSystem bonus: 4 months PremiumSystem bonus: 6 months PremiumBonus pack receivedRename HangarChoose a name for your hangar. The name must conform to the Bigpoint General Terms and Conditions.ConfirmCONFIRMHangar was renamed.Hangar couldn't be renamed. Please try again later.You need to own a Premium-Account to rename the Hangar.CreditsSepromLog-disksa.m.A.M.p.m.P.M.COMPANY CULTUREMars Mining OperationsI'm not going to blow smoke up your tush, so I'll just get straight to the point. We at Mars Mining Operations want you for two reasons: to mine ore and to eradicate all alien scum infecting our galactic sector. Do this successfully and you'll soon be popping rival pilots for thrills and honor!&lt;li&gt;Pragmatism, mutual support, toughness, and hard work ensure that merit is rewarded&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are the galaxy's toughest fighters and best engineers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us to unite humanity under Martian leadership&lt;/li&gt;Earth Industries CorporationPilot, these are trying times during which only those made of the purest inner steel can prevail! How tough is your mettle? We reward loyalty and impeccable manners with the best lasers Uridium can buy. Join us in the fight to cleanse our sector of all those cretins that stand in our way. For glory and privilege!&lt;li&gt;Education, wealth, comfort, and culture create superior citizens fit to guide humanity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are the galaxy's most cunning tacticians and best businessmen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us to rule the galaxy and turn alien races into humanity's vassals&lt;/li&gt;Venus Resources UnlimitedWe pride ourselves in our ability to push the envelope of technological advancement, while retaining a communal atmosphere. Some call us a cult desiring galactic domination, but they simply misunderstand our brilliant recruitment methods. We are always looking for talented pilots to help us destroy our enemies and shape humanity's future!&lt;li&gt;Curiosity, experimentation, intelligence, and social engineering have made us supremely adaptable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are the galaxy's cleverest scientists and most intrepid explorers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us to use alien and cosmic knowledge to further human evolution&lt;/li&gt;CONFIRMJOIN UP!SELECT YOUR COMPANY NOWYou can always switch Companies later onActivate the automatic purchase function here. Whenever you collect green pirate booty but do not have the required key, activating this function will enable the purchase of 1 green booty key, provided that you have a sufficient amount of Uridium.You may deactivate this function at anytime in the settings section. Don't display againAcceptYour e-mail confirmation bonus has been credited to your account (LF4 laser cannon).Your e-mail confirmation bonus has been credited to your account (LF4 laser cannon).Your e-mail confirmation bonus has been credited to your account (LF4 laser cannon).You've used capsules for the in-game lottery!You've used capsules for the Partner Lottery!You redeemed a capsule for the lottery that's offering material prizes.You solved the word puzzle and a capsule has been booked to your account!Collected word puzzle letter: %LETTER%You received a capsule for the lottery!You've received %AMOUNT% capsules for the lottery!Small Capsule Pack bookedMedium Capsule Pack bookedLarge Capsule Pack bookedXL Capsule Pack bookedXXL Capsule Pack bookedModule has been repairedTagTagedStundeStundenhMinuteMinutenmSekundeSekundensRepair Battle Station: %STATIONNAME%Battle Station destroyed.Battle Station Module destroyed.You destroyed a Battle Station Module: %MODULNAME% (Level %MODULLEVEL%).You destroyed a Battle Station: %STATIONNAME%.Match wonMatch lostCompanion AppUse the code to connect this free app with your game account and play the minigames to earn rewards for new items in DarkOrbit!This code is still good for %TIME% min.Uridium PackVengeance Starter KitPro Savings Kit1 Month Premiumfree ship repairs, twice as effective repair robots and much morethe rapid Vengeance ship, powerful generators and much moreSave big on elite ammo, elite long-range rockets, and much more!Type the words here:New CaptchaCaptcha code invalidHelpWIN UP TO %%CURRENCY%%10,000Look alive, Space Pilots! It's time for the Jackpot Arena - an amazing adventure that might win you up to %%CURRENCY%%10,000. Pilots from all over Orbit will be there, fighting one-on-one until there's only one pilot left standing. Register now for the battle on %DATE%. And, of course, may the best pilot win!Arena Tournament Test RunSpace Pilots, &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; The Jackpot battle as you know it is no more - It's been replaced with a fairer, 1-on-1 arena tournament system called the Jackpot Arena. One thing hasn't changed, though - the winner still takes home the big jackpot! 	But before we open up our first real Jackpot Arena, we'd like to have a test run to find and fix the bugs. All players can sign up for the test, which will take place on %DATE%. Once you've successfully signed up, a Jackpot Arena status window will appear on the spacemap. Please understand that once this window appears on the spacemap, you must participate in the test run. 	Since this is only a test for the new Jackpot Arena, you won't be able to win any cash or prizes. The real Jackpot Arena, which offers a cash prize, will take place on another date. 	Please post any problems you encounter in the &lt;a href="%BOARDLINK%" target="_blank"&gt;Forum&lt;/a&gt;REGISTERYour registration was successful. Good luck!Your registration was not successful. Please try again later!Because the test server is not available, we automatically logged you on to the %INSTANCENAME% server.You received a reward for rating our game.Du hast ein Schiffsdesign im Pament gekauft: %ITEMNAME%Du hast das Schiffsdesign Package CD-ALL im Pament gekauft.Item purchased: %ITEMNAME%Received item: %ITEMNAME%Received item: %CATEGORY% - %ITEMNAME%ShipShip DesignAmmunitionDroneDrone DesignEquipmentGeneratorLaserModuleYou've won the Team Deathmatch!Your well-earned reward:PilotPilot ProfileAccountAccount CenterI’m not going to blow smoke up your tucus, so I'll just get straight to the point. We at Mars Mining Operations want you for two reasons: to mine ore and to eradicate all alien scum infecting our galactic sector. Do this successfully and you’ll soon be popping rival pilots for thrills and honor! A gruff bounty hunter with a lust for direct action, Morgus Petterson found himself climbing the corporate ladder after years of loyally murderous freelance work for MMO and less reputable organizations. Exactly why he was hired to lead MMO’s human resources department is unknown. Regardless, his lust for execution - in all meanings of the word – has greatly endeared him to upper management. Those that must report to him call him ‘The Morgue’, though not to his face. It is said that he enjoys his nickname.Space Pilot, these are trying times where only those made of the purest inner steel can prevail! How tough is your mettle? We reward loyalty and impeccable manners with the best lasers Uridium can buy! Join us in the fight to cleanse our sector of all those cretins that stand in our way. For glory and privilege!Reginald Crowley descends from a long line of aristocratic “Leaders of Men”. Now an old warhorse uncomfortably confined to the corporate world, Reginald uses his senior position to lecture colleagues about how things ought to be done and to intimidate anyone he believes unworthy. His unending elitism has led to him being given the nickname “Admiral Blueblood”.We at Venus Resources Unlimited pride ourselves in our ability to push the envelope of technological advancement, while retaining our family atmosphere. Some call us a sick cult with allusions of galactic domination, but they simply misunderstand our brilliant recruitment methods. We are always looking for talented pilots to help us destroy our enemies and extend our galactic dominance.Vanessa Arkadium is a lethal assassin trained in the dark arts of information extraction – any and all means will be utilized. Raised by VRU from birth, Vanessa is completely indoctrinated and will do anything company management ask of her. Although still young, there are already legends praising her exploits, which has made colleagues envious and uncomfortable in her presence. Rival company operatives refer to her as the “Fluffy Dagger”.&lt;h1&gt;DarkOrbit – Join the intergalactic struggle for control of the galaxy&lt;h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Engage the thrusters and prepare for battle in the free space MMO. Team up with millions of space pilots for a bitter fight to the end&lt;h2&gt;Listen up space pilot! The vast expanse of DarkOrbit awaits! Choose your spacecraft and make for your battle station poste-haste to lend a fighting hand to the efforts of mankind and vanquish the alien vermin threatening the existence of man. Take up the fight as you range the galaxy at the helm of your very own space ship. Sign up today in DarkOrbit, become a space pilot, place your allegiances in one of three factions, while joining forces with fellow pilots or forming clans in an effort to round up valuable resources and lead your faction to victory, while dispatching scores of galactic garbage in the free-to-play space game for your computer’s browser! &lt;h3&gt;Whatever the Company you keep, it’s yours in the Galaxy&lt;h3&gt; However, evil aliens are not the only danger lurking about in Bigpoint’s action-packed space MMO! Begin your journey through space in DarkOrbit by selecting one of three rival factions - each replete with their own philosophy of achieving victory in this interstellar fight. Use force, might and aggression in the Mars Mining Organization to emerge victorious, achieve your goals with monetary might in the Earth Industries Corporation or wield cunning and grace to defeat your enemies in the Venus Resources Unlimited. No matter your decision, your mission remains the same: compile valuable resources and turn the tide of the galactic struggle to claim victory in this shooter full of fulminant space action. &lt;h3&gt;Command the Ship of your Choice&lt;h3&gt; Faction affiliations notwithstanding, Bigpoint’s smash space browser game gives you a plethora of unique options of putting your own personal touch on your individual struggle throughout space. DarkOrbit puts you in command – find your spacecraft from a host of specialized ships: from ships specialized in laying quick waste to enemy hordes and swift space ships fleet of foot designed to gather invaluable intel to bulky contraptions of high-tech brawn that lay down vital cover to your allies, while meting out heavy damage to targets. &lt;h3&gt;Join the Epitome of an Online Community&lt;h3&gt; What truly makes DarkOrbit unique, setting it apart from the competition is one thing: You! While other browser games claim to be multiplayer, they simply cannot hold a flame to DarkOrbit’s massive community: over 80 million active players blast off each and every day. Thanks to You and yours, DarkOrbit is the premiere cult online space games. Join the skirmish today alongside millions of space pilots or stand against floes of imposing enemies determined to see out your destruction. Arm your weapons and remain ready – with danger lurking at every turn, a moment’s hesitation can be the difference between success or failure. &lt;h3&gt;Fight with Friends, or Against&lt;h3&gt; Roam the myriad of galaxies of one of the all-time favorite space shooters. Fraught with danger at seemingly every turn, players must be on their guard and remain alert while scouring for resources, discovering new maps or completing a host of new missions. Form a clan with your friends and respected fellow pilots to boost your chances of victory and survival against hordes of imposing intergalactic beasts, or take on the most intimidating missions as you and your crew attempt to level up at the speed of light.You can only rename your Pilot once every 48 hours.&lt;br&gt; (Your last name change: %DATETIME%)This Pilot name is already in use.Your Pilot name must be between 4 and 20 characters long.Your chosen Pilot name contains invalid characters. You may use any character except (blank), &lt;, &gt;, @, +, ', ", &amp;, %, ;, /, \, -- and ?.Your chosen Pilot name is invalid.You are currently not permitted to change your Pilot name.This Pilot name is not permitted.Your Pilot name has been changed.ChangeCHANGEThe game is subject to the following:PILOT LICENSECORPORATE RECORDSDivisionHornetScorpionCobraBEST PILOTSBEST CLANSLIVECurrentUPCOMINGUpcomingOccupationFree AgentNEWSLETTERReaktivierungspaket erhalten:&lt;br /&gt; 4 x Laser LF-3&lt;br /&gt; 4 x Generator S3GN-B02&lt;br /&gt; 10.000 x Batterien MCB-50&lt;br /&gt; 1.000 x Raketen PLT-2021As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 25 x FWX-L&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x SAB-50As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 25 x FWX-L&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x SAB-50&lt;br /&gt; - 10 x EMP-M01As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 25 x FWX-L&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x SAB-50&lt;br /&gt; - 10 x EMP-M01&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x RSB-75&lt;br /&gt; - 10 x Booty Key Green&lt;br /&gt; - 1x DMG-B02As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 25 x FWX-L&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x SAB-50&lt;br /&gt; - 10 x EMP-M01&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x RSB-75&lt;br /&gt; - 250 x HSTRM-01As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 25 x FWX-L&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x SAB-50&lt;br /&gt; - 10 x EMP-M01&lt;br /&gt; - 1.000 x RSB-75&lt;br /&gt; - 250 x HSTRM-01&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x Design D-TR-01 (only if you don't have it)As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 150 x Extra EnergyAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 300 x Extra EnergyAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 750 x Extra EnergyAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 750 x Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x Hercules Drone DesignAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 750 x Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x Hercules Drone Design&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x BAT Drone Formation&lt;br /&gt; - 3 Month Premium MembershipAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 150 x Extra EnergyAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 300 x Extra EnergyAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 750 x Extra EnergyAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 750 x Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x Kappa Booster&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x Goliath Design HezarfenAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 1500 x Extra Energy&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x Kappa Booster&lt;br /&gt; - 1 x Goliath Design Hezarfen&lt;br /&gt; - 1 Month Premium MembershipAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 75 x Extra Energy - 5 x Green Booty KeysAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 150 x Extra Energy - 10 x Green Booty KeysAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 375 x Extra Energy - 25 x Green Booty KeysAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 375 x Extra Energy - 25 x Green Booty Keys - 1 x Hercules Drone DesignAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 500 x Extra Energy - 25 x Green Booty Keys - 1 x Hercules Drone Design - 1 Month Premium Membership - 1 Month Rebate Advantage PackAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 2 Weeks Premium MembershipAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 2 Weeks Premium Membership - 1 Week Rebate Advantage PackAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 1 Week Premium Membership - 1 Month Rebate Advantage PackAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 500 x Extra Energy - 1 x Hercules Drone Design - 1 x Goliath Surgeon ShipAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 500 x Extra Energy - 1 x Hercules Drone Design - 1 x Goliath Surgeon Ship - 1 Month Premium Membership - 1 x Lance Drone FormationAs a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 2 x High-Frequency Cables - 1 x Nano Case         As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 3 x High-Frequency Cables - 3 x Nano Case         As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 4 x High-Frequency Cables - 3 x Nano Case - 2 x Prismatic Socket         As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 5 x High-Frequency Cables - 5 x Nano Case - 3 x Prismatic Socket - 2 x Nano Condenser         As a token of our appreciation for your purchase, you have been given the following items:&lt;br /&gt; - 5 x High-Frequency Cables - 5 x Nano Case - 3 x Prismatic Socket - 3 x Nano Condenser - 2 x hybrid processor - 2 x micro transistor         Bonus booked: %PACKAGENAME%Package chosen: %PACKAGENAME%Don't show me these again.Ultimate Battle Arena rewardcompleted coldwave hardcompleted coldwave easyReward for 2nd place during last JPA 2014 received.Reward for 3rd and 4th place during last JPA 2014 received.Reward for 5th to 8th place during last JPA 2014 received.Reward for 9th to 16th place during last JPA 2014 received.Reward for 17th to 32nd place during last JPA 2014 received.You received the Pusat package deal.You received the victory day package1 deal.You received the victory day package2 deal.You received the victory day package3 deal.Ausgleichszahlung für inaktives PaymentpaketFeedback submitted. Thank you for your help.Oops, an error occurred. Please try again later.FeedbackSADECE 1,5 TLBu paket senin için tasarlandı!Muhteşem &lt;span class="text_highlight"&gt;1 TL paketi&lt;/span&gt; yenilendi. 1 XP BO1, 10 EMP 01, 100 PLT-3030, 1000 RSB-75’ten oluşan bu savaş paketine sadece 1 TL’ye &lt;span class="text_highlight"&gt;önümüzdeki iki saat&lt;/span&gt; içerisinde sahip olabilirsin.Bu efsane kampanyayı sakın kaçırma!DÜKKANUltimate Battle Arena Season %SEASON_NAME%: you have received the %RANKING_POSITION% reward pack.Ultimate Battle Arena Season RewardUltimate Battle Arena SeasonSeasonCitadel Specialist package purchasedAegis Specialist package purchasedSpearhead Specialist package purchasedEspionage Package purchasedFootball Superfan package purchasedGoliath Collector package purchasedGoliath Connoisseur package purchasedVengeance Served Up package purchasedDefcom Memorial Re-Issue purchasedYamato Memorial Re-Issue purchasedExpo16 Defcom purchasedExpo16 Yamato purchasedExpo16 Basics I purchasedExpo16 Basics II purchasedMimesis Set purchasedTartarus Set purchasedExpo16 Full Pack purchasedSmall Hope purchased.Great Hope purchased.1 Red Skull purchased.10 Red Skulls purchased.1 Blue Skull purchased.10 Blue Skulls purchased.1 Green Skull purchased.10 Green Skulls purchased.1 Red Reaper purchased.10 Red Reapers purchased.1 Blue Reaper purchased.10 Blue Reapers purchased.1 Green Reaper purchased.10 Green Reapers purchased.1 Red Robo-bat purchased.10 Red Robo-bats purchased.1 Blue Robo-bat purchased.10 Blue Robo-bats purchased.1 Green Robo-bat purchased.10 Green Robo-bats purchased.
    The Red Box purchased10 Apocalypse Booty Keys purchased.60 Apocalypse Booty Keys purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Space Cup design purchased.Hardware Starter Pack purchased.Hardware Tinker Pack purchased._TODO__TODO_Hardware Basic Pack purchased.Hardware Main Pack purchased.Hardware Advance Pack purchased.Blaze Spectrum Set purchased.Blaze Spectrum purchased.Blaze Spectrum P.E.T. Design purchased.Blaze Spectrum Drone Design purchased.Blaze Pusat Set purchased.Blaze Pusat purchased.Blaze Pusat P.E.T. Design purchased.Blaze Pusat Drone Design purchased.A1 Engineers Pack purchasedAce Engineers Pack purchased1320 Apocalypse Booty Keys purchased5000 Apocalypse Booty Keys purchased300 Red Booty Keys purchased1000 Red Booty Keys purchased200 Blue Booty Keys purchased660 Blue Booty Keys purchased1320 Booty Keys purchased5000 Booty Keys purchased250 Scrap obtained500 Scrap obtained500 Scrap and 5 Schism obtained700 Scrap, 10 Schism and 1 H-MT obtained1000 Scrap, 40 Schism and 6 H-MT obtained1000 Scrap, 40 Schism and 6 H-MT obtained1000 Scrap, 40 Schism and 6 H-MT obtained1000 Scrap, 40 Schism and 6 H-MT obtained5 Obsidian Microchips purchased12 Obsidian Microchips purchased25 Obsidian Microchips purchased65 Obsidian Microchips purchased135 Obsidian Microchips purchasedProxium Drop Chance Booster purchasedProxium Reward Doubler purchasedUltimate Proxium Booster purchased65 Obsidian Microchips purchased135 Obsidian Microchips purchased30,000 Uridium, 1 x Month Premium, 1 x 3 week Rebate Advantage Pack and 1 x 3 week Doubler Advantage Pack purchased40,000 RSB-75, 1.000 ACM-1, 100 EMP-01 and 20 CLO4K purchased.20,000 PIB–100 Infection Laser Ammo, 5000 Extra Energy, 1000 IM-01 Infection Mine, 1000 SL-M01, 10,000 CBO-100, 5 x 24 hours 50% HON, 50% EXP Booster Pack, Honor Booster BO1 and BO2 (5 x 10 Hours), Experience Booster BO1 and BO2 (5 x 10 Hours) and 1 x 5 week Rebate Advantage Pack purchased.Grab this excellent offer and get 15,000 Uridium, 2 weeks Premium and 50 Extra Energy.You can't miss out on this offer of 30,000 Uridium, 2 weeks Premium, a 1 week Rebate Advantage Pack, 50 Extra Energy and 5 Green Booty Keys.Get this opportunity before it goes. Offer includes: 75,000 Uridium, 2 weeks Premium, 2 weeks Rebate Advantage Pack, 2 weeks Double Advantage Pack, 100 Extra Energy and 20 Green Booty Keys.Superb value for money with this offer of 150,000 Uridium, 2 weeks Premium, 500 Extra Energy, 40 Green Booty Keys, the Yamato Ship and the Hercules Design. Ready for action!An exceptional offer you simply can't afford to miss. Includes 330,000 Uridium, 1 whole month Premium, 650 Extra Energy, 50 Green Bounty Keys, Yamato Ship, Hercules Design and the classic Goliath Surgeon.As thanks for your purchase the following items have been booked: 2 Weeks Premium, 50 Extra Energy and 10 Bifenon.As thanks for your purchase the following items have been booked: 2 Weeks Premium, 1 Week Rebate Advantage Pack, 50 Extra Energy, 5 BK-100 (Green Booty Keys), 20 Bifenon, and 4 Tetrathin.As thanks for your purchase the following items have been booked: 2 Weeks Premium, 2 Weeks Rebate Advantage Pack, 2 Weeks Double Advantage Pack, 100 Extra Energy, 20 BK-100 (Green Booty Keys), 40 Bifenon, and 10 TetrathinAs thanks for your purchase the following items have been booked: 2 Weeks Premium, 500 Extra Energy, 40 BK-100 (Green Booty Keys), 80 Bifenon, 20 Tetrathin, 10 Kyhalon, a Lava Pusat and a Lava Pusat Drone.As thanks for your purchase the following items have been booked: 1 Month Premium, 650 Extra Energy, 50 BK-100 (Green Booty Keys), 160 Bifenon, 80 Tetrathin, 50 Kyhalon, a Lava Spectrum and a Lava Spectrum Drone.As thanks for your purchase the following item has been booked: 3 Indoctrine Oil.As thanks for your purchase the following item has been booked: 10 Indoctrine Oil.As thanks for your purchase the following item has been booked: 30 Indoctrine Oil.As thanks for your purchase the following item has been booked: 70 Indoctrine Oil.As thanks for your purchase the following item has been booked: 145 Indoctrine Oil.Assembly collection: %ITEMNAME%Venom Designs Pack purchasedSolace Designs Pack purchasedPusat Design Pack purchasedSpectrum Design Pack purchasedAegis Elite Design Pack purchasedYamato Ronin purchasedDefcom Raven purchasedGoliath Ignite purchasedNostromo Ambassador purchased     Premium Obsidian Microchip Pack purchasedPlatinum Obsidian Microchip Pack purchasedUridium Compensation RewardedtodotodotodoHailstorm Drone Design purchased10 Hailstorm Drones Design purchasedPoison Phantom Drone Design purchased10 Poison Phantom Drones Design purchasedBlaze Phantom Drone Design purchased10 Blaze Phantom Drones Design purchasedSandstorm Phantom Drone Design purchased10 Sandstorm Phantom Drones Design purchasedPremium Obsidian Microchip Pack purchasedPlatinum Obsidian Microchip Pack purchasedYou purchased 5 Obsidian MicrochipsYou purchased 10 Obsidian MicrochipsYou purchased 20 Obsidian MicrochipsYou purchased 40 Obsidian MicrochipsYou purchased 71 Obsidian MicrochipsYou purchased 155 Obsidian MicrochipsYou purchased a Special Probability BoosterYou purchased a Special Benefit BoosterYou purchased a Special Combo BoosterYou purchased 5 Apocalypse Booty KeysYou purchased 10 Apocalypse Booty KeysYou purchased 20 Apocalypse Booty KeysYou purchased 40 Apocalypse Booty KeysYou purchased 71 Apocalypse Booty KeysYou purchased 155 Apocalypse Booty KeysYou purchased the Fatsali Kerem Bundle5 Blue Booty Keys10 Blue Booty Keys20 Blue Booty Keys40 Blue Booty Keys71 Blue Booty Keys155 Blue Booty Keys10 Red Booty Keys20 Red Booty Keys40 Red Booty Keys80 Red Booty Keys142 Red Booty Keys310 Red Booty Keys60 day premium extension successful.90 day premium extention successful.todoYou've been chosen to get this ace opportunity and you'll feel amazing when you see the discount in this pack!An exclusive offer just for you! Bursting with valuable treasures, why not grab the Vital Uridium Cache!A classy exclusive discount for the loyal heroes of DarkOrbit!<item name="history_deal-proxiumDrop"><![CDATA[todo]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-proxiumReward"><![CDATA[todo]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-proxiumUlti"><![CDATA[todo]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-frostDrone1"><![CDATA[Hailstorm Drone Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-frostDrone10"><![CDATA[10 Hailstorm Drones Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-phantomGreenS"><![CDATA[Poison Phantom Drone Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-phantomGreenL"><![CDATA[10 Poison Phantom Drones Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-phantomRedS"><![CDATA[Blaze Phantom Drone Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-phantomRedL"><![CDATA[10 Blaze Phantom Drones Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-phantomOrangeS"><![CDATA[Sandstorm Phantom Drone Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-phantomOrangeL"><![CDATA[10 Sandstorm Phantom Drones Design purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-obsidianPremiumMar"><![CDATA[Premium Obsidian Microchip Pack purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-obsidianPlatinMar"><![CDATA[Platinum Obsidian Microchip Pack purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-keyCopper"><![CDATA[You purchased 5 Obsidian Microchips]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-keyBronze"><![CDATA[You purchased 10 Obsidian Microchips]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-keySilver"><![CDATA[You purchased 20 Obsidian Microchips]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-keyGold"><![CDATA[You purchased 40 Obsidian Microchips]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-keyPlatinum"><![CDATA[You purchased 71 Obsidian Microchips]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-keyDiamond"><![CDATA[You purchased 155 Obsidian Microchips]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-plagueBoosterDrop"><![CDATA[You purchased a Special Probability Booster]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-plagueBoosterReward"><![CDATA[You purchased a Special Benefit Booster]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-plagueBoosterCombi"><![CDATA[You purchased a Special Combo Booster]]></item>
    <item name="history_package_masqueKey-copper"><![CDATA[You purchased 5 Apocalypse Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_package_masqueKey-bronze"><![CDATA[You purchased 10 Apocalypse Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_package_masqueKey-silver"><![CDATA[You purchased 20 Apocalypse Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_package_masqueKey-gold"><![CDATA[You purchased 40 Apocalypse Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_package_masqueKey-platin"><![CDATA[You purchased 71 Apocalypse Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_package_masqueKey-diamond"><![CDATA[You purchased 155 Apocalypse Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-tr-charityMarch2017"><![CDATA[You purchased the Fatsali Kerem Bundle]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-blue-copper"><![CDATA[5 Blue Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-blue-bronze"><![CDATA[10 Blue Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-blue-silver"><![CDATA[20 Blue Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-blue-gold"><![CDATA[40 Blue Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-blue-platin"><![CDATA[71 Blue Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-blue-diamond"><![CDATA[155 Blue Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-red-copper"><![CDATA[10 Red Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-red-bronze"><![CDATA[20 Red Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-red-silver"><![CDATA[40 Red Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-red-gold"><![CDATA[80 Red Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-red-platin"><![CDATA[142 Red Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="history_resource-deal-red-diamond"><![CDATA[310 Red Booty Keys]]></item>
    <item name="package_premium-extension-2"><![CDATA[60 day premium extension successful.]]></item>
    <item name="package_premium-extension-3"><![CDATA[90 day premium extention successful.]]></item>
    <item name="balance_delete_uridium"><![CDATA[todo]]></item>
    <item name="layer_special-offer_desc_pay_reactivation"><![CDATA[You've been chosen to get this ace opportunity and you'll feel amazing when you see the discount in this pack!]]></item>
    <item name="layer_special-offer_desc_conversion"><![CDATA[An exclusive offer just for you! Bursting with valuable treasures, why not grab the Vital Uridium Cache!]]></item>
    <item name="layer_special-offer_desc_veterans"><![CDATA[A classy exclusive discount for the loyal heroes of DarkOrbit!]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-obsidianPremiumFeb"><![CDATA[Premium Obsidian Microchip Pack purchased]]></item>
    <item name="history_deal-obsidianPlatinFeb"><![CDATA[Platinum Obsidian Microchip Pack purchased]]></item>
    <item name="collect_compensation"><![CDATA[Uridium Compensation Rewarded]]></item>
</resource>
